<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:J1a4qFX2vzg</id>
  <yt:videoId>J1a4qFX2vzg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Riders Of Destiny: Risking Life as a Child Jockey in Indonesia | Witness</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J1a4qFX2vzg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T20:13:48+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T20:13:49+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Riders Of Destiny: Risking Life as a Child Jockey in Indonesia | Witness</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/J1a4qFX2vzg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/J1a4qFX2vzg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Seven-year-old Sila is a child jockey supporting his family financially on the remote island of Sumbawa, Indonesia.

With the high unemployment rate on Sumbawa, Sila's parents no longer work because the money their young son earns takes care of the whole family.

Each race poses an enormous risk to Sila and the other young jockeys who spend up to 10 days competing in several traditional horse racing tournaments each year. Injuries are common, deaths occur, and Sila is one of the most in-demand jockeys of all the young riders.

Seen through the eyes of Sila and a local photojournalist, the film Riders Of Destiny is a rare insight into how some of Indonesia's most remote communities reconcile tradition with the need to survive.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="35" average="4.89" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2032"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Iw5luRX0b6s</id>
  <yt:videoId>Iw5luRX0b6s</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>South Africa: Security forces accused of fatal lockdown crackdown</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Iw5luRX0b6s"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T18:41:19+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T18:41:19+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>South Africa: Security forces accused of fatal lockdown crackdown</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Iw5luRX0b6s?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Iw5luRX0b6s/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Security forces in South Africa are being accused of using excessive force while implementing coronavirus lockdown measures.
They have allegedly killed at least six people. 

Al Jazeera's Fahmida Miller reports from Johannesburg - in the latest part of our series on the effect of the pandemic on human rights. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #SouthAfrica</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="47" average="4.74" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2714"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:TqIYMuWkPxc</id>
  <yt:videoId>TqIYMuWkPxc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Morocco's Bollywood Dream | Al Jazeera World</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TqIYMuWkPxc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T18:28:59+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T18:28:59+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Morocco's Bollywood Dream | Al Jazeera World</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/TqIYMuWkPxc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/TqIYMuWkPxc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Asked to pick a country where people are passionate about Indian cinema, few might choose the North African Kingdom of Morocco. Bollywood came to the country in the 1950s, where it was embraced for its glamour, dance, romance and pure escapism. 

There is no obvious explanation for the connection, although it may have started when Ibrahim al-Sayeh began dubbing films - including Indian cinema - into the local Arabic dialect, Darija.

Now, the most devoted fans have decorated their homes with Bollywood paraphernalia and perform Hindi songs at themed events - and there is sometimes an Indian section at the annual Marrakech International Film Festival attended by well-known actors and directors.

Others have gone even further, like Imane Karouach who left Morocco for India when she was 16. She has worked hard to become a jobbing Bollywood actress and, although not a mega-star, she has had several high-profile roles; she also runs a pizzeria in Mumbai.

This quirky documentary, filled with a wide variety of characters, voices and movie clips, is a fascinating snapshot of a world few outside Morocco knew existed. It also includes a contribution from legendary Bollywood actor Rishi Kapoor who passed away in April 2020.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="97" average="4.22" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="5147"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:RaVncsHmZZs</id>
  <yt:videoId>RaVncsHmZZs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sweden drops probe into unsolved 1986 murder of PM Olof Palme</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RaVncsHmZZs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T18:11:18+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T18:25:08+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sweden drops probe into unsolved 1986 murder of PM Olof Palme</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/RaVncsHmZZs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RaVncsHmZZs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Sweden has dropped its investigation into the murder mystery of former Prime Minister Olof Palme, who was shot dead 34 years ago in Stockholm city centre.
Sweden's prosecutor on Wednesday named the main suspect in the murder of Palme and then closed the 34-year old case.
But the locking away the files looks unlikely to give the country closure.
Al Jazeera's Paul Rhys reports from Stockholm, Sweden.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Sweden</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="84" average="4.81" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4510"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:42xF9Z5cnVE</id>
  <yt:videoId>42xF9Z5cnVE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>What does the domicile law mean for Kashmir? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=42xF9Z5cnVE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T17:42:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T17:58:53+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>What does the domicile law mean for Kashmir? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/42xF9Z5cnVE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/42xF9Z5cnVE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A new domicile law for Indian-administered Kashmir is fuelling anxiety among millions of people already enduring tough security restrictions imposed by India’s central government.

For decades, Kashmiris had rights on education, jobs and land enshrined within legal codes that accompanied semi-autonomy. But that all changed in August 2019, when the BJP-led central government revoked the region’s special status. In April the central government went further, introducing laws that dramatically expand who can live permanently in the newly-designated Union Territory of Jammu and Kashmir.

The new rules allow Indian citizens who have lived in Jammu and Kashmir for 15 years to claim a 'domicile certificate' for residency benefits, as well as those who have studied there for seven years. Children of central government officials who worked in Jammu and Kashmir for at least ten years can also apply, even if they have never set foot in the territory.

Officials within the BJP-led central government say the domicile law will usher in &quot;equality and dignity for all&quot;. But people across Kashmir are worried that the new laws will clear the way for people across India to move into the region based on scant documentary proof, taking jobs and opportunities from indigenous Kashmiris. Legal scholars say the new domicile laws will encourage “demographic flooding” of Muslim-majority Jammu and Kashmir and render stateless indigenous Kashmiris who are unable to prove their residency and obtain a domicile certificate.

We'll look at how Kashmiris are reacting to the domicile laws and their concerns for the future. Join the conversation.

TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream 
Subscribe to our channel http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#Kashmir
#India
#Aljazeeraenglish
#News</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="28" average="3.86" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="0"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:qWpH_OulveU</id>
  <yt:videoId>qWpH_OulveU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>What does it take to end racism? I Inside Story</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qWpH_OulveU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T17:17:44+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T17:45:11+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>What does it take to end racism? I Inside Story</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/qWpH_OulveU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/qWpH_OulveU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>African American George Floyd has been buried in his hometown. 
He's going to change the world - according to his brother.
It's hoped his story will become a turning point in the fight against racism. 
And that's not just in the U.S.
Rallies over racial oppression and police brutality are spanning continents. 
From the UK to Senegal, tens of thousands of people are kneeling, or chanting 'I can't breathe'. 
The gestures represent the moments a white police officer knelt on Floyd's neck.
So, how challenging is it to combat racism around the globe?

Presenter: Mohammed Jamjoom

Guests
Treva Lindsey, Associate Professor of Women's, Gender, and Sexuality Studies at  The Ohio State University
Thembisa Fakude, Researcher at the Al Jazeera Centre for Studies
Udo Enwereuzor, head of Race and ethnicity equality for COSPE, Cooperation for the Development of Emerging Countries

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #BlackLivesMatter #InsideStory</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="69" average="4.36" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4932"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:I7Przv6KQXM</id>
  <yt:videoId>I7Przv6KQXM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>George Floyd's brother testifies at Capitol Hill hearing</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I7Przv6KQXM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T17:16:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T17:34:18+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>George Floyd's brother testifies at Capitol Hill hearing</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/I7Przv6KQXM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/I7Przv6KQXM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>George Floyd's brother has told politicians to make sure his death is not in vain. 
Philonise Floyd testified at a hearing on Capitol Hill.
His brother's death in police custody sparked two weeks of protests across the United States and around the world. 
The House Judiciary Committee says it is answering protesters' calls for a fundamental change in the culture of law enforcement. 


- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #BlackLivesMatter #UnitedStates</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="41" average="4.32" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1603"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:8z4a8eJOjkg</id>
  <yt:videoId>8z4a8eJOjkg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Is Canada facing its own reckoning with racism? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8z4a8eJOjkg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T15:42:46+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T16:42:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Is Canada facing its own reckoning with racism? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/8z4a8eJOjkg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/8z4a8eJOjkg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Recent anti-racism protests in the United States have sparked a national debate in Canada about its own problems with equality.

Over the past few weeks, thousands of people across the country have been taking to the streets, calling for an end to prejudice and police brutality at home and abroad.

It is “time for us as Canadians to recognize that we, too, have our challenges,” Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said recently, urging citizens to join the fight against discrimination. 

However, other officials are downplaying the problem, sparking fierce backlash from minority communities across Canada. 

Acknowledging systemic issues is just the first step, activists say. The harder part is establishing programs to increase accountability and defeat anti-black prejudice.   

In this episode we ask, is Canada finally facing its own reckoning with racism? Join the conversation:

TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream 
Subscribe to our channel http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#blacklivesmatter
#ajstream
#aljazeeraenglish
#canada</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="718" average="4.13" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="20014"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:TCENnSAT4ns</id>
  <yt:videoId>TCENnSAT4ns</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Conspiracy to Massacre: Anti-Semitism in America | Fault Lines</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TCENnSAT4ns"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T14:30:44+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T14:44:08+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Conspiracy to Massacre: Anti-Semitism in America | Fault Lines</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/TCENnSAT4ns?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/TCENnSAT4ns/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Fault Lines examines rising levels of violence and threats against Jewish Americans and the anti-Semitic conspiracy theories that often animate these attacks.

Anti-Semitic hate crimes reached a five-year high in 2016. The next year, anti-Semitic incidents saw an unprecedented surge, and white supremacists marched through Charlottesville, Virginia chanting &quot;Jews will not replace us.&quot;

In 2018, the US witnessed the deadliest anti-Semitic attack in its history when a white supremacist opened fire at Pittsburgh's Tree of Life synagogue. Then, in 2019, according to the Anti-Defamation League, anti-Semitic incidents reached an all-time high, eclipsing every previous year on record.

Anti-Semitism plays a unique role in the dangerous worldview of white supremacists. It is often coded into terms like &quot;white genocide&quot; and &quot;replacement,&quot; which stem from the conspiracy theory that Jews are trying to change the demographics of the US.

Fault Lines decodes anti-Semitic conspiracy theories and speaks with Jewish families and community leaders struggling to move forward from tragedy against the backdrop of accelerating attacks.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="74" average="4.08" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2842"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:W_pkBaAcuXE</id>
  <yt:videoId>W_pkBaAcuXE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Brazil restores coronavirus data after controversy, court ruling</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W_pkBaAcuXE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T14:24:10+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T14:38:17+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Brazil restores coronavirus data after controversy, court ruling</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/W_pkBaAcuXE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/W_pkBaAcuXE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Brazil has restored detailed COVID-19 data to its official national website following controversy over the removal of cumulative totals and a ruling by the Supreme Court that full information be reinstated.
President Jair Bolsonaro's government was accused of hiding the truth when it took the data off its websites.
Al Jazeera's Priyanka Gupta reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeera #Brazil #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="69" average="4.77" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4461"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kwMEtaLxCvM</id>
  <yt:videoId>kwMEtaLxCvM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Trying to stay afloat: Dutch heritage vessels sail in protest</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kwMEtaLxCvM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T10:33:02+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T10:34:55+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Trying to stay afloat: Dutch heritage vessels sail in protest</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kwMEtaLxCvM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kwMEtaLxCvM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>In the Netherlands, a fleet of historical sailing ships is staging an unusual protest.
They want the government to do something to help them maintain their boats, which have found a new life as tourist vessels.
With the coronavirus pandemic and physical distancing measures making it impossible to achieve the volume they need, the owners fear they will lose their ships.

Al Jazeera’s Step Vaessen reports from Muiden in the Netherlands.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Netherlands  #Chartervloot  #Pampus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="71" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3747"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:sJ_oFMjUqt8</id>
  <yt:videoId>sJ_oFMjUqt8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Iran braces for new coronavirus wave after surge in infections</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sJ_oFMjUqt8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T09:30:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T09:45:14+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Iran braces for new coronavirus wave after surge in infections</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/sJ_oFMjUqt8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/sJ_oFMjUqt8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>An alarming flare-up in coronavirus cases in Iran has raised fresh fears of a broad COVID-19 resurgence, sparking official warnings of new restrictions and underlining the sanctions-battered country's challenge of returning to post-virus normality.
President Hassan Rouhani has warned stricter measures will have to be re-imposed if social distancing rules are not respected.

Al Jazeera’s Zein Basravi reports from Tehran.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Iran  #coronavirus  #covid19</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="98" average="4.71" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="8882"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:NfGG32m02Bk</id>
  <yt:videoId>NfGG32m02Bk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Yemen COVID-19: Fears cases and deaths are being underreported</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NfGG32m02Bk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T09:09:03+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T09:15:27+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Yemen COVID-19: Fears cases and deaths are being underreported</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/NfGG32m02Bk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/NfGG32m02Bk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Fears that the coronavirus outbreak in Yemen could be worse than thought are being compounded by claims that Houthi rebels are suppressing the real toll.
The UN and aid groups are also running out of money to help, with funding falling short of what is needed for basic aid in the country.

Al Jazeera’s Charlotte Bellis reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Yemen  #Coronavirus  #COVID19</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="43" average="4.81" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1983"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:2WjVV3e0Cn4</id>
  <yt:videoId>2WjVV3e0Cn4</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Latin America: Economic inequality makes coronavirus worse</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2WjVV3e0Cn4"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T08:11:59+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T08:16:00+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Latin America: Economic inequality makes coronavirus worse</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/2WjVV3e0Cn4?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/2WjVV3e0Cn4/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Pan American Health Organization says it is going to take a lot longer to stop the spread of COVID-19 in Latin America.
The number of infections is growing exponentially in Brazil, Peru and Mexico. 
Analysts believe economic inequality is largely to blame for the region becoming the new coronavirus epicentre.

Al Jazeera’s Manuel Rapalo reports from Mexico City, Mexico.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Coronavirus  #Covid19  #LatinAmerica</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="46" average="4.74" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2965"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:STg8DXekBd8</id>
  <yt:videoId>STg8DXekBd8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>UK: Oxford protesters demand Cecil Rhodes statue be removed</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=STg8DXekBd8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T06:49:09+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T06:52:09+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>UK: Oxford protesters demand Cecil Rhodes statue be removed</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/STg8DXekBd8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/STg8DXekBd8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>In the UK, a statue of an 18th-century slave trader Robert Milligan has been removed from outside a London museum.
Officials say it was no longer acceptable to the local community.
A campaign has been ongoing since 2015 to remove the monument to Cecil Rhodes, a Victorian imperialist in Southern Africa who made a fortune from mines and endowed the University of Oxford's Rhodes scholarships. 
Public pressure is building to take action and remove it, sooner rather than later.

Al Jazeera’s Rory Challands reports from Oxford, UK.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#RobertMilligan  #RhodesMustFall  #BlackLivesMatter</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="395" average="4.61" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="13138"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
