<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:xCwnMq8TSlc</id>
  <yt:videoId>xCwnMq8TSlc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rwanda genocide suspect Felicien Kabuga arrested in France</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xCwnMq8TSlc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T18:28:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T18:37:37+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rwanda genocide suspect Felicien Kabuga arrested in France</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/xCwnMq8TSlc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xCwnMq8TSlc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Rwandan genocide suspect Felicien Kabuga was arrested on Saturday near Paris after 25 years on the run, accused of playing a leading role in one of the worst massacres of the 20th century. 
The 84-year-old, who is Rwanda's most-wanted man and had a $5m bounty on his head, was living under a false identity in a flat in Asnieres-Sur-Seine, according to the French justice ministry.
 
 
Al Jazeera's Sonia Gallego reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Rwanda #France</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="102" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2391"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:zEABolcJNwY</id>
  <yt:videoId>zEABolcJNwY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Pandemic hits Ukraine’s surrogate birthing industry</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zEABolcJNwY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T18:11:46+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T18:12:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Pandemic hits Ukraine’s surrogate birthing industry</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/zEABolcJNwY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/zEABolcJNwY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The global coronavirus pandemic is also affecting the surrogate birthing industry.
Ukraine, like many countries around the world, has closed its borders to foreigners, preventing new parents from taking their children home. 
Al Jazeera's Katia Lopez-Hodoyan reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Ukraine #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="23" average="4.65" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="699"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:A5XjGuJe_DY</id>
  <yt:videoId>A5XjGuJe_DY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Can apps put coronavirus in check? | Inside Story</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A5XjGuJe_DY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T17:30:01+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T17:36:20+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Can apps put coronavirus in check? | Inside Story</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/A5XjGuJe_DY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/A5XjGuJe_DY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Health officials and tech companies around the world have been racing to develop smart-phone apps to control the spread of coronavirus.
Some governments maybe weighing rights violations and mass surveillance, but others have adpoted the technology.
Singapore is one of the first countries to launch a non-mandatory, contact-tracing app using bluetooth signals.
Australia, Malaysia and the UK have followed suit.
There have also been apps that go beyond contact tracing - notably in China, where a system has been built to collect people's health data and travel history.
India and South Korea launched similar apps.
But how effective are they? 
And do they endanger other human rights? 

Presenter: Sami Zeidan

Guests
Nishanth Sastry, senior lecturer in the department of informatics at King's College London.  
Ali Fenwick, a behaviourial pyschologist and professor of organisational behaviour at Hult Business School.  
Dr Patrick Tang is the division chief of pathology sciences at Sidra Medicine.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #InsideStory #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="19" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="996"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Ve9vanaj4cw</id>
  <yt:videoId>Ve9vanaj4cw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>US sees biggest food price rises in 46 years</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ve9vanaj4cw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T14:01:31+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T14:08:21+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>US sees biggest food price rises in 46 years</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Ve9vanaj4cw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/Ve9vanaj4cw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>In the US, grocery prices increased by 4.3 percent in April - the biggest monthly jump in 46 years.
The price rises have put more pressure on Americans struggling to make ends meet during the pandemic - with more than 36 million people out of work. 
Al Jazeera's John Hendren reports from Chicago. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #UnitedStates #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="163" average="4.85" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7726"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kd8_zMVxlhY</id>
  <yt:videoId>kd8_zMVxlhY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Why are some OPEC nations struggling to make any money right now? | Counting the Cost</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kd8_zMVxlhY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T13:23:47+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:43:57+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Why are some OPEC nations struggling to make any money right now? | Counting the Cost</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kd8_zMVxlhY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kd8_zMVxlhY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Not all OPEC nations are rich and can weather a storm like the coronavirus pandemic with oil prices also sliding into negative territory, however briefly.  

OPEC cartel leader Saudi Arabia is cutting subsidies and raising taxes but it also has massive foreign currency reserves that can see it through the crisis. 

But that is not the case for the likes of Oman and Bahrain, which have slashed budgets, though they could get help from Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates.

Our focus is those resource-rich nations that have had to turn to the International Monetary Fund and those that have not, as oil prices hover just north of $30 a barrel.

Algeria - The North African nation has seen its debt soar to 45 percent of GDP from just 26 percent in 2017. It had based this year’s austerity budget on oil prices of $50 a barrel.

Angola - In 2018, Africa's second-biggest oil producer received a $3.7bn loan from the IMF and could be banging on its doors again. It relies on the sale of crude for 65 percent of its tax revenue. 

Ecuador - Creditors have given the country a debt payment holiday. But it could still default on its $17bn debt. It also received an IMF loan of more than $600m.

And then there is Africa's biggest oil producer, Nigeria, which last month received approval for a $3.4bn emergency IMF loan. The country is dependent on oil for 90 percent of its export earnings. With crude prices cratering, it has little room to service debt.

Kola Karim, chief executive of the Shoreline Group, which has holdings in a number of Nigerian oil ventures, shares his thoughts with Al Jazeera.

Lithium vs Oil 

This is the stuff of science fiction. 

Wuhan University has developed a plasma thruster, a type of propulsion engine, that could potentially power the planes of tomorrow, and bring emissions-free flying a step closer.  

The pandemic has reduced global consumption of oil by about a third - with grounded jet airlines guzzling at least 5 million barrels of oil daily.

The coronavirus may just be the push green energy needs. It should come as no surprise that decline in fossil fuel usage has led to a fall of 8 percent in global carbon dioxide emissions, according to the International Energy Agency.

Andy Leyland, head of strategic advisory at Benchmark Minerals, discusses whether lithium, the stuff that powers much of our electric cars, can emerge as a winner from this crisis.

Saudi Arabia's 'sports washing' 

Newcastle United could be in the hands of new owners very soon. 

But the buyer comes with a lot of baggage. Saudi Arabia’s Public Investment Fund will own 80 percent of the English Premier League club. 

Saudi Arabia’s human rights record, the killing of journalist Jamal Khassoggi and the country's alleged theft of Middle Eastern Premier League rights could derail the $375m deal.  

Amnesty has accused Crown Prince Mohammed Bin Salman of using the glamour and prestige of the Premier League to cover up actions that are deeply immoral.  

Simon Chadwick, director at the Centre for the Eurasian Sport Industry, comments on Saudi Arabia's &quot;sports washing&quot;.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="60" average="4.60" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3762"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:mMeG1asuWzU</id>
  <yt:videoId>mMeG1asuWzU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Italy to reopen borders after strict lockdown</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mMeG1asuWzU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T11:55:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T11:55:35+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Italy to reopen borders after strict lockdown</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/mMeG1asuWzU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mMeG1asuWzU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>There are signs of hope in Italy, after the government announced it would allow travel to and from the country starting next month.
Since March, the country has been under one of the world’s strictest lockdowns.
It has hit the tourism-reliant economy hard.
Al Jazeera's Priyanka Gupta reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Italy #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="80" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="5746"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Vk_-NUR38eQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>Vk_-NUR38eQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Amidst Lockdown, Philippines's Largest TV Network Goes Off Air | The Listening Post</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vk_-NUR38eQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T11:54:31+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T14:54:11+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Amidst Lockdown, Philippines's Largest TV Network Goes Off Air | The Listening Post</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Vk_-NUR38eQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/Vk_-NUR38eQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>On The Listening Post this week: The Filipino government has forced local television network ABS-CBN off the air. Plus, COVID-19 is used as a cover to stifle voices of dissent in Hong Kong

Amidst lockdown, Philippines's largest TV network goes off air

The consensus of presidents and prime ministers just about everywhere has been that getting accurate news and information out is vital since it can save lives.

So what have the authorities in the Philippines done? Duterte's government has ordered the country's biggest television broadcaster, ABS-CBN, off the airwaves. The government says the network's franchise had expired, and so had its right to broadcast.

That is nowhere near the full story. President Rodrigo Duterte has persistently attacked ABS-CBN for its critical journalism, including its coverage of his so-called war on drugs. He had long threatened to take the network down.

Now that he has got his wish, other media outlets in Duterte's crosshairs are wondering if and when he will be coming for them. 

Contributors: 

Manuel Mogato - editor-at-large, PressOnePH

Inday Espina-Varona - former chair, National Union of Journalists of the Philippines

Ging Reyes - head of news, ABS-CBN

Paul Gutierrez - National Press Club of the Philippines

On our radar: 

Richard Gizbert speaks to producer Flo Phillips about President Donald Trump's confrontations with journalists by day and tweetstorms by night.

Under the cover of COVID: Cracking down on Hong Kong

Before the pandemic hit, hundreds of thousands of people in Hong Kong took to the streets protesting the erosion of their freedoms, demanding independence from China.

The months of demonstrations led to changes in Hong Kong's media ecosystem. Nascent, digital news outlets reporting on the front lines saw a huge jump in their numbers and support, a reflection of protesters' growing distrust in their mainstream media - and mainland China's growing influence.

Things are gradually returning to a new normal but when COVID-19 first emptied Hong Kong's streets, depriving those outlets of editorial content, a question arose - what will become of them?

In addition, both Beijing and Hong Kong authorities appear to have been using the virus as a cover to crack down on voices they do not like, including the city's only pro-democracy newspaper, the Apple Daily.

The Listening Post's Johanna Hoes reports on Hong Kong's changing media landscape, COVID-19, and the use of a pandemic to silence dissent.

Contributors: 

Mark Simon - executive, Apple Daily

Yuen Chan - senior lecturer, City University

Ronson Chan - deputy assignment editor, Stand News 

Tom Grundy - founder, Hong Kong Free Press


- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="47" average="4.23" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1508"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:2Jhi0SbT7DY</id>
  <yt:videoId>2Jhi0SbT7DY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Nigerian food prices rise during Ramadan</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Jhi0SbT7DY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T11:53:10+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T12:11:22+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Nigerian food prices rise during Ramadan</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/2Jhi0SbT7DY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/2Jhi0SbT7DY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Nigerians are complaining about rising food prices during Ramadan.
The cost of some items has doubled, and they are expected to stay high after the Muslim fasting month ends.
Al Jazeera's Ahmed Idris has been speaking with buyers and sellers in markets in the capital, Abuja.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Nigeria #Ramadan</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="59" average="4.73" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3416"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Z6Sska630Tc</id>
  <yt:videoId>Z6Sska630Tc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>UK eases restrictions: Some people now back at work</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z6Sska630Tc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T11:20:45+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T11:26:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>UK eases restrictions: Some people now back at work</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Z6Sska630Tc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/Z6Sska630Tc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Many workers in the United Kingdom have been allowed to go back to their jobs, and people can now spend more time outside.
But, there is concern that lifting lockdown restrictions too soon could lead to a second wave of coronavirus infections.
The UK is one of the hardest-hit countries in the world, with nearly 34,000 deaths.
 
Al Jazeera’s Jonah Hull reports from London.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#UKlockdown  #Coronavirus  #LockdownEasing</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="38" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2584"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:lnzf8FDNdqc</id>
  <yt:videoId>lnzf8FDNdqc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Netherlands: Climate activists protest Schiphol airport expansion</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lnzf8FDNdqc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T11:19:19+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T11:19:22+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Netherlands: Climate activists protest Schiphol airport expansion</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/lnzf8FDNdqc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/lnzf8FDNdqc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Dutch prime minister's plan to go ahead with the expansion of Amsterdam Schiphol Airport has angered environmentalists.
They say the coronavirus pandemic is the perfect time for The Netherlands to become more environmentally friendly.
 
Al Jazeera’s Step Vaessen reports from Amsterdam.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#GreenPeace  #Schiphol  #ClimateChange</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="39" average="4.79" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1670"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:eb1TqElNpiw</id>
  <yt:videoId>eb1TqElNpiw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Protest in Arizona as state lifts COVID-19 restrictions</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eb1TqElNpiw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T10:36:50+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T10:40:44+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Protest in Arizona as state lifts COVID-19 restrictions</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/eb1TqElNpiw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/eb1TqElNpiw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Many states in the United States are reopening parts of their economies, despite public health experts warning it will lead to a surge in deaths from COVID-19.
Arizona is one such state, and some people are opposing the move.
To date, more than 620 Arizonans have died from COVID 19, and the number of new infections is still rising.

Al Jazeera’s Rob Reynolds reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#UScoronavirus  #TooSoonArizona  #DougDucey</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="75" average="4.25" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2455"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:s3VRuqFa44Y</id>
  <yt:videoId>s3VRuqFa44Y</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Iraqi protesters remain in jail in test for new PM</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s3VRuqFa44Y"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T10:05:53+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T10:13:40+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Iraqi protesters remain in jail in test for new PM</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/s3VRuqFa44Y?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/s3VRuqFa44Y/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Iraq's new prime minister, Mustafa al-Kadhimi, ordered the release of demonstrators last week to ease tensions with protesters. According to the Human Rights Commission, at least 98 protesters have been detained in Iraq’s state prisons and dozens more are missing. But courts have so far not acted and this is being seen as the first test of al-Kadhimi's power to carry out reforms. 

Al Jazeera's Simona Foltyn reports from Baghdad.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Iraq #IraqProtests #MustafaalKadhimi</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="27" average="4.85" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1673"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:IjRiVosuqx4</id>
  <yt:videoId>IjRiVosuqx4</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>More displacement in East Africa as Lake Victoria swells</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IjRiVosuqx4"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T09:38:59+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T09:39:01+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>More displacement in East Africa as Lake Victoria swells</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/IjRiVosuqx4?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/IjRiVosuqx4/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Record floods have devastated East Africa this rainy season with almost half a million people displaced.
Lake Victoria is Africa’s largest lake and connects Tanzania, Kenya and Uganda.
It is at its highest recorded level.
 
Al Jazeera’s Malcolm Webb reports on what that means for the communities living around the lake.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#EastAfricaFloods  #LakeVictoria  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="79" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="6568"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:BeHkEBMRZOE</id>
  <yt:videoId>BeHkEBMRZOE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rising CAR unrest threatens to reignite war</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BeHkEBMRZOE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T08:57:39+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T08:58:30+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rising CAR unrest threatens to reignite war</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/BeHkEBMRZOE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/BeHkEBMRZOE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Rising violence in the Central African Republic is threatening to plunge the country back into war. Fighting has intensified between ethnic groups and armed gangs vying for territory. Aid workers say they are unable to help thousands of people who have been displaced by the conflict. 

Al Jazeera's Ahmed Idris reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#CAR  #CentralAfricanRepublic  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="43" average="4.63" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2174"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:bkMm_YRgP_U</id>
  <yt:videoId>bkMm_YRgP_U</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>US House Democrats push ahead with $3 trillion coronavirus bill</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bkMm_YRgP_U"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T07:22:34+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T07:22:35+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>US House Democrats push ahead with $3 trillion coronavirus bill</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/bkMm_YRgP_U?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/bkMm_YRgP_U/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A $3 trillion package aimed at helping those struggling to deal with the fall out from the coronavirus pandemic has passed its first hurdle in the United States.
But President Donald Trump is threatening to veto it.
He is also promising to deliver a coronavirus vaccine by the end of the year, a deadline medical experts say is unrealistic.
 
Al Jazeera’s Heidi Zhou-Castro reports from Silver Spring, Maryland.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#UScoronavirus  #CoronavirusReliefBill #COVID19</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="50" average="4.60" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3393"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
