<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:oMG7wToKqao</id>
  <yt:videoId>oMG7wToKqao</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>How should US police forces be reformed? | Inside Story</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oMG7wToKqao"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T17:08:45+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T19:11:12+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>How should US police forces be reformed? | Inside Story</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/oMG7wToKqao?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/oMG7wToKqao/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The killing of Black American George Floyd last month triggered protests across the U.S. and elsewhere against police brutality.
People are demanding justice and drastic changes to policing.
Activists say officers routinely discriminate against minorities, and use excessive force when making arrests.
The protest demands include cutting funding for law enforcement agencies, stripping police of military gear such as armoured trucks, and even abolishing police altogether.
The Democrat-controlled House of Representatives passed a police reform bill to ban chokeholds, combat racial profiling, and establish a national database to track police misconduct.
But the Republican-controlled Senate is unlikely to pass the law.
So is there a political will for genuine change?

Presenter: Imran Khan

Guests:
Jamira Burley - Human Rights activist

Steven Rogers - Retired police lieutenant

Elisabeth Anker - Professor of American Studies and Political Science at George Washington University.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #US #BlackLivesMatter</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="94" average="4.40" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4020"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:KrthPfOCzZw</id>
  <yt:videoId>KrthPfOCzZw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Pakistan: 4 killed in attack on Karachi stock exchange</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KrthPfOCzZw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T16:52:51+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T22:49:21+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Pakistan: 4 killed in attack on Karachi stock exchange</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/KrthPfOCzZw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/KrthPfOCzZw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Four people were killed after gunmen stormed the Pakistan Stock Exchange (PSX) compound in the southern city of Karachi in an attack claimed by ethnic Baloch separatists.

Four gunmen attacked the stock exchange building at approximately 10am (05:00 GMT) on Monday, firing indiscriminately as they charged past a security checkpoint at the compound's entrance.

Two attackers were killed at that checkpoint, security officials said, while the other two were shot dead while attempting to gain entrance to the building.

The dead included three private security guards and a police officer, hospital officials said. At least seven people were wounded in the attack.

 
Al Jazeera's Sara Khairat has more. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Pakistan</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="279" average="4.77" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="8261"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:B-TK1cm-vHk</id>
  <yt:videoId>B-TK1cm-vHk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>India's fuel prices at the pumps rise despite low oil prices</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B-TK1cm-vHk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T16:50:27+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T21:40:35+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>India's fuel prices at the pumps rise despite low oil prices</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/B-TK1cm-vHk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/B-TK1cm-vHk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The rising cost of petrol and diesel in India is provoking protests in many cities.
Prices at the pumps have increased almost daily for the past three weeks, despite low oil prices.
The government says it has raised fuel taxes to offset the economic crisis caused by the lockdown.
Critics accuse leaders of making huge profits from the struggling poor.
Al Jazeera's Elizabeth Puranam reports from New Delhi. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #India #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="152" average="4.68" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3707"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:WVdUM42BHr4</id>
  <yt:videoId>WVdUM42BHr4</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Ertugrul: Turkish TV's Ottoman phenomenon goes global | The Listening Post (Feature)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WVdUM42BHr4"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T15:58:16+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T16:31:34+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Ertugrul: Turkish TV's Ottoman phenomenon goes global | The Listening Post (Feature)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/WVdUM42BHr4?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/WVdUM42BHr4/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Every nation has a trove of stories - alluring, magnetic narratives that are retold time and again. In Turkey, over the past decade or so, Ottoman history - the opulence, conquests and power - has been one of the most popular storylines across media, especially on TV.

&quot;The recent interest in Ottoman stories and Ottoman narratives is not something out of air or without context - it has a historical background,&quot; Burak Ozcetin, Associate Professor at Istanbul Bilgi University told The Listening Post's Meenakshi Ravi. &quot;Turkey is a society in constant change, constant flux. In times of crisis especially, history plays a significant role in creation of identities. The rising interest in the Ottoman past in terms of TV dramas has been a really, really important phenomenon.&quot;

The demand for Ottoman stories on TV has gone far beyond Turkey. With five seasons, more than 400 episodes and hundreds of millions of viewers worldwide, Dirilis: Ertugrul, or Resurrection: Ertugrul, is one of Turkey's biggest television exports yet, and has helped put Turkey among the top exporters of TV content in the world. Set in the 13th century during the founding of the Ottoman empire, the show has helped launch a wave of nostalgia and fascination for the era that has become known as &quot;Neo-Ottoman Cool&quot;.

&quot;'Neo-Ottoman Cool' is a term that I and my colleague Marwan Kraidy coined to reflect that new image of Turkey that started perhaps around 15 years ago,&quot; says Omar Al-Ghazzi, Assistant Professor at London School of Economics and co-author of the academic article Neo-Ottoman Cool: Turkish Popular Culture in the Arab Public Sphere. &quot;It demonstrated that shift of perception from Turkey as an enemy to Turkey as a model ... Turkish soft power was perhaps at its height with the rise of President Erdogan - this went hand-in-hand with the popularity of Turkish popular culture, particularly Turkish TV series.&quot;

&quot;Dirilis: Ertugrul being popular specifically in the Middle East and the Muslim world is fascinating,&quot; says Senem Cevik, Lecturer in International Studies at UC Irvine. &quot;A show that is produced by a Muslim country, a Muslim regional power is very important, and having those characters in the shows that are powerful, strong, defenders of their nations and their tribes is something I think I would say the Muslim world is looking for.&quot;

For President Recep Tayyip Erdogan and the AK Party, reconnecting with the Ottoman era has been central to their messaging. Erdogan has pushed a notion of continuity from the Ottoman sultans through to himself and TV dramas such as Dirilis: Ertugrul and Payitaht: Abdulhamid - both commissioned by Turkey's state broadcaster TRT - have aligned nicely with the AK Party's communications strategy.

&quot;They are, in a way, rewriting the Ottoman history for the current Turkish public. They're trying to showcase a type of history that is continuous from the Ottoman Empire to the current Turkish republic in a way that it elevates the Ottoman history,&quot; says Ozcetin. &quot;'Neo-Ottoman Cool' is directly related with the Turkish Republic's quest for enlarging its sphere of influence in the region, both politically, economically and culturally.&quot;

Contributors:

Burak Ozcetin - Associate Professor, Istanbul Bilgi University
Senem Cevik - Lecturer in International Studies, UC Irvine
Omar Al-Ghazzi - Assistant Professor, LSE and Co-author, Neo-Ottoman Cool: Turkish Popular Culture in the Arab Public Sphere

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="744" average="4.66" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="12081"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:yFwHLK3k-v8</id>
  <yt:videoId>yFwHLK3k-v8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Are women being left out of the Black Lives Matter movement? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yFwHLK3k-v8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T15:44:21+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T21:17:52+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Are women being left out of the Black Lives Matter movement? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/yFwHLK3k-v8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/yFwHLK3k-v8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>George Floyd. Rayshard Brooks. Trayvon Martin. Tamir Rice. Eric Garner.

The deaths of each of these men at the hands of police have served as rallying cries for the Black Lives Matter movement in the United States.

But as BLM picks up steam, some are concerned that women are being left out of the conversation.

“If Black lives really do matter, all Black lives have to matter,” activist Kimberlé Crenshaw said this month. “That means Black lives across gender have to be lifted up.”

Crenshaw founded #SayHerName in 2014 to spotlight police violence against Black women, including the 2015 death of Sandra Bland in a Texas jail. The hashtag has gained new traction after the recent police killing of Breonna Taylor.

In this episode we ask, are women being left out of the Black Lives Matter movement? 

Join the conversation:
TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream 
Subscribe to our channel  http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#aljazeeraenglish
#blacklivesmatter
#ajstream</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="447" average="3.43" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="11393"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:yLnD1LLiY08</id>
  <yt:videoId>yLnD1LLiY08</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>China forces birth control on Uighurs to suppress population: AP</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yLnD1LLiY08"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T14:42:44+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T14:54:47+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>China forces birth control on Uighurs to suppress population: AP</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/yLnD1LLiY08?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/yLnD1LLiY08/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A new investigation says that China is carrying out a campaign to forcibly lower birth rates among ethnic Uighurs.
The Associated Press investigation found hundreds of thousands of women have had to undergo pregnancy checks, forced birth control implants, or abortions.
The Chinese government has denied the allegations.

Al Jazeera's Alexi O'Brien reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#China  #Uighurs  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="199" average="4.24" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="6670"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:XxUCZNdekNk</id>
  <yt:videoId>XxUCZNdekNk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Former French PM Francois Fillon handed prison sentence for fraud</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XxUCZNdekNk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T13:54:59+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T14:10:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Former French PM Francois Fillon handed prison sentence for fraud</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/XxUCZNdekNk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XxUCZNdekNk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Former French Prime Minister Francois Fillon has been handed a five-year prison sentence for fraud.
A court in Paris found him guilty of misusing public funds and embezzlement, for setting up fake jobs for his wife and their children.

His wife received more than a million dollars and has been convicted as an accomplice.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #France</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="68" average="4.82" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4105"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:LLKvPfO7beY</id>
  <yt:videoId>LLKvPfO7beY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>COVID-19: Thousands of foreign workers stranded in Chile</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LLKvPfO7beY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T13:53:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T13:53:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>COVID-19: Thousands of foreign workers stranded in Chile</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/LLKvPfO7beY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/LLKvPfO7beY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>In Chile, thousands of foreign fruit pickers are stranded because their savings have gone and borders remain closed.
Many are from Bolivia, which does not have full diplomatic ties because of a long-running territorial dispute with its neighbour.
Al Jazeera's Lucia Newman reports from Santiago. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Chile</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="22" average="4.64" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1961"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:7Z1Mwt-b7qY</id>
  <yt:videoId>7Z1Mwt-b7qY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Mourning in the time of COVID-19 | Between Us</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Z1Mwt-b7qY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T13:00:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T13:00:05+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Mourning in the time of COVID-19 | Between Us</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/7Z1Mwt-b7qY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7Z1Mwt-b7qY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Adrian Brown has been covering the COVID-19 pandemic in Hong Kong since the beginning of the outbreak. But the story really hit home when his father died in the United Kingdom and Brown suddenly found himself forced into the same reality so many others have faced - grieving from a distance.

In the latest episode of Between Us, Adrian Brown shares his experience mourning his father during the pandemic.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/
#COVID19
#CORONAVIRUS</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="216" average="4.70" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="6089"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:xkow93xBIYQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>xkow93xBIYQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>France ex-PM Fillon awaits verdict over corruption case</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xkow93xBIYQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T09:02:40+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T09:12:22+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>France ex-PM Fillon awaits verdict over corruption case</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/xkow93xBIYQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xkow93xBIYQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A verdict is expected in the corruption trial of former French Prime Minister Francois Fillon.
He faces up to five years in jail but says the scandal is a political smear campaign.

Al Jazeera’s Natacha Butler reports from Paris.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#France  #FrancoisFillon  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="40" average="4.70" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2441"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kps7ciRJPhc</id>
  <yt:videoId>kps7ciRJPhc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Mississippi votes to remove Confederate emblem from state flag</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kps7ciRJPhc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T08:39:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T08:49:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Mississippi votes to remove Confederate emblem from state flag</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kps7ciRJPhc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kps7ciRJPhc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Senators in the US state of Mississippi have voted to replace the state flag, the last in the nation to display the Confederate battle emblem.
The Bill now goes to Republican Governor Tate Reeves to be signed into law.
Many see the current design as racist for its links to slavery in the South. 

Al Jazeera’s Gabriel Elizondo reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Mississippiflag #Mississippi #ConfederateFlag</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="221" average="4.60" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7028"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:wfOcvgCCz7s</id>
  <yt:videoId>wfOcvgCCz7s</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>French Greens make gains as Macron’s party falters in local polls</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wfOcvgCCz7s"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T08:01:34+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T08:08:25+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>French Greens make gains as Macron’s party falters in local polls</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/wfOcvgCCz7s?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/wfOcvgCCz7s/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Greens appear to have made major gains in France's local elections, while President Emmanuel Macron's party has struggled. 
It is the second round of polls for mayors and municipal councillors, which was delayed because of the coronavirus lockdown.
The election is seen by many as a test of Macron's reforms and his handling of the outbreak. 

Al Jazeera’s Natacha Butler reports from Paris.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#France  #Municipales2020  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="78" average="4.69" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4111"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:RouKd00sAM8</id>
  <yt:videoId>RouKd00sAM8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Gunmen attack Karachi stock exchange building in Pakistan</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RouKd00sAM8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T07:36:39+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T07:41:21+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Gunmen attack Karachi stock exchange building in Pakistan</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/RouKd00sAM8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RouKd00sAM8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Gunmen attacked the Pakistan Stock Exchange building in the city of Karachi over an hour ago. 
A grenade was thrown as the men entered the compound.
Security forces were quickly on the scene and police say the attack is now over.
Several people have been killed including four of the assailants, an official said.

Al Jazeera’s Kamal Hyder joins us live from the capital, Islamabad.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Pakistan  #KarachiAttack  #KarachiStockExchange</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="2514" average="4.78" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="163790"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:2vI04YCbG90</id>
  <yt:videoId>2vI04YCbG90</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Brazil COVID-19: Protests over Bolsonaro's handling of outbreak</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2vI04YCbG90"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T07:22:27+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T20:26:11+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Brazil COVID-19: Protests over Bolsonaro's handling of outbreak</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/2vI04YCbG90?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/2vI04YCbG90/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Groups of protesters in more than 20 countries and in Brazil’s main cities have called for the resignation of President Jair Bolsonaro, saying he is a threat to democracy. 
The protesters called their international day of protest “Stop Bolsonaro”.
They criticized his erratic response to the coronavirus pandemic and what they see as threats against democracy. 

Al Jazeera’s Alessandro Rampietti reports from the Colombian capital, Bogota.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Brazil  #BrazilProtests  #Bolsonaro</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="107" average="4.74" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7340"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kiwOCDTO3j4</id>
  <yt:videoId>kiwOCDTO3j4</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Poland's Duda leads in presidential election first round</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kiwOCDTO3j4"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-29T05:46:21+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-29T05:55:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Poland's Duda leads in presidential election first round</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kiwOCDTO3j4?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kiwOCDTO3j4/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Exit polls suggest Poland's president has won the most votes in the first round of the country's election.
But Andrzej Duda has not picked up enough to votes to prevent a runoff poll next month.

Al Jazeera's Sonia Gallego reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Poland  #AndrzejDuda  #PolandElection2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="94" average="3.77" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4457"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
