<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:-UK2wohN13Q</id>
  <yt:videoId>-UK2wohN13Q</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>UK zoos' future threatened by COVID-19 lockdown</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-UK2wohN13Q"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T14:36:58+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T14:37:42+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>UK zoos' future threatened by COVID-19 lockdown</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/-UK2wohN13Q?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/-UK2wohN13Q/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>While many businesses have had to shut down, zoos have had to keep some staff to take care of the animals. And with no income from visitors, this case hit them hard.
The government of the United Kingdom is working on a fund to support its 141 zoos and aquariums which have suffered a financial setback as a result of the coronavirus lockdown.
But as Al Jazeera's Charlie Angela reports, some say it will not be enough to cover their losses.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #UK #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="15" average="4.20" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="167"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:6QDey-qQ8LE</id>
  <yt:videoId>6QDey-qQ8LE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>COVID-19 lockdown worsens migrants' suffering in Libya</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6QDey-qQ8LE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T14:35:17+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T14:36:12+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>COVID-19 lockdown worsens migrants' suffering in Libya</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/6QDey-qQ8LE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/6QDey-qQ8LE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>For migrants who have left African countries for Libya, life was already a struggle before the coronavirus pandemic.
Now, lockdown measures are leaving many without work.
Al Jazeera's Mahmoud Abdelwahed reports from Tripoli.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Libya #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="17" average="4.29" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="170"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Vqw6cbMjeU8</id>
  <yt:videoId>Vqw6cbMjeU8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Indonesia among countries struggling with social distancing</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vqw6cbMjeU8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T14:34:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T14:34:36+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Indonesia among countries struggling with social distancing</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Vqw6cbMjeU8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/Vqw6cbMjeU8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The outbreak of COVID-19, the disease caused by the novel coronavirus, has forced countries around the world to reassess what it means to be an essential worker. 
Drivers who are delivering food are one group at a higher risk of being exposed to the virus.
Indonesia is one of the numerous countries that are unable to practice social distancing and that leaves them fearful for their safety.
Al Jazeera's Jessica Washington reports from Jakarta.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Coronavirus #Indonesia</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="10" average="4.60" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="154"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:EC2zNBDmLas</id>
  <yt:videoId>EC2zNBDmLas</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>India Muslims targeted in attacks over coronavirus</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EC2zNBDmLas"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T14:32:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T14:32:42+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>India Muslims targeted in attacks over coronavirus</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/EC2zNBDmLas?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/EC2zNBDmLas/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>India has rejected a report by the US Commission on International Religious Freedom, which named it &quot;a country of particular concern&quot;. 
Muslims have been attacked after a religious gathering in the capital allegedly led to a rise in coronavirus cases, with the minority being blamed for the spread of the disease.
Al Jazeera's Elizabeth Puranam reports from New Delhi.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #India #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="61" average="4.08" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="549"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:ikqptTSiOUg</id>
  <yt:videoId>ikqptTSiOUg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Spain emerges from lockdown as strict measures ease further</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ikqptTSiOUg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T14:29:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T14:30:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Spain emerges from lockdown as strict measures ease further</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/ikqptTSiOUg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/ikqptTSiOUg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Spain plans to launch a $17bn reconstruction fund to deal with the economic damage caused by the global coronavirus pandemic.
The country is one of the hardest hit in the world, but it has seen the number of infections and deaths decrease.
That is why it has begun to ease restrictions in phases after seven weeks of strict lockdown.
People are now being allowed to exercise outside.
Al Jazeera's Alexi O'Brien reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Coronavirus #Spain</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="22" average="4.82" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="220"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:3KtiQSe2H3U</id>
  <yt:videoId>3KtiQSe2H3U</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro: Turning COVID-19 denial into media spectacle | The Listening Post (Full)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3KtiQSe2H3U"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T14:01:45+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T14:19:36+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Brazil's Bolsonaro: Turning COVID-19 denial into media spectacle | The Listening Post (Full)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/3KtiQSe2H3U?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/3KtiQSe2H3U/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>On The Listening Post this week: Brazil's President Bolsonaro and COVID-19 misinformation. Plus, how well has the WHO performed as a key information source during the pandemic?

Brazil's Bolsonaro: Turning COVID-19 denial into media spectacle

A president at odds with his advisers and scientists over COVID-19, who has said the virus is no worse than the flu, and whose supporters accuse the media of hyping up the story. Not Donald Trump, but Brazil's Jair Bolsonaro.

Even as deaths in Brazil surpass China, President Bolsonaro continues to downplay the pandemic. After firing his health minister, he went on to attend a &quot;protest&quot; demanding military intervention to lift the lockdown. He also has the support of two of Brazil's biggest media players, Record TV and SBT. Whether Bolsonaro is in denial, or just playing politics, they are standing firmly by his side.

Contributors:

Andrew Fishman - Managing editor, The Intercept Brasil

Gustavo Ribeiro - Founder, Brazilian Report

Bob Fernandes - Journalist and commentator

Leonardo Custodio, Postdoctoral researcher - Abo Akademi University

On our radar:

Richard Gizbert speaks to producer Meenakshi Ravi about a media storm in Pakistan, where a religious leader turned a televised coronavirus fundraiser into an attack on the broadcasters.

Who holds WHO accountable?

COVID-19 is the biggest news story most of us have ever seen. Of all the institutions responsible for getting information out, the World Health Organization (WHO) may be the most vital. 

The WHO is a specialised agency of the United Nations borne out of the recognition that no single country can manage a global outbreak, and that an international health body is needed to rise above the politics of national interests.

In this pandemic, however, the WHO has been accused of falling short of its mandate and was unable to act independently in accessing and assessing the outbreak. The WHO was only granted access to Wuhan in mid-February. And not only did it fail to verify the early information on COVID-19 coming out of China, but it amplified it by repeating Chinese misinformation.

On January 14, the WHO tweeted that there was &quot;no proof of human-to-human transmission&quot; of the coronavirus. But at the time, media in Hong Kong and other countries, were already comparing the virus to SARS and saying it was most likely transmitting from people to people.

The Listening Post's producer Nic Muirhead reports on the WHO, and how one of the most important news sources in the world may be compromised.

Contributors:

Lawrence Gostin - Director, O'Neill Institute, Georgetown University

Osman Dar - Global Health Programme, Chatham House

Stephen Buranyi - Journalist, The Guardian

Rana Mitter - Director, China Centre, Oxford University

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="40" average="4.70" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="351"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:6CyqlfRoIc8</id>
  <yt:videoId>6CyqlfRoIc8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Will the coronavirus pandemic lead to a food crisis? | Counting the Cost</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6CyqlfRoIc8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T13:35:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T13:50:47+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Will the coronavirus pandemic lead to a food crisis? | Counting the Cost</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/6CyqlfRoIc8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/6CyqlfRoIc8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>From a health crisis to a food crisis, the coronavirus pandemic is upending the world as we know it. The United Nations's World Food Programme (WFP) is warning of multiple famines &quot;of biblical proportions&quot; as tens of millions of people are plunged into starvation.

Long before the pandemic, the agency had been warning world leaders that 2020 would bring &quot;the worst humanitarian crisis since world war two&quot;. 

An estimated 135 million people face starvation and that could double to 265 million by the end of the year. It blames the perfect storm, the wars in Yemen and Syria, natural disasters and changing weather patterns. 

At particular risk are refugees and informal workers. For example, it is estimated that about 136 million people in India working in the non-agriculture sector are at immediate risk of losing their jobs.

With more than two billion people under lockdown, supply chains have been disrupted. But that disruption is not just in emerging and developing markets. 

The rapid collapse of economic activity has led to more than 30 million people applying for unemployment benefits in the United States and a sharp increase in demand at American food banks, according to food charities. And yet, farmers are destroying produce, dumping milk and culling livestock despite grocery stores struggling to stock shelves.

While rich nations have the financial muscle to see themselves through the crisis, it is the low income and developing nations that could see past economic gains disappear.

Maximo Torero, the chief economist of the Food and Agriculture Organization, explains what kind of effect the pandemic might have on the economies of developing nations. 

The spread of the virus among workers at US meat processing plants has raised concerns of food shortages. But, President Donald Trump passed an order to keep them open, which has been criticised by unions and some investors. 

Maria Lettini, the executive director of FAIRR, a $20 trillion investor group, explained how Trump's decision might sow the seeds for future pandemics. 

Loan or grants?

European Union nations hit hard by the coronavirus hope to convince others to provide them with grants rather than loans as they plan a route to recovery.

Italy and Spain would like to avoid taking loans, which would increase their debt burden. 

Italy's debt currently stands at 134.8 percent of gross domestic product (GDP) and that number is expected to rise to 155.7 percent due to the crisis. 

European nations have spent more than 1.8 trillion euros ($1.99 trillion) on tackling the pandemic. But the economy is expected to contract by 7.5 percent, according to the International Monetary Fund. The EU has now agreed to a one trillion-euro ($1.11 trillion) recovery fund to help nations. 

Lorenzo Codogno, chief economist at Macro Advisors, comments on the deal and Michael Reid, senior editor at the Economist, shares his thoughts with Al Jazeera. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #CountingTheCost #FoodCrisis</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="44" average="4.64" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="352"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:X9zuJi5v2Kc</id>
  <yt:videoId>X9zuJi5v2Kc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Burkina Faso comedians combat COVID-19 anxiety with humour</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X9zuJi5v2Kc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T10:55:36+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T10:58:43+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Burkina Faso comedians combat COVID-19 anxiety with humour</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/X9zuJi5v2Kc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/X9zuJi5v2Kc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Young people in Burkina Faso are turning to comedy to deal with mounting uncertainty.  
With the country already struggling from years of violence, comedians are now using humour to address serious health issues like the global pandemic.

Al Jazeera’s Nicolas Haque reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#BurkinaFaso  #COVID19  #Cpronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="32" average="4.75" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1174"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:YGkBslPsOZ8</id>
  <yt:videoId>YGkBslPsOZ8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>US FDA allows emergency use of remdesivir drug for coronavirus</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YGkBslPsOZ8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T09:00:36+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T09:00:37+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>US FDA allows emergency use of remdesivir drug for coronavirus</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/YGkBslPsOZ8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/YGkBslPsOZ8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>An experimental antiviral drug has been approved for emergency use in treating coronavirus patients in the US.
1.5 million vials of the drug Remdesivir will be distributed to hospitals from Monday, after a study showed it could shorten recovery time.

Al Jazeera’s Patty Culhane reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#COVID19  #Remdesivir #Gilead</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="58" average="4.86" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2922"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:MlNRNsYU0IE</id>
  <yt:videoId>MlNRNsYU0IE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>N Korea's Kim Jong Un makes first 'public appearance' in weeks</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MlNRNsYU0IE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T08:46:03+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T08:51:16+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>N Korea's Kim Jong Un makes first 'public appearance' in weeks</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/MlNRNsYU0IE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/MlNRNsYU0IE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>North Korean leader Kim Jong Un has made his first public appearance in 20 days, North Korean state media reported early on Saturday, ending an absense that sparked speculation about his health.

The Korean Central News Agency (KCNA) reported that Kim attended a ceremony marking the completion of a fertiliser factory in Suncheon, near the capital of Pyongyang, with other senior officials, including his sister, Kim Yo Jong.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #NorthKorea #KimJongUn</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="1131" average="4.77" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="62841"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:eNe0SbOhK9U</id>
  <yt:videoId>eNe0SbOhK9U</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>COVID-19 tracking apps raise privacy concerns in Asia</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eNe0SbOhK9U"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T08:26:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T08:26:06+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>COVID-19 tracking apps raise privacy concerns in Asia</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/eNe0SbOhK9U?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/eNe0SbOhK9U/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Digital technologies have proven a popular tool for governments across Asia to monitor and contain the spread of the coronavirus. 
Medical authorities say tracking software has helped slow transmission, but critics say it has highlighted the power of governments to exploit people's personal data. 

Al Jazeera’s Sarah Clarke reports from Hong Kong.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#coronavirus #COVID19 #COVID19Tracking</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="31" average="4.35" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1379"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:9LZvygiCkpo</id>
  <yt:videoId>9LZvygiCkpo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>‘It never, never happened’: Biden denies Tara Reade’s sexual allegation</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9LZvygiCkpo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T06:45:49+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T06:50:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>‘It never, never happened’: Biden denies Tara Reade’s sexual allegation</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/9LZvygiCkpo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/9LZvygiCkpo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Joe Biden, the Democratic candidate who is the most likely to take on Donald Trump in this year's US presidential election, has spoken publicly to deny an allegation of sexual assault.
The accusation was made by a woman who worked for Biden when he was a senator in the early 1990s.
The former vice president insists it never happened.

Al Jazeera’s Alan Fisher reports from the US capital, Washington, DC.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#JoeBiden  #TaraReade  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="53" average="4.32" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2345"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:JhFRhf3WMvM</id>
  <yt:videoId>JhFRhf3WMvM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Canada bans assault-style weapons after Nova Scotia mass shooting</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JhFRhf3WMvM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T05:43:25+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T05:43:26+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Canada bans assault-style weapons after Nova Scotia mass shooting</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/JhFRhf3WMvM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/JhFRhf3WMvM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Canada is banning assault-style weapons after the country's deadliest mass shooting two weeks ago.  
Twenty-two people were killed in the province of Nova Scotia, when a man, dressed as a policeman, went on a shooting spree.
The ban comes into effect immediately, but there will be a two-year amnesty for people to dispose of weapons they already own. 

Al Jazeera’s Daniel Lak reports from Toronto, Canada.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Canada #AssaultWeapons  #NovaScotiaShootings</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="126" average="4.49" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3730"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:O3knOR36G7E</id>
  <yt:videoId>O3knOR36G7E</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>UK: Black Africans dying at much higher rate than white Britons</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O3knOR36G7E"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-02T04:43:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-02T04:43:43+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>UK: Black Africans dying at much higher rate than white Britons</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/O3knOR36G7E?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/O3knOR36G7E/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Statistics are emerging in the UK, showing the COVID-19 death rate is higher among ethnic minorities.
There have been similar disparities in the US.
The government has promised to increase testing, tracking and tracing, as it looks to lifting its lockdown soon.

Al Jazeera’s Nadim Baba reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#EuropeCoronavirus  #UKcoronavirus  #COVID19</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="74" average="4.03" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="5153"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:DzJBFcsYSZo</id>
  <yt:videoId>DzJBFcsYSZo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Italians concerned over COVID-19 economic impact</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DzJBFcsYSZo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-01T19:26:28+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-01T19:43:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Italians concerned over COVID-19 economic impact</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/DzJBFcsYSZo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/DzJBFcsYSZo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Italian prime minister has apologised for the economic hardships endured by his people during the coronavirus pandemic.
The government is easing what has been Europe's longest lockdown on Monday.
Italy has had the second-highest number of deaths worldwide.
But there are concerns the road to recovery may be much longer and harder.

Al Jazeera's Priyanka Gupta explains.   

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Italy #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="176" average="4.82" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="22417"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
