<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:PruJ_1BVZjI</id>
  <yt:videoId>PruJ_1BVZjI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Indonesia: Jakarta is reopening after weeks of lockdown</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PruJ_1BVZjI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T19:48:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T19:59:42+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Indonesia: Jakarta is reopening after weeks of lockdown</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/PruJ_1BVZjI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PruJ_1BVZjI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Traffic jams are on the way back in Indonesia's capital as Jakarta starts reopening after weeks of lockdown.
But healthcare workers worry the relaxation of restrictions is too soon for Southeast Asia's largest city. 
Al Jazeera's Jessica Washington reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Indonesia #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="58" average="4.86" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2351"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:mars9RD_rww</id>
  <yt:videoId>mars9RD_rww</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>As India reopens, one state outnumbers China in coronavirus cases</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mars9RD_rww"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T19:45:29+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T19:52:34+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>As India reopens, one state outnumbers China in coronavirus cases</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/mars9RD_rww?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mars9RD_rww/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The number of reported cases of coronavirus worldwide has topped seven million. 
In India, malls, restaurants and places of worship have re-opened despite a surge in new infections. 
There are more than a quarter of a million cases and over 7,000 people are reported to have died. 
Al Jazeera's Elizabeth Puranam reports from New Delhi.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #India #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="45" average="3.84" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1199"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:qio0BvKDMUM</id>
  <yt:videoId>qio0BvKDMUM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>How can you be an ally to the Black Lives Matter movement? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qio0BvKDMUM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T19:25:31+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T19:34:48+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>How can you be an ally to the Black Lives Matter movement? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/qio0BvKDMUM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/qio0BvKDMUM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Mass protests in the US over the killing by police of another unarmed black man, George Floyd, have been swelled by the presence of people of all races in numbers not seen before.
 
But whether it’s on the streets or online, what does true allyship look like?
 
“You're walking down the street and you see a child and a big dog charging towards it. Do you let the dog eat the child or save the child?&quot; writer and activist Feminista Jones told The Stream. &quot;If you observe something, and you know something is going to happen, do you do everything you can to stop it, or do you think of self-preservation?&quot; 
 
Activists say it’s vital that being an ally is an ongoing process of both education and action. Manuals on allyship are circulating on social media to help people take steps in that direction.
 
Some of the suggestions are: educating yourself, researching, listening and not talking. Showing up at protests, observing and protecting people who are more vulnerable to police action. Donating to organisations on the frontline, centering and amplifying the voices of Black people. 
 
In this episode of The Stream we'll take a closer look at those ideas and ask how they can bring about substantive change.

TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream 
Subscribe to our channel:  http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#BlackLivesMatter
#Aljazeeraenglish
#News</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="59" average="2.69" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="0"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:8qZoSXc4myY</id>
  <yt:videoId>8qZoSXc4myY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Why is the US pulling out troops from Germany? I Inside Story</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8qZoSXc4myY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T17:30:00+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T17:30:00+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Why is the US pulling out troops from Germany? I Inside Story</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/8qZoSXc4myY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/8qZoSXc4myY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>They are a legacy of World War Two - a symbol of U.S. commitment to protecting its European allies.
But U.S. military forces stationed in Germany are reportedly going to be sharply reduced.
President Donald Trump plans to pull out 9,500 American soldiers by September - reducing the number to 25,000.
Troops will either be redeployed elsewhere or sent home. 
It's being seen as the latest twist in relations between Washington and Berlin.
Tensions between the two sides have been strained over a number of disagreements. 
But defence spending has been of particular concern for Donald Trump.
He's repeatedly pressed Germany to increase its military budget.
And he's criticised NATO allies for relying on the U.S. to shoulder the costs of maintaining the alliance.
But why is this move coming now?
And should U.S. allies and NATO be concerned?

Presenter: Laura Brennan

Guests
Andrew Bacevich,  U.S. military historian and Professor Emeritus of International Relations and History at Boston University.
Ulrich Brueckner  political analyst and Professor in European Studies at Stanford University Berlin 
Pavel Felgenhauer, defence analyst.


- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Germany #US #InsideStory</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="355" average="4.71" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="26832"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:VcL-HjT0GBc</id>
  <yt:videoId>VcL-HjT0GBc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>How is Kashmir coping with back-to-back lockdowns? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VcL-HjT0GBc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T15:50:23+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T22:08:08+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>How is Kashmir coping with back-to-back lockdowns? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/VcL-HjT0GBc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/VcL-HjT0GBc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Several states in India are tentatively relaxing coronavirus lockdowns that for weeks have kept people’s movements to a minimum. But millions of people in Indian-administered Kashmir are still enduring two parallel sets of restrictions – one based on security, the other on public health.

Measures to limit the spread of coronavirus were rolled out across the two Muslim-majority territories of Jammu and Kashmir and Ladakh in late March. That was just as the region was emerging from some aspects of a security lockdown that accompanied the central government’s revocation of Kashmir’s semi-autonomy last year.

Residents already weary from the day-to-day presence of troops and police on the streets and the longest internet blackout ever seen in a democracy are now struggling to contact loved ones over slow 2G mobile internet as the threat of coronavirus looms large. Doctors across Jammu and Kashmir say their ability to effectively control and treat COVID-19 is being seriously hampered by the internet restrictions. 

India's Bharatiya Janata Party-led central government maintains the robust security posture in newly-absorbed Jammu and Kashmir will eventually overcome Kashmiri separatism in the region and build a &quot;New India&quot;. But amid a recent surge in violence touching the main city of Srinagar, as well as simmering anger over a domicile law that clears the way for outsiders to settle in Jammu and Kashmir, millions of people remain on edge.

We'll look at how people in Indian-administered Kashmir are coping with life under two very different sets of restrictions. Join the conversation.

TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream 
Subscribe to our channel http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#Kashmir
#coronavirus
#India
#Aljazeeraenglish
#News</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="704" average="4.38" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="15181"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:zOaMRopo3Oc</id>
  <yt:videoId>zOaMRopo3Oc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>US: Controversy over statues of Confederate leaders</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zOaMRopo3Oc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T11:56:36+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T12:05:21+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>US: Controversy over statues of Confederate leaders</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/zOaMRopo3Oc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/zOaMRopo3Oc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Statues built after the American Civil War to honour leaders who fought to defend slavery have often been a flashpoint, as they are now in cities such as Richmond in the US state of Virginia.
 
Richmond was the capital of the Confederacy - the 11 pro-slavery southern states which lost their bid to break away when they were defeated in the US Civil War.
 
Protesters in Richmond last week set fire to the home of the &quot;Daughters of the Confederacy&quot;, who are dedicated to preserving Confederate monuments.
 
The statue of Confederate General William Wickham was pulled down on Saturday, something his own descendants had called for years ago.
 
And Virginia's governor announced plans to remove the statue of Confederate General Robert E Lee.
 

Maurice Jackson, associate professor of African American Studies at Georgetown University, talks to Al Jazeera.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #BlackLivesMatter</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="235" average="4.73" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="16385"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:q43Axnr7QAQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>q43Axnr7QAQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>South African schools reopen as COVID-19 lockdown is eased</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q43Axnr7QAQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T11:54:44+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T11:55:34+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>South African schools reopen as COVID-19 lockdown is eased</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/q43Axnr7QAQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/q43Axnr7QAQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Most schools in South Africa have reopened.
The students in their final years of primary and secondary school have been allowed to return.
Al Jazeera's Fahmida Miller spent the morning at one school in Johannesburg. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #SouthAfrica #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="50" average="4.76" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4305"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:bUv46G-2W78</id>
  <yt:videoId>bUv46G-2W78</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Caught on camera: Police brutality and racism in Trump's America | The Listening Post (Full)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bUv46G-2W78"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T11:29:28+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T12:55:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Caught on camera: Police brutality and racism in Trump's America | The Listening Post (Full)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/bUv46G-2W78?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/bUv46G-2W78/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>On The Listening Post this week: How the video of a Black man's murder set the United States ablaze. Plus, drone investigations from on high.

Caught on camera: Police brutality and racism in Trump's America

Racially charged social unrest has been sweeping America on a scale not seen in decades. Showdowns are taking place in city after city between demonstrators and police, as authoritarian noises and tactics come from the Trump White House. From the phone camera that captured the police killing of George Floyd, to Twitter flagging how dangerous the president's tweets can be, to all those videos showing police attacking journalists and then finally to the lengths that the White House will go to to get a photo opportunity - there is no shortage of media angles to this story.

Contributors:

Siva Vaidhyanathan - Author, Antisocial Media: How Facebook Disconnects Us and Undermines Democracy

Meredith Clark - Assistant Professor in Media Studies, University of Virginia

Tiffany Cross - Author, Say It Louder! Black Voters, White Narratives and Saving Our Democracy

Mary Frances Berry - Professor of American Social Thought, University of Pennsylvania

On our radar:

Richard Gizbert speaks to producer Meenakshi Ravi about how the demonstrations in the US have delivered the perfect opportunity for some international media - for example, state-run outlets in Iran and China - to take pot shots at America.

Eyes in the sky: Gathering evidence with drones

Sometimes capturing an image or a single video can have a transformative effect. Anyone contending with state violence, whether they are in Minneapolis, Hong Kong or the Middle East, knows that sometimes all they need to make their case - to expose illegality - is the right picture. But there are some places that satellites and phones cannot go. That is where drones come in. Television journalists love drone images for the perspective and scope they provide. Advertisers use them for their cinematic quality and effect on consumers. But drones are also being used to provide irrefutable, photographic evidence of human rights abuses and illegality. The Listening Post's Tariq Nafi looks at drones and how they are being used in investigations across the world.

Feature contributors:

Josh Lyons - Director of Geospatial Analysis, Human Rights Watch

Juan Bergelund - CEO, UAV del Peru and Country Manager, Peru Flying Labs

Kelly Matheson - Human rights attorney and Director, Video as Evidence programme, Witness

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="169" average="4.48" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="8297"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Ugdc1fpoudQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>Ugdc1fpoudQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Pakistan COVID-19 infections pass 100,000</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ugdc1fpoudQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T10:21:00+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T10:28:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Pakistan COVID-19 infections pass 100,000</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Ugdc1fpoudQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Ugdc1fpoudQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The number of coronavirus cases in Pakistan has passed 100,000. 
Infections jumped after the Islamic holy month of Ramadan ended and markets reopened. 
Doctors and other health professionals wanted tougher lockdown measures, including the closure of mosques.
But the government rejected them.
More than 2,000 people in Pakistan have died from COVID-19 since the outbreak began.

Al Jazeera’s Kamal Hyder joins us live from Islamabad.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Pakistan  #covid19  #PakistanCoronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="86" average="4.40" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="5284"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:QxYaKJT3q4s</id>
  <yt:videoId>QxYaKJT3q4s</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Nazi submarine base in France repurposed for art space</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QxYaKJT3q4s"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T08:54:29+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T08:54:30+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Nazi submarine base in France repurposed for art space</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/QxYaKJT3q4s?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/QxYaKJT3q4s/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>An abandoned submarine base in France has been given a new lease on life.
The docks, built by the Nazis during WWII, is now projecting a different kind of message.

Al Jazeera’s Charlotte Bellis reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#France  #BassinsDeLumieres  #CultureSpaces</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="64" average="4.81" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3825"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:SK1gUVbsj6g</id>
  <yt:videoId>SK1gUVbsj6g</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Project in Russia spreads passion for books amid lockdown</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SK1gUVbsj6g"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T07:15:34+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T07:15:36+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Project in Russia spreads passion for books amid lockdown</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/SK1gUVbsj6g?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/SK1gUVbsj6g/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Lockdowns in Russia are hitting book publishers hard.
Shops are shut and publishing houses are facing bankruptcy.
But some young children are getting around the coronavirus lockdown restrictions thanks to a project aimed at spreading the love of reading books.

Al Jazeera's Priyanka Gupta reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Russia  #RussiaLockdown  #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="46" average="4.74" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2001"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Kap1UN7a5zg</id>
  <yt:videoId>Kap1UN7a5zg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Brazil: Rival rallies held for and against Bolsonaro</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kap1UN7a5zg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T06:18:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T06:18:06+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Brazil: Rival rallies held for and against Bolsonaro</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Kap1UN7a5zg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/Kap1UN7a5zg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Thousands of people in Brazil have defied a lockdown to demonstrate against what they see as threats to democracy and health under President Jair Bolsonaro.
He has described the protesters as 'terrorists” and says he will continue pushing to arm ordinary Brazilians to defend the country.
In Rio de Janeiro, a group of Bolsonaro supporters ridiculed his opponents calling them “the antifas”, or antifascists.
President Jair Bolsonaro has played down the dangers of the disease throughout the outbreak.

Al Jazeera’s Lucia Newman reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Brazil  #BrazilProtests  #Bolsonaro</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="255" average="4.29" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="15220"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:GtnVpNLQoek</id>
  <yt:videoId>GtnVpNLQoek</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>NYC mayor vows to shift funding from NYPD to youth initiatives</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GtnVpNLQoek"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T05:46:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T05:46:21+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>NYC mayor vows to shift funding from NYPD to youth initiatives</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/GtnVpNLQoek?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/GtnVpNLQoek/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio is making moves to change the city's police department, after more than a week of protests.
The measures include shifting part of the NYPD budget to youth and social work, and better transparency for officer's disciplinary files.

Al Jazeera’s Patty Culhane reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#GeorgeFloydProtests  #NYPD  #BillDeBlasio</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="263" average="4.59" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="15348"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:9ZPRuMa1_Gw</id>
  <yt:videoId>9ZPRuMa1_Gw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Anti-racism protests held across Europe</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9ZPRuMa1_Gw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-07T18:58:52+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-07T19:05:01+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Anti-racism protests held across Europe</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/9ZPRuMa1_Gw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/9ZPRuMa1_Gw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Solidarity protests against racism have been held across Europe - including London.
For the second day in a row, thousands of people gathered outside the US embassy.
They are demanding an end to systemic racism and police brutality.
Al Jazeera's Nadim Baba reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #BlackLivesMatter #Europe</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="433" average="4.54" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="25148"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
