<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:IN5hqsFQRpc</id>
  <yt:videoId>IN5hqsFQRpc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Canada election: Has Trudeau's gamble backfired? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IN5hqsFQRpc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T20:01:08+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T20:29:44+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Canada election: Has Trudeau's gamble backfired? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/IN5hqsFQRpc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/IN5hqsFQRpc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The pressure is on for Prime Minister Justin Trudeau as Canada prepares for upcoming federal elections. Enjoying high public approval for his pandemic control measures, Trudeau called for a snap election two years ahead of schedule.

But the move appears to have backfired, causing his popularity to plummet in the polls and the opposition Conservative Party to make gains. The results of the election will come at a critical time for Canada, with the economy, climate change and COVID-19 at the top of voters' minds. 

For some Canadians, whether candidates follow through with pledges to honor Indigenous reconciliation is also top of mind. This comes after the discovery of hundreds of Indigenous children’s bodies in unmarked graves at former residential school sites in Canada this year.

In this episode of The Stream we ask, will Trudeau survive Canada's upcoming snap election?

Join the conversation: 
TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream 
Subscribe to our channel http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#aljazeeraenglish
#ajstream
#canada</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="327" average="4.66" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="10099"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:iIoBWoNWWFk</id>
  <yt:videoId>iIoBWoNWWFk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Afghanistan: Taliban’s Mullah Baradar denies rumours of his death</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iIoBWoNWWFk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T18:58:49+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T19:01:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Afghanistan: Taliban’s Mullah Baradar denies rumours of his death</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/iIoBWoNWWFk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/iIoBWoNWWFk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Afghanistan's acting Deputy Prime Minister Mullah Abdul Ghani Baradar has appeared in a video to deny rumours of his death.&#13;
Speculation had been swirling that Baradar was caught up in a violent confrontation between rival Taliban factions after the formation of the interim government.&#13;
Despite Baradar's appearance and Taliban denials, many Afghans still worry that a prolonged leadership crisis could create more poverty and uncertainty.&#13;
&#13;
Al Jazeera’s Hashem Ahelbarra reports from Kabul, Afghanistan.&#13;
 &#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#Afghanistan #Taliban #MullahBaradar</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="787" average="4.77" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="36139"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:04OCyZfljbc</id>
  <yt:videoId>04OCyZfljbc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Court rules against officials in landmark Jakarta pollution case</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=04OCyZfljbc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T17:51:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T17:59:27+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Court rules against officials in landmark Jakarta pollution case</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/04OCyZfljbc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/04OCyZfljbc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A group of Jakarta residents has won a legal battle for clean air.&#13;
A court in Indonesia has found the president and top government officials negligent for failing to establish proper standards to curb pollution.&#13;
The &quot;citizen's lawsuit&quot; was filed two years ago, against seven politicians - including Jakarta's governor, Anies Baswedan.&#13;
The court said President Joko Widodo, should strengthen Indonesia's air quality standards.&#13;
It is a problem Widodo has raised before, in 2019, when he admitted pollution around Jakarta was out of control.&#13;
&#13;
Al Jazeera’s Katia Lopez-Hodayan reports.&#13;
&#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish/&#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera/&#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#Indonesia #IndonesiaAirPollution #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="65" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2011"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:VdR1ZarFT5s</id>
  <yt:videoId>VdR1ZarFT5s</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Can the European Union defend itself? | Inside Story</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VdR1ZarFT5s"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T17:30:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T17:38:15+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Can the European Union defend itself? | Inside Story</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/VdR1ZarFT5s?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/VdR1ZarFT5s/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Many European leaders have long pushed for a bigger military role. &#13;
One that is independent of the US-led NATO alliance.&#13;
The need for this increased military capability was recently made clear, during the chaotic evacuations from Kabul airport. &#13;
European nations had to rely almost entirely on the United States. &#13;
European Commission president Ursula Von Der Leyen says the bloc needs the political will to stand on its own. &#13;
She says the EU should be able to deploy a military force without relying on the US or NATO.  &#13;
But what is holding it back from achieving this goal?&#13;
&#13;
Presenter: Nastasya Tay&#13;
&#13;
Guests:&#13;
Theresa Fallon - Director of Centre for Russia Europe Asia Studies. &#13;
David DesRoches - Associate Professor at National Defense University.&#13;
Nicholas Whyte - International Affairs Strategist.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#EUmilitaryforce #NATO  #InsideStory</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="151" average="4.58" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7353"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:2-AwVw7DRwU</id>
  <yt:videoId>2-AwVw7DRwU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Hezbollah-brokered Iranian fuel arrives in crisis-hit Lebanon</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-AwVw7DRwU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T16:21:15+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T16:21:30+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Hezbollah-brokered Iranian fuel arrives in crisis-hit Lebanon</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/2-AwVw7DRwU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/2-AwVw7DRwU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Much needed fuel has arrived in Lebanon to ease the country's crippling shortages.&#13;
The first of several truck convoys carrying Iranian fuel from Syria was arranged by the Iran-backed Hezbollah party.&#13;
Importing fuel from Iran risks US action under the current sanctions.&#13;
That is why the Iranian backed Lebanese armed group says it chose to offload at a port in Syria and bring the supplies through illegal crossings - so Lebanon will not have to deal with sanctions-related complications.&#13;
The Biden administration, which considers Hezbollah a terrorist organisation, has chosen not to respond. Some say it is because of efforts to restart negotiations with Iran on a nuclear deal.&#13;
&#13;
Al Jazeera’s Zeina Khodr reports from Beirut, Lebanon.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#LebanonFuelShortages #Hezbollah #LebanonEconomicCrisis</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="493" average="4.66" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="24971"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:_gSOGp3COfI</id>
  <yt:videoId>_gSOGp3COfI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Australia: Asylum-seeking Tamil family legal battle continue</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_gSOGp3COfI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T15:15:56+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T15:15:56+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Australia: Asylum-seeking Tamil family legal battle continue</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/_gSOGp3COfI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/_gSOGp3COfI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A Tamil family’s bid to seek asylum in Australia has been given a temporary reprieve after the country's immigration minister granted them a three-month extension to stay while he considers their case.&#13;
The Murugappan family fled to Australia in the early 2010s and have been seeking asylum there ever since.&#13;
Supporters of the Murugappan family are pleading with the Australian government, warning the family could be tortured if they are deported to Sri Lanka.&#13;
&#13;
Al Jazeera’s Sarah Clarke reports from Brisbane, Australia&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#AustraliaAsylumSeekers #Muruguppan #HomeToBilo</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="66" average="4.21" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3370"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:4QjxZB1hQ7w</id>
  <yt:videoId>4QjxZB1hQ7w</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Hong Kong: Candle in the Wind | 101 East</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4QjxZB1hQ7w"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T14:19:15+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T14:19:15+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Hong Kong: Candle in the Wind | 101 East</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/4QjxZB1hQ7w?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/4QjxZB1hQ7w/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>In Hong Kong, dissent has become a dangerous business. Activists have been jailed and many opposition politicians have been imprisoned and are facing criminal charges.

As the political crackdown intensifies, 101 East follows three Hong Kongers who refuse to be silenced, despite the risks.

Hong Kong Chief Secretary for Administration John Lee Ka-chiu declined 101 East's invitation to appear in this film, but did offer the following statement:

&quot;Hong Kong residents enjoy the freedoms of assembly, of procession and of demonstration as well as other rights and freedoms protected under the Basic Law. However, such rights and freedoms are not absolute and may be subject to restrictions as prescribed by law and in the interests of, amongst others, national security, public order (ordre public) and the protection of the rights and freedoms of others.

In this regard, it should be pointed out that safeguarding national sovereignty, security and development interests is an indisputable duty of a responsible national in all countries and places around the world. The Government of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region (HKSAR) is no exception. The Hong Kong National Security Law (NSL) aims to prevent, suppress and punish acts and activities endangering national security. That notwithstanding, the NSL upholds human rights in safeguarding national security in the HKSAR, clearly stipulating that the rights and freedoms enjoyed by residents under the Basic Law and the provisions of the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights and the International Covenant on Economic, Social and Cultural Rights as applied to Hong Kong, shall be protected in accordance with the law. Freedoms of speech and of publication are among the rights and freedoms explicitly mentioned in Article 4 of the NSL.

Public health is the paramount consideration for epidemic control in Hong Kong. The COVID-19 pandemic remains severe and the number of cases including mutant strains around the world is rising continuously. We should not let our guard down. It is essential for us to take all necessary measures to strengthen epidemic control by guarding against the importation of cases and the resurgence of domestic infections. As such, there is a need for the Government to prevent the spread of COVID-19 in the community through the continued implementation of various social distancing measures. To protect public health, we do not recommend the organisation of mass gatherings involving a large number of people with prolonged duration of contact, and where there would be difficulty in controlling the crowd size and ensuring adequate social distancing among participants. The effectiveness of this approach can be seen in the fact that Hong Kong has not had to implement prolonged city-wide lockdowns seen elsewhere, and that we have not had any local transmission cases for more than a month. To suggest that other reasons are behind this anti-epidemic policy during a global health crisis does not stand up to any scrutiny.

The Police have been handling and will continue to handle notifications for public meetings and public processions in accordance with the law.&quot;

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="89" average="4.24" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2905"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:OEof45XvLBs</id>
  <yt:videoId>OEof45XvLBs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Philippines say Duterte will not cooperate with ICC drug war probe</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OEof45XvLBs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T13:24:39+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T13:24:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Philippines say Duterte will not cooperate with ICC drug war probe</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/OEof45XvLBs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/OEof45XvLBs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Philippine government says it will not cooperate with an investigation by the International Criminal Court into its so-called “war on drugs”. &#13;
The ICC approved an inquiry into alleged crimes against humanity in President Rodrigo Duterte's campaign on Wednesday.&#13;
The Hague-based tribunal said there was “reasonable basis” to proceed, noting that “specific legal element of the crime against humanity of murder” has been met in the crackdown that left thousands dead.&#13;
&#13;
Al Jazeera’s Jamela Alindogan reports from Manila, the Philippines.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#Philippines  #Duterte  #PhilippinesWarOnDrugs</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="144" average="4.25" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="5761"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:3rcyaOXQxvM</id>
  <yt:videoId>3rcyaOXQxvM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Biden announces a new security agreement with the UK and Australia</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3rcyaOXQxvM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T11:04:33+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T11:10:59+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Biden announces a new security agreement with the UK and Australia</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/3rcyaOXQxvM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/3rcyaOXQxvM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Australia, the United States and the United Kingdom have announced a new trilateral security alliance, including a joint effort to help the Australian military acquire nuclear-powered submarines, in an apparent attempt to counter China.&#13;
&#13;
Adam Leong from the National defence University of Malaysia. He joins us live from Kuala Lumpur to discuss this.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#AlJazeeraEnglish #UnitedStates #UnitedKingdom #Australia</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="169" average="4.38" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="8512"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:VpJtjkxsIGQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>VpJtjkxsIGQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>France says leader of ISIL group in Sahel has been killed</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VpJtjkxsIGQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T09:21:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T09:21:43+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>France says leader of ISIL group in Sahel has been killed</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/VpJtjkxsIGQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/VpJtjkxsIGQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>France says that the leader of ISIL (ISIS)-affiliated Islamic State in Greater Sahara (ISGS) group, known for its deadly attacks in the so-called tri-border region of Mali, Niger and Burkina Faso, has been killed by French forces.

“[Adnan Abu Walid al-Sahrawi], leader of the terrorist group Islamic State in the Greater Sahara was neutralised by French forces,” French President Emmanuel Macron said in a tweet on Thursday.
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#AlJazeeraEnglish #France #ISILleader</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="326" average="4.64" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="19128"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:eHpGOyiRE8I</id>
  <yt:videoId>eHpGOyiRE8I</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Mexico: Hundreds of migrants protest in southern city of Tapachula</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eHpGOyiRE8I"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T06:22:21+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T06:27:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Mexico: Hundreds of migrants protest in southern city of Tapachula</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/eHpGOyiRE8I?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/eHpGOyiRE8I/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Tens of thousands of migrants hoping to reach the US remain stuck in southern Mexico.&#13;
They are mainly from Haiti and Central America but cannot leave the border town of Tapachula due to a Mexican government policy.&#13;
Despite the blockade more migrants continue to arrive every day making the crowded shelters unlivable&#13;
Al Jazeera's Manuel Rapalo reports from Tapachula, Mexico.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#AlJazeeraEnglish #Mexico #Migration</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="126" average="3.73" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="5587"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:xodJMY_jdwY</id>
  <yt:videoId>xodJMY_jdwY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Simone Biles blasts USA Gymnastics, FBI for allowing sex abuse</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xodJMY_jdwY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T05:30:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T05:37:24+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Simone Biles blasts USA Gymnastics, FBI for allowing sex abuse</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/xodJMY_jdwY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xodJMY_jdwY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>US Olympic gymnast Simone Biles and her fellow athletes have accused the FBI and USA Gymnastics of turning a blind eye to sexual abuse they suffered at the hands of former team doctor, Larry Nassar.&#13;
Four athletes gave emotional testimony to a US Senate Judiciary Committee.&#13;
The Committee is looking into the agency's mishandling of the case which involves hundreds of gymnasts, the largest sexual abuse incident in US sports history.&#13;
McKayla Maroney said the FBI had not only not reported her abuse but falsified details when she told them about it.&#13;
Al Jazeera's Shihab Rattansi reports from Capitol Hill, Washington, DC, the United States.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#AlJazeeraEnglish #LarryNassar #SexualAbuse</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="224" average="4.77" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="9794"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:7qHmJG5r4YI</id>
  <yt:videoId>7qHmJG5r4YI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>US, UK and Australia agree to new Indo-Pacific security pact</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7qHmJG5r4YI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T04:55:25+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T05:00:13+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>US, UK and Australia agree to new Indo-Pacific security pact</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/7qHmJG5r4YI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7qHmJG5r4YI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The UK and US have agreed to help Australia develop nuclear-powered submarines under a new partnership they are calling the 'Indo-Pacific Security Alliance'.&#13;
Dubbed AUKUS, the agreement is seen as a way to counter China's influence in the region.&#13;
The leaders of all three nations said that the submarines would be nuclear powered but insisted that they would not carry any nuclear weapons.&#13;
Al Jazeera's Mike Hanna reports from Washington, DC, the US.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#AlJazeeraEnglish #UnitedStates #UnitedKingdom #Australia</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="343" average="4.27" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="15328"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Bh6K1KylFgo</id>
  <yt:videoId>Bh6K1KylFgo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>First all-civilian space crew blasts off on SpaceX rocket</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bh6K1KylFgo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T04:48:25+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-16T04:49:32+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>First all-civilian space crew blasts off on SpaceX rocket</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Bh6K1KylFgo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/Bh6K1KylFgo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>For the first time in 60 years of human spaceflight, no professional astronaut is aboard an orbit-bound rocket.&#13;
Four civilians have made history, after taking off on a fully-automated SpaceX mission without any professional space crew.&#13;
The 'Inspiration4' mission blasted off from Cape Canaveral, Florida, a few minutes after 8pm local time on Wednesday (00:00 GMT Thursday).&#13;
Al Jazeera's Rob Reynolds reports.&#13;
&#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#AlJazeeraEnglish #SpaceX #CivilianSpaceCrew</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="288" average="4.72" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="15017"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:RPSlo1FdL-Q</id>
  <yt:videoId>RPSlo1FdL-Q</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Kosovo war crimes suspect slams ‘Gestapo’ court as trial opens</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RPSlo1FdL-Q"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-15T22:30:49+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-15T22:35:13+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Kosovo war crimes suspect slams ‘Gestapo’ court as trial opens</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/RPSlo1FdL-Q?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RPSlo1FdL-Q/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A former Kosovar military commander is in court to face war crimes charges.&#13;
Salih Mustafa is accused of the murder, torture, cruel treatment and arbitrary detention of civilians during the 1990s conflict with Serbia.&#13;
It is the first trial to be heard in the Kosovo Special Chambers - an EU-backed court established in the Netherlands in 2015.&#13;
“I am not guilty of any of the counts brought here before me by this Gestapo office,” Mustafa, 49, said as his trial started, comparing the war crimes court to Nazi Germany’s secret police.&#13;
Al Jazeera’s Nadim Baba reports.&#13;
 &#13;
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe &#13;
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish &#13;
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera &#13;
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/&#13;
&#13;
#Kosovo  #SalihMustafa  #KosovoWarCrimes</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="134" average="4.40" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7795"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
