<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:KDDiepEWZKE</id>
  <yt:videoId>KDDiepEWZKE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Does Brazil's Bolsonaro care about coronavirus? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KDDiepEWZKE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-29T20:02:04+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-01T20:34:59+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Does Brazil's Bolsonaro care about coronavirus? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/KDDiepEWZKE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/KDDiepEWZKE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>When Brazil's President Jair Bolsonaro was asked this week to respond to the fact his country had hit a record number of COVID-19 deaths in 24 hours, his response took even some supporters by surprise. &quot;So what?&quot; he replied, unleashing a deluge of criticism.

Latin America’s largest country faces a growing health emergency as it contends with the twin challenges of coronavirus and political turmoil.

More than 90,000 people in Brazil are confirmed to be infected with COVID-19, but health authorities estimate the actual number to be at least 10 times higher. 

Though millions are now at risk, Bolsonaro has repeatedly downplayed the seriousness of the situation, referring to the pandemic as a “measly cold.”

But as hospitals become overwhelmed with patients and mass graves proliferate, Bolsonaro is rapidly losing political clout. And the high-profile departures of his popular health and justice ministers in recent weeks have left him vulnerable to impeachment inquiries.

In the absence of federal leadership, local governors have attempted to enforce social distancing measures. But in poorer neighborhoods, this has been impossible.

In this episode we ask, does Brazil's Bolsonaro care about coronavirus?

Join the conversation: 
TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream 
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream 
Subscribe to our channel http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#coronavirus
#ajstream
#aljazeeraenglish
#brazil</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="110" average="4.78" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="972"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:CkOURd1vUC8</id>
  <yt:videoId>CkOURd1vUC8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Iran forces accused of drowning Afghans amid pandemic</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CkOURd1vUC8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T14:59:40+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T14:59:59+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Iran forces accused of drowning Afghans amid pandemic</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/CkOURd1vUC8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/CkOURd1vUC8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The coronavirus pandemic has caused tens of thousands of Afghans to cross the border from Iran, the region's worst hit country.
But some have also been trying to go in the other direction, looking for work. 
Now, Afghanistan is accusing Iranian border forces of drowning dozens of Afghan migrants, to stop them from crossing over. 
It is thought at least 38 people died. Iran has denied the allegations.
Al Jazeera's Alexi O'Brien has more.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Iran #Afghanistan #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="12" average="4.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="128"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:mreS6Er7qG8</id>
  <yt:videoId>mreS6Er7qG8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rights group says Malaysia risks health of detained migrants</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mreS6Er7qG8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T14:21:59+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T14:27:02+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rights group says Malaysia risks health of detained migrants</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/mreS6Er7qG8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mreS6Er7qG8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Police in Malaysia have detained more than 700 refugees and migrant workers. 
They live in areas where COVID-19 cases surged last month, triggering accusations that foreigners are spreading the virus. 
Rights groups say they could be held for months in dangerously cramped conditions, and that detaining the migrants in close quarters will only increase the virus. 
Phil Robertson is the Deputy Asia Director at Human Rights Watch.
He says Malaysian authorities are risking the health of the people they have arrested.
 
- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Malaysia #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="8" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="122"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:awCo-oYpeJM</id>
  <yt:videoId>awCo-oYpeJM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Where are we with a coronavirus vaccine? | Start Here</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=awCo-oYpeJM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T13:00:01+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T13:00:02+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Where are we with a coronavirus vaccine? | Start Here</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/awCo-oYpeJM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/awCo-oYpeJM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>As government lockdowns focus on limiting the spread of the coronavirus, scientists around the world are working on treating and protecting us.
They have their work cut out. Vaccine and drug development is laborious, full of experimentation and repeated testing. Knowing how the virus works is key.  
But what other challenges do they face? And how long will it take before we can defeat this virus with a pill or an injection?
Start Here explains.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #StartHere #CoronavirusVaccine</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="496" average="4.55" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3465"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vevDNjUjTwI</id>
  <yt:videoId>vevDNjUjTwI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sudanese struggle with inflation, lockdown during Ramadan</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vevDNjUjTwI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T12:26:36+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T12:35:31+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sudanese struggle with inflation, lockdown during Ramadan</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vevDNjUjTwI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vevDNjUjTwI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Nearly eight million people in Sudan’s capital, Khartoum, are marking the fasting month of Ramadan under a lockdown imposed to try and curb the spread of the novel coronavirus.  
But with the country facing an economic crisis as well, stocking up for the month has been hard for many - especially for families who rely on a day-to-day income.

Al Jazeera's Hiba Morgan reports from Khartoum.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Sudan #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="27" average="4.70" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="259"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:WL7Y-xI7nZU</id>
  <yt:videoId>WL7Y-xI7nZU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Home delivery network fuels China economy amid lockdown</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WL7Y-xI7nZU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T12:25:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T12:27:51+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Home delivery network fuels China economy amid lockdown</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/WL7Y-xI7nZU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/WL7Y-xI7nZU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Tens of millions of people in China were confined to their homes during its strict coronavirus lockdown.
Now, although restrictions have been eased, many are afraid of venturing outside even for basic supplies. 
But thanks to China's vast home delivery network, drivers and logistics companies are helping the economy tick over while people stay indoors. 
Al Jazeera's Katrina Yu reports from Beijing, China.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #China #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="33" average="4.76" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="315"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:80ALtbLGGL0</id>
  <yt:videoId>80ALtbLGGL0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Who holds WHO accountable? | The Listening Post (Feature)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=80ALtbLGGL0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T12:14:45+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T12:14:46+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Who holds WHO accountable? | The Listening Post (Feature)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/80ALtbLGGL0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/80ALtbLGGL0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Much of the coverage of the COVID-19 pandemic treats the World Health Organization (WHO) as an authoritative, impartial source of information. But should it?

From the advent of COVID-19, the WHO's press conferences have been a fixture in global news coverage. They serve as a touchstone for journalists and, given that the WHO has 194 member states, the pressers have become a primary source of information for global context.

&quot;The WHO does shape information globally quite significantly,&quot; says Lawrence Gostin, a professor in global health law at Georgetown University who has worked closely with the WHO in the past, &quot;because it is a trusted and objective science adviser to the world&quot;.

However, the organisation's objectivity has been called into question. It started in early January when China media analysts started observing a similarity between what the WHO was saying and official statements coming out of China. For example, on January 14, the WHO tweeted: &quot;Preliminary investigations conducted by the Chinese authorities have found no clear evidence of human-to-human transmission of the novel coronavirus&quot;.

That same day, the Wuhan Health Commission's public bulletin declared, &quot;We have not found proof for human-to-human transmission.&quot; The question is, why would the WHO repeat - almost verbatim - the claims made by China when news outlets, in Hong Kong and elsewhere, were already comparing the novel coronavirus to SARS and saying that it could very well be transferred from person to person? The answer comes down to access. China only granted the WHO access to Wuhan in February 2020, nearly three months after the first case was detected.

&quot;WHO's reporting, by virtue of its governance, is highly dependent on every member country's ability, honesty and willingness to share data and issue notifications of epidemics,&quot; says Osman Dar, director of the Global Health Programme at Chatham House. &quot;Its verification systems can only be as good as the access their member states provide.&quot;

Which is the crux of the issue. Member states are not beholden to the WHO but rather the WHO is beholden to them. Not only is the organisation's access, in large part, determined by its member states, but they also make up most of the WHO's funding.

On April 15, US President Donald Trump threatened to halt his country's funding to the WHO, accusing the organisation of being China-centric. The president's critics say the threat was an attempt to deflect criticism of Trump's own mishandling of this crisis; however, his actions highlight a key vulnerability in the WHO.

The US is, by far, the organisation's biggest funder and if Washington follows through with Trump's threat, then that would severely hinder its operational capacity. Which begs the question - how can the WHO speak truth to power when those powers largely control its access and its funding?

&quot;It's not totally neutral. If you're seeing something coming from the WHO, it's something that its member states wanted to be released, it is something that a member state consented to be released,&quot; says Stephen Buranyi, a journalist at The Guardian newspaper, &quot;to see the full picture, you have to go beyond what states are telling it.&quot;

 

Produced by:

Nicholas Muirhead

Contributors:

Lawrence Gostin - Director, O'Neill Institute, Georgetown University

Osman Dar - Global Health Programme, Chatham House

Stephen Buranyi - Journalist, The Guardian

Rana Mitter - Director, China Centre, Oxford University

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="87" average="4.49" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="913"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Lgy_ovXvmLE</id>
  <yt:videoId>Lgy_ovXvmLE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Algerian Berber musician Idir dies at 70</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lgy_ovXvmLE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T11:25:37+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T11:25:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Algerian Berber musician Idir dies at 70</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Lgy_ovXvmLE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Lgy_ovXvmLE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>One of the most well-known figures of Indigenous Berber music has died.
Born Hamid Cheriet in 1949 in Ath Yenni, a Berber-speaking region in the central Atlas Mountains of Algeria, his musical prowess began to be recognised by his colleagues in a gas and oil field where he worked.
The Algerian musician, known by his stage name Idir, used his songs to address social and political injustices. He was 70 years old when he died.
 
Al Jazeera’s Laura Burdon-Manley takes a look at his life and career.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Idir  #RipIdir #MusiqueAlgerienne</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="32" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="549"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:p8JgOv7Hybw</id>
  <yt:videoId>p8JgOv7Hybw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>India at 142 on World Press Freedom Index over Kashmir blackout</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p8JgOv7Hybw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T10:40:13+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T10:45:16+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>India at 142 on World Press Freedom Index over Kashmir blackout</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/p8JgOv7Hybw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/p8JgOv7Hybw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>India has dropped two places on the World Press Freedom Index, now ranking at 142 out of 180 countries.
Reporters Without Borders says a communications blackout in Indian-administered Kashmir, which made it increasingly difficult for journalists to report on what is happening in the region, played a significant role in that shift.
Their report calls the area a &quot;vast open prison&quot;.
Yet, India's government maintains there is nothing short of absolute media freedom.
 
Al Jazeera’s Elizabeth Puranam reports from New Delhi.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#WorldPressFreedomDay  #WorldPressFreedomIndex  #IndiaPressFreedom</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="326" average="4.25" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3680"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:CaL355gY0Ew</id>
  <yt:videoId>CaL355gY0Ew</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Trump threatens action against China over COVID-19</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CaL355gY0Ew"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T10:16:10+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T10:18:14+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Trump threatens action against China over COVID-19</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/CaL355gY0Ew?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/CaL355gY0Ew/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>While some individual states have already filed suits against China, the administration of US President Donald Trump is reportedly considering measures against China for its handling of the coronavirus pandemic.
Trump’s position is that China could have done more to warn and protect the world from the pandemic.
Such measures could worsen already strained relations between Washington and Beijing.

Al Jazeera’s John Hendren reports from Chicago in the US state of Illinois.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#UScoronavirus  #Trump  #China</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="220" average="4.42" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7765"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:b4WcewTMccg</id>
  <yt:videoId>b4WcewTMccg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Social media criticism in Iran as petrol prices stay high</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b4WcewTMccg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T09:50:58+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T09:50:59+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Social media criticism in Iran as petrol prices stay high</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/b4WcewTMccg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/b4WcewTMccg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The global fall in oil prices has left many governments reeling, but Iran's president says his country's economy is able to cope better than most, thanks to being forced to diversify because of US sanctions.
When global oil prices fell earlier this month, some Iranians turned to social media and began asking for the savings to be passed on to them.

Al Jazeera’s Zein Basravi reports from Tehran, Iran.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Iran  #PetrolPrice  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="126" average="4.68" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="6440"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:NZRgrcl9GEA</id>
  <yt:videoId>NZRgrcl9GEA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Coronavirus: US meat processing plants forced to close</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NZRgrcl9GEA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T08:58:56+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T09:00:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Coronavirus: US meat processing plants forced to close</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/NZRgrcl9GEA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/NZRgrcl9GEA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The pandemic has forced meat-processing plants across the US to slow down production or close entirely.
But on April 28, President Donald Trump invoked a war-time law, ordering plants to stay open to avoid any shortages.
Labour unions are worried that this will mean the workers’ safety is put at risk, as they are forced to stand close together in the plants.

Al Jazeera’s Alan Fisher reports from Falls Church in the US state of Virginia.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#UScoronavirus  #MeatSupply  #Trump</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="78" average="4.74" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4322"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:jPE8NxtGBmg</id>
  <yt:videoId>jPE8NxtGBmg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Spain emerges from lockdown as strict measures ease further</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jPE8NxtGBmg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T07:24:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T07:24:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Spain emerges from lockdown as strict measures ease further</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/jPE8NxtGBmg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jPE8NxtGBmg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>After 50 days of lockdown, Spaniards have been allowed to leave their homes to exercise outside.
The country has been one of the hardest-hit in the world, but the numbers of infections and deaths are now decreasing.
Spain's prime minister has urged caution though and says masks will be compulsory on public transport from next week.
 
Al Jazeera’s Sonia Gallego reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Coronavirus  #EuropeCoronavirus  #Spain</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="33" average="4.64" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2931"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:26p8iQohKRc</id>
  <yt:videoId>26p8iQohKRc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>US coronavirus death toll surpasses 65,000</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=26p8iQohKRc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T06:41:19+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T06:41:20+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>US coronavirus death toll surpasses 65,000</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/26p8iQohKRc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/26p8iQohKRc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Nearly half of the states in the US have partially reopened for business as the number of deaths from COVID-19 swells past 65,000.
So far, testing shows more than 1.1 million people have been infected with COVID-19 nationwide. 
But there is a glimmer of hope in New York, as cases there continue to decline, although New York Governor Andrew Cuomo says the numbers are still “terrifyingly high”.

Al Jazeera’s Rob Reynolds reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#UScoronavirus  #COVID19  #AljazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="114" average="4.61" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="8129"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vGv0ywFc4vQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>vGv0ywFc4vQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dozens killed in Venezuela prison riot</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vGv0ywFc4vQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-03T05:32:16+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-03T05:32:17+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dozens killed in Venezuela prison riot</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vGv0ywFc4vQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vGv0ywFc4vQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>More than 40 people have been killed during a prison riot in Venezuela.  
The protest started over a demand for relatives to be allowed to visit in order to bring food and medicines.
Riots in Latin America's overcrowded prisons have been increasing as coronavirus restrictions are put in place.

Al Jazeera’s Teresa Bo reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Venezuela  #Coronavirus  #LosLlanos</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="74" average="4.62" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4902"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
