<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Al Jazeera English</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-11-23T14:12:43+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:plcm0jEZbR0</id>
  <yt:videoId>plcm0jEZbR0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>George Floyd killing: A pivotal moment in US history? | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=plcm0jEZbR0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T22:44:46+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T22:48:29+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>George Floyd killing: A pivotal moment in US history? | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/plcm0jEZbR0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/plcm0jEZbR0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>When video of another unarmed Black man's death goes viral, what is its real impact? In Minnesota and across the US, days of public outrage and protests have followed the killing of George Floyd, a 46-year-old Minneapolis man who died after a white police officer used his knee to pin his neck to the ground. Footage of the incident has circulated widely on social media, reigniting African American trauma and conversations about racism, law enforcement and white supremacy in the country. 

In this episode, we'll discuss anger over Floyd's death and how people across the United States are responding. 

Join the conversation
TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream
Subscribe to our channel  http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe

#Aljazeeraenglish
#News
#GeorgeFloyd
#BlackLivesMatter</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="46" average="3.43" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="0"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:jMSHnqbY1eU</id>
  <yt:videoId>jMSHnqbY1eU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Mexico to start reopening from lockdown amid rising infections</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jMSHnqbY1eU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T19:27:40+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T19:47:14+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Mexico to start reopening from lockdown amid rising infections</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/jMSHnqbY1eU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jMSHnqbY1eU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Mexico plans to start reopening on Monday, two and a half months after it went into lockdown.
But infections are still on the rise.
Al Jazeera's John Holman joined paramedics near Mexico City.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Coronavirus #Mexico</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="87" average="4.68" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4478"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:YlOcNncJCoU</id>
  <yt:videoId>YlOcNncJCoU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sudan gold, fuel smuggling costs hundreds of millions annually</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YlOcNncJCoU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T19:17:10+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T19:29:16+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sudan gold, fuel smuggling costs hundreds of millions annually</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/YlOcNncJCoU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/YlOcNncJCoU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Gold and fuel smuggling costs resource-rich Sudan hundreds of millions of dollars a year.
A new report by financial watchdog group Global Financial Integrity(GFI) has revealed the extent of mismanagement in those sectors and its impact on the economy.
Al Jazeera's Hiba Morgan reports from Khartoum.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Sudan</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="50" average="4.92" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3567"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:3aps85d34Ew</id>
  <yt:videoId>3aps85d34Ew</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Al-Aqsa Mosque reopens after COVID-19 closure</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3aps85d34Ew"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T18:56:51+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T18:57:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Al-Aqsa Mosque reopens after COVID-19 closure</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/3aps85d34Ew?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/3aps85d34Ew/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Al-Aqsa Mosque in occupied East Jerusalem has reopened.
It had been closed for two months to contain COVID-19.
Worshippers have been asked to wear face masks and bring their prayer mats.
Al Jazeera's Harry Fawcett is on the ground with more.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Israel #Palestine</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="162" average="4.75" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2854"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:ArAUkFQsWVI</id>
  <yt:videoId>ArAUkFQsWVI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>How divisive is politics in the United States? I Inside Story</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ArAUkFQsWVI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T17:30:01+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T17:30:02+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>How divisive is politics in the United States? I Inside Story</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/ArAUkFQsWVI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/ArAUkFQsWVI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Running battles with the police, fires burning, lootings and protesters arrested.
Riots over the death of George Floyd have spread across dozens of U.S. cities, and close to President Donald Trump's doorstep at the White House.
Governors have imposed curfews and dispatched National Guards.
The Floyd case has reignited rage over the deaths of black Americans at the hands of police and racial inequality. 
It's also opened a divisive political debate between Democrats and Republicans.
President Donald Trump has promised to put an end to what he calls 'mob violence'.
Trump says healing is needed, but he's accused of the oppositie - igniting tension.
So can America overcome its divisions?

Presenter: Kim Vinell

Guests
Maurice Jackson, an Associate Professor in the History Department and African American Studies at Georgetown University.
Kevin Powell, author and civil rights activist.
Sahar Aziz, professor of law &amp; Chancellor’s Social Justice Scholar at Rutgers University

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #UnitedStates</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="500" average="4.54" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="28394"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:jFBzaVJ1UJs</id>
  <yt:videoId>jFBzaVJ1UJs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Drive-in theatres see revival amid lockdowns</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jFBzaVJ1UJs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T17:12:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T17:31:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Drive-in theatres see revival amid lockdowns</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/jFBzaVJ1UJs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jFBzaVJ1UJs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Going to watch a movie or a concert under the stars is back in fashion.
Drive-in theatres are seeing an unusual revival as cinemas and theatres worldwide remain closed because of coronavirus restrictions.
Al Jazeera's Priyanka Gupta explains.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="29" average="4.45" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2795"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:DH0LbI23kHY</id>
  <yt:videoId>DH0LbI23kHY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Zimbabwe lockdown: Grandmothers offer free therapy</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DH0LbI23kHY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T15:37:28+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T15:37:29+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Zimbabwe lockdown: Grandmothers offer free therapy</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/DH0LbI23kHY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/DH0LbI23kHY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Health experts say globally there has been an increase in anxiety and depression as people struggle to cope with COVID -19 and job losses.

Some grandmothers in Zimbabwe are offering free therapy sessions to tackle these mental health difficulties during the coronavirus lockdown. This is part of an initiative called the Friendship Bench.

Al Jazeera's Haru Mutasa reports from the city of Gweru in Zimbabwe. 

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#AlJazeeraEnglish #Zimbabwe #Coronavirus</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="39" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2542"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:5pivozUk3GY</id>
  <yt:videoId>5pivozUk3GY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Why is coronavirus killing BAME Britons?  | The Stream</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5pivozUk3GY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T15:31:58+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T16:06:35+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Why is coronavirus killing BAME Britons?  | The Stream</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/5pivozUk3GY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/5pivozUk3GY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Ethnic minorities make up less than 20 percent of the British population but the outsized impact of coronavirus on their communities is startling. 
 
According to the UK’s Office for National Statistics black people are four times more likely to die from COVID-19 than white people. Ethnic Bangladeshi and Pakistani men are 1.8 times more likely to have a COVID-19-related death than white males. And ethnic minority women are 1.6 times more likely to die from the virus.
 
The impact on frontline workers is similarly stark. Almost 100 black, Asian and ethnic minority (BAME) medical staff are now known to have died from COVID-19. 
 
Under growing political pressure, the British government and National Health Service have launched a public health inquiry with initial findings due at the end of May. The opposition Labour party has begun an independent investigation of its own. 
 
Research available so far suggests several factors are driving the high infection rates and death toll in socioeconomically disadvantaged groups - bigger households, higher rates of comorbidities such as diabetes and heart disease, large numbers of BAME workers in frontline services and a lack of information in community languages.
 
Some scientists are examining whether a genetic component, alongside the other risk factors, may also predispose BAME populations to complications from COVID-19.
 
In this episode of The Stream, we look into the numbers and meet BAME community members to ask why the pandemic is having such a devastating impact on them.


Join the conversation
TWITTER: https://twitter.com/AJStream
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/AJStream
Subscribe to our channel  http://bit.ly/AJSubscribe


#aljazeeraenglish
#ajstream
#BAME</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="501" average="4.43" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="21737"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:FBYtdSvuEFM</id>
  <yt:videoId>FBYtdSvuEFM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Science journalism in the spotlight | The Listening Post (Feature)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FBYtdSvuEFM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T13:18:38+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T13:18:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Science journalism in the spotlight | The Listening Post (Feature)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/FBYtdSvuEFM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/FBYtdSvuEFM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>For months now, journalists around the world have been on a crash course in reporting on medical science. But they had no experience in covering a pandemic.

Now we are turning to journalists with some actual credentials in this field: science and health reporters. In many cases, they were the first to recognise the dangers of the outbreak in Wuhan, leaving the rest of us to play catch-up. The Listening Post's Flo Phillips spoke with three science journalists, from three different countries, about how they sounded the alarm on the virus that would come to be known as COVID-19.

&quot;It was something I definitely thought we needed to be watching,&quot; Helen Branswell, Senior Infectious Disease Reporter for STAT news explained. &quot;The reports out of China were starting to become alarming because the numbers were growing pretty quickly. So if you watch these kinds of outbreaks over time, this was something that was setting off alarm bells.&quot;

And in fact, many of these reporters have been watching out for these types of outbreaks for years. Back in 2013, Kai Kupferschmidt, a contributing correspondent for Science magazine, wrote an article about a bat in China carrying a potential pandemic.

&quot;Again and again, in the last 10 years or so, when I was doing my reporting, this sentence came up from scientists,&quot; Kupferschmidt said. &quot;They were telling me, you know, it's not a question of if there will be a big pandemic. The question is when.&quot;

Since the outbreak, science journalists have been relentlessly reporting. They have introduced audiences to concepts such as flattening the curve and social distancing; they have explained the need for lockdowns and mass testing, and; they have challenged governments on their pandemic responses. For their efforts, many have witnessed skyrocketing readership and online followings. But this new attention has come with a price, as political polarisation can often taint the information and lead to ad hominem attacks.

&quot;They want the reporting to be in line with the politics so that it doesn't make India look bad&quot;, said Vidya Krishnan, a health and science journalist from the country. &quot;The minute the story goes online, we have government handles and politicians attacking individual reporters and questioning our integrity and dismissing the story without actually pointing out what's wrong factually that's being put out.&quot;

In the United States, a similar picture has emerged.

&quot;One of the things that I found tragic about this pandemic and the coverage of the pandemic is how politicised the whole thing has become,&quot; said Branswell. &quot;Which side of the divide people fall on relates to which party they support. There's a deep misunderstanding of what's going on in certain parts of the country.&quot;

With COVID-19 becoming as much about the politics as it is about the science, many science journalists have been left out of the daily press briefings - hardly the best use of available resources when the story you are covering is a pandemic.

&quot;I'm not sure that science journalists need to take the lead, but I certainly think they should be at the table,&quot; said Kupferschmidt. &quot;There are a lot of important questions that science journalists know to ask that political journalists don't know to ask. It just seems like this press conference would really profit if there were also science journalists there.&quot;

Contributors:
Helen Branswell - Senior Infectious Disease Reporter, STAT
Kai Kupferschmidt - Contributing Correspondent, Science magazine
Vidya Krishnan - Health and Science Journalist

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="18" average="4.78" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1303"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:peJMq_9NmcY</id>
  <yt:videoId>peJMq_9NmcY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>DR Congo activists fight misinformation around COVID-19</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=peJMq_9NmcY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T10:53:13+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T10:53:13+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>DR Congo activists fight misinformation around COVID-19</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/peJMq_9NmcY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/peJMq_9NmcY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The number of confirmed coronavirus infections in the Democratic Republic of the Congo has risen to nearly 3,000 - seeing its highest daily jump on Friday.
But many people do not believe COVID-19 is a threat, and activists are trying to change that.
 
Al Jazeera’s Charlotte Bellis reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Coronavirus #Congo  #AlJazeeraEnglish</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="30" average="4.73" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2856"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:hzJfYdd-WcU</id>
  <yt:videoId>hzJfYdd-WcU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>US protesters defy curfews as outrage over police brutality intensifies</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hzJfYdd-WcU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T09:09:49+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T09:09:50+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>US protesters defy curfews as outrage over police brutality intensifies</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/hzJfYdd-WcU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/hzJfYdd-WcU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Protests against racism have spread to even more US cities, becoming violent in many of them.
What began as demonstrations over the death of George Floyd after being arrested, has reawoken national outrage over deaths blamed on the police.
 
Al Jazeera’s Mike Hanna reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#JusticeForGeorgeFlyod #GeorgeFloyd #GeorgeFloydprotest</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="800" average="4.78" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="55212"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:QFWkj6fCeAw</id>
  <yt:videoId>QFWkj6fCeAw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Call for economic support for Indian-administered Kashmir</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QFWkj6fCeAw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T08:30:02+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T08:36:42+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Call for economic support for Indian-administered Kashmir</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/QFWkj6fCeAw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/QFWkj6fCeAw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>India reported another record daily jump of almost 8,000 new coronavirus infections on Saturday.
But, it is slowly easing its strict lockdown.
The government is trying to cushion the economy from its worst contraction in 40 years.
One region particularly affected is Indian-administered Kashmir where business leaders are predicting a disaster.
 
Al Jazeera’s Elizabeth Puranam reports from New Delhi.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Kashmir  #India  #IndiaLockdown</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="207" average="3.40" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="6995"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:y-yElcRKG7s</id>
  <yt:videoId>y-yElcRKG7s</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>SpaceX and NASA astronauts make historic launch</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y-yElcRKG7s"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T07:19:13+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T07:26:13+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>SpaceX and NASA astronauts make historic launch</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/y-yElcRKG7s?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/y-yElcRKG7s/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A new era of space travel has begun after the first privately-owned rocket sent two NASA astronauts into orbit.
The SpaceX aircraft successfully launched from Cape Canaveral in Florida. It was the US's first manned space flight in almost 10 years.
 
Al Jazeera’s Andy Gallacher reports from Florida, US.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#SpaceX  #NASA  #Falcon9</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="281" average="4.72" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="12539"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:K14GtaIp4FY</id>
  <yt:videoId>K14GtaIp4FY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Brazil's coronavirus death toll now the world's fourth-highest</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K14GtaIp4FY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Al Jazeera English</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCNye-wNBqNL5ZzHSJj3l8Bg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T06:52:04+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T06:52:05+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Brazil's coronavirus death toll now the world's fourth-highest</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/K14GtaIp4FY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/K14GtaIp4FY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Latin American countries are struggling to get the coronavirus outbreak under control.
Brazil has now surpassed France to record the fourth-highest death toll in the world.
 
Al Jazeera’s Alessandro Rampietti reports.

- Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe 
- Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish 
- Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera 
- Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/

#Brazil  #Coronavirus  #COVID19</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="166" average="4.64" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="17779"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
