<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</id>
 <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
 <title>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <author>
  <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2008-08-02T09:14:56+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:AAX9h3ljRJ8</id>
  <yt:videoId>AAX9h3ljRJ8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Suffering in pain, older dog with mange healed.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AAX9h3ljRJ8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-17T13:00:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T07:30:54+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Suffering in pain, older dog with mange healed.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/AAX9h3ljRJ8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/AAX9h3ljRJ8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Turn suffering to radiant beauty.  Please donate: 
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

Even when this darling old boy was in excruciating pain, he was gentle, kind and considerate. From the first moment he saw our rescue team, he seemed to want to  put his fading life in our hands. Every day of his 6-week treatment for advanced, life-threatening mange, his humble nature only gave pleasure to others. Cured of mange, neutered and much healthier, meet mighty old Monty now!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="18311" average="4.98" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="130184"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:VyerqInDq98</id>
  <yt:videoId>VyerqInDq98</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Wounded and rescued, wild piglets get the greatest gift of all...</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VyerqInDq98"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-10T13:00:17+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-12T12:21:58+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Wounded and rescued, wild piglets get the greatest gift of all...</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/VyerqInDq98?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/VyerqInDq98/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>For injured and emotional babies, please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

A wild piglet was seriously hurt with multiple puncture wounds from an animal attack. Even hours after her wounds were cleaned and bandaged, this young sweetheart trembled with fear. She had never been touched by a human hand before, and it scared her. She would need incredible bravery, but snuggled deep into her blanket for the feeling of the comfort she had known sleeping with her siblings against her mother's big body. Now she was all alone. Though she ate well, she was facing a long recovery, and she may have been significantly depressed. But someone very special was waiting for her, though none of us would have guessed. 

Just one week after her admission, we rescued another little piglet with similar puncture wounds--a little boy piglet full of his own noisy squeals and twirls. As we treated his wound, we told him he was in for a beautiful surprise. As soon as we had secured his bandages, we delighted in introducing him to his new friend. Though they were a few weeks different in age, pigs are such social and emotional beings that no questions were asked! They bonded within minutes. We felt we could see their healing accelerate from the sheer joy in each other's comfort and...play! Watch these tumble-bunnies in action.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="25268" average="4.95" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="319940"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Ie27ksvYIiM</id>
  <yt:videoId>Ie27ksvYIiM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog's amazing recovery after leopard attack left him horrifically wounded.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ie27ksvYIiM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-03T13:00:19+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-14T19:34:03+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog's amazing recovery after leopard attack left him horrifically wounded.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Ie27ksvYIiM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Ie27ksvYIiM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The most frightening injuries need the bravest effort. Please donate:
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate

We can only imagine that the leopard was interrupted, though no one saw the attack--maybe this dog fought back too hard. He was in utter shock for hours after the attack to his throat and chest. Residents from a nearby village hurried him to our hospital. Saving his life seemed an almost impossible assignment. But his strength was phenomenal, and the jaws of the leopard had closed on him just millimeters short of killing him. 

His astonished eyes stayed wide as adrenalin ran through his body long after arriving in our hospital. A great amount of flesh had been simply taken, and there was insufficient skin remaining to stitch closed the wounds. We could only keep them clean and snuggly bandaged, and changed them every day for 2 months. To our amazement, this dignified boy completely healed. 

Meet Beesi today!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="56324" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1292623"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:ov8LEOMHOgk</id>
  <yt:videoId>ov8LEOMHOgk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Puppy's paw was crushed and degloved, but when he healed, he sang!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ov8LEOMHOgk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-08-28T13:00:30+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-13T05:12:14+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Puppy's paw was crushed and degloved, but when he healed, he sang!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/ov8LEOMHOgk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/ov8LEOMHOgk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>You can put a song in someone's heart. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

This precious teenaged puppy screamed in pain when his rescuers tried to lift him. His feet had been run over by a vehicle, and one paw was crushed and degloved. His toes were splayed and swollen to twice their normal size. Standing was too excruciating to bear. Had he been an older dog with more brittle bones, he might have been facing an amputation, but this young boy still had soft bones. 

We treated his wound and wrapped his intensely painful feet in thick bandages which we changed every day. The little guy was one of the most careful young patients we've ever had. He seemed determined to cause no fuss. But he was so inward we wondered if he was depressed. Then, when he'd progressed a bit on his healing journey, well, this boy burst out in song. Meet Elvis now!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="48767" average="4.93" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="976129"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:eMAl_rmzTRI</id>
  <yt:videoId>eMAl_rmzTRI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog's eyeball ruptured, urgent surgery saved Sammy's life.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eMAl_rmzTRI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-08-21T13:00:14+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-15T04:45:52+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog's eyeball ruptured, urgent surgery saved Sammy's life.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/eMAl_rmzTRI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/eMAl_rmzTRI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Love can lift someone out of suffering. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

Few injuries are more horrible to imagine than a ruptured eyeball, but this gentle boy's eye had ruptured. His suffering was extreme. The wound may have been caused by a passing vehicle hitting his head from behind. His excruciating pain had exhausted him, and he completely gave himself to his rescuer without the slightest resistance. 

Maybe he knew he was in safe hands. But could he know that those safe hands would hold him tight for the rest of his life?

It was evening when he arrived at the hospital, and to prepare him for surgery in the morning we treated him for pain and made sure he did not eat or drink prior to surgery. His eye could not be saved, but the procedure went well, and he woke up from surgery immediately relieved. But only then did we realize, Sammy was also blind in the other eye. We've welcomed him to live for the rest of his life in the happy sanctuary of Animal Aid. What a snugglebug he has become, and we hope you'll join us in falling in love with Sammy.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="40120" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="655253"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:0o5Pl8u4VJI</id>
  <yt:videoId>0o5Pl8u4VJI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Join our street treatment team for the day!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0o5Pl8u4VJI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-08-13T13:00:00+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-13T02:29:05+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Join our street treatment team for the day!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/0o5Pl8u4VJI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0o5Pl8u4VJI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please help us by supporting our street treatment program: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

Join us on the road as our Street Treatment medical team makes their daily rounds in the neighborhoods. You'll see how much good medical care can be administered while sparing an animal the stress of entering the hospital, avoiding contact with infectious diseases and staying close to their friends and families. It's also interesting for people who don't live in Udaipur to get a glimpse of the neighborhoods we work in. So hop on in and join us for a fascinating few minutes of loving care.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="21879" average="4.92" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="374745"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:DKpuplmxBM0</id>
  <yt:videoId>DKpuplmxBM0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Precious baby donkey's pain made him terrified, but when he healed, he loved!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DKpuplmxBM0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-08-07T13:00:10+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-08-27T01:52:11+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Precious baby donkey's pain made him terrified, but when he healed, he loved!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/DKpuplmxBM0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/DKpuplmxBM0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Helping someone who is hurting feels so good. Please donate: 
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

This little donkey's wound on his backside must have multiplied in size and depth once maggots began destroying the live tissue. Still energetic and optimistic, this precious boy, who we called Micky, seemed to have no idea that he was in grave danger and would have died without urgent rescue. 

His mother's love would be a vital comfort to him, so of course we brought them together, and Mom's face, within moments, seemed to express relief that they were now in safe, healing hands. 

Watch now, as Micky's fear, during the days to come, turned into love.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="77333" average="4.80" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4811675"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:k1MvY8EfAT0</id>
  <yt:videoId>k1MvY8EfAT0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Shocked by the trauma of multiple wounds, but Chickpea didn't give up...</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k1MvY8EfAT0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-07-30T13:00:25+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-12T14:46:57+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Shocked by the trauma of multiple wounds, but Chickpea didn't give up...</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/k1MvY8EfAT0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/k1MvY8EfAT0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Help them sparkle again. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate

When a neighbor saw a young dog who was too weak to climb out of a gutter, they called our rescue team. Gently, when we lifted her, we saw that she had multiple puncture wounds and was completely weak. Once back at the hospital we treated her with IV fluids for shock, but her condition was declining, and she took short rapid breaths. 

It was nighttime and she was able to feel secure in the quiet of her kennel bed. By morning, her breathing had normalized, but she was still collapsed. Even eating was impossible for her to do alone. But within a few days, her sparkle was returning and we caught a glimpse of her first tail wag. 

Meet adorable Chickpea now!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="28675" average="4.89" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="782837"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:RCoc0Vuhi-U</id>
  <yt:videoId>RCoc0Vuhi-U</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>With her last ounce of strength, she wagged her tail.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RCoc0Vuhi-U"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-07-24T13:00:23+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-13T06:49:54+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>With her last ounce of strength, she wagged her tail.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/RCoc0Vuhi-U?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RCoc0Vuhi-U/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The reason to help is in their eyes. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

This sweetheart suffered with mange probably most of her short life, and the mange was winning: she had collapsed in the corner of a shed and would never have stood up again if rescuers had not arrived. 

At the sound of our voices, she found the strength to wag her tail, and her black button eyes told us all we needed to know. She needed help or she would die. We hurried her to the hospital and gave her an IV drip to hydrate and nourish her. By morning she was already slightly improved, and we began treating her infected wounds and mange. 

Her progress was immediate, and with delight we helped give her the care and love she needed to blossom. Meet Cotton now! 

This video is for educational and motivational purposes.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="93247" average="4.85" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4645413"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:LIP4-_vnYhE</id>
  <yt:videoId>LIP4-_vnYhE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>10 astounding rescues to make your heart race.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LIP4-_vnYhE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-07-17T13:00:17+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-12T11:19:27+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>10 astounding rescues to make your heart race.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/LIP4-_vnYhE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/LIP4-_vnYhE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Sometimes there's not a moment to lose. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

A desperate dog swimming in circles and near drowning with exhaustion; a dog stuck upside down in a narrow passageway; a young bull who would have been stuck until death after falling in a well, and other extreme disasters for street animals who could not survive without the help of human beings. 

Again and again, it's the neighbors who waste no time in calling our ambulance, helping lift animals to safety and lifting our hearts. Your heart will race just watching these astounding rescues.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="54841" average="4.75" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3381593"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:SLhR0b2s3eU</id>
  <yt:videoId>SLhR0b2s3eU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Terrible life-threatening wounds on most cheerful sweet dog.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SLhR0b2s3eU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-07-09T13:00:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-02T17:52:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Terrible life-threatening wounds on most cheerful sweet dog.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/SLhR0b2s3eU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/SLhR0b2s3eU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Life is precious. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate

Hiding in pain and wailing when touched, this dog had been hit by a car, her hind leg fractured and partially degloved; her front leg sliced deeply at the top. But as soon as she understood she was safe in the arms of her rescuer, this girl stopped howling and wagged her tail. Unbelievable! 

And when we eased her pain with medication, wound dressing, splint and surgery on her forearm wound, she gave us the most beautiful reward: non-stop smiles filled with love throughout the coming weeks of her healing. 

Bessie's one of the precious souls who lives life like a song of gratitude, to the air, the earth; to her animal friends, to us, and to you.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="38934" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="593961"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:43QuVrRcaEE</id>
  <yt:videoId>43QuVrRcaEE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Impaled by a rod, dog in agony before rescue--beautiful recovery.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=43QuVrRcaEE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-07-02T13:00:03+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-17T22:11:18+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Impaled by a rod, dog in agony before rescue--beautiful recovery.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/43QuVrRcaEE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/43QuVrRcaEE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Extra love helps those who need extra courage. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

Neighbors spotted a beautiful dog laying by a rod in a construction site. When they came closer they saw to their horror that the rod had pierced through her thigh and she had impaled her. She couldn't get free no matter how she struggled. They called Animal Aid to the rescue, and we quickly arranged for workers to come with an electric metal saw. 

The terrified dog had to endure terrifying sounds of the saw against the metal, but we covered comforted her while the rod was cut and we were able to free her. 

Her wound was serious but because no bones had broken, we were able to clean, bandage and protect her with antibiotics. After her ordeal, she needed extra love to find the courage she would need to heal. 

And after a month of daily wound dressings and many cuddles, meet Shylee now!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="460245" average="4.95" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="12339035"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:O6uAR3Kf2Xk</id>
  <yt:videoId>O6uAR3Kf2Xk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Circling and disoriented, puppy rescued with head injury is a happy boy now.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O6uAR3Kf2Xk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-06-26T13:00:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-06-27T06:41:48+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Circling and disoriented, puppy rescued with head injury is a happy boy now.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/O6uAR3Kf2Xk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/O6uAR3Kf2Xk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Help young angels have wagging tails for many years to come. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/

Stumbling and circling, this beautiful puppy's brain was injured after his head was hit by a passing car. His tender-hearted neighbors saw his extreme disorientation and called us to the rescue. 

His breathing was distressed and rapid and we worried that he might be bleeding internally. The first job was to stabilize his breathing; we gave him oxygen and medicine to reduce swelling. Regaining his balance and orientation would take weeks. We are so grateful that his brain damage isn't permanent but his adorable charm sure is. 

Meet Shabi now, one of the world's TRUE angels.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="22669" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="302619"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:WKibkpSsTVA</id>
  <yt:videoId>WKibkpSsTVA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rescue of bleeding and terrified young dog.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WKibkpSsTVA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-06-19T13:00:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-08-19T05:51:02+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rescue of bleeding and terrified young dog.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/WKibkpSsTVA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/WKibkpSsTVA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Some little heroes need extra love in order to heal. Please donate.
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate

This sweetheart was overcome with fear after being hit by a car. His lower canine tooth was dislodged and bled profusely and he couldn't stand. Although he had no broken bones, it took several days before he had the strength to stand on his own. 

His most aching pain, however, was his broken tooth, and the day after he was admitted we popped him in and out of surgery to extract it. This little guy--we named him Rana--was so emotional that he wouldn't eat until he was cuddled and reassured. 

Rana was neutered as soon as he was strong enough, and now he's as good as new. If courage is measured by overcoming fear, Rana proved to be a very brave little boy.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="225221" average="4.87" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="9474359"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:B-caXBT4Q6w</id>
  <yt:videoId>B-caXBT4Q6w</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sweetest bull horrifically wounded by car, rescued.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B-caXBT4Q6w"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-06-13T13:00:09+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-05T19:07:43+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sweetest bull horrifically wounded by car, rescued.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/B-caXBT4Q6w?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/B-caXBT4Q6w/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The vehicle must have slammed into this beautiful bull at high speed. 

A huge chunk of flesh was simply missing as blood and gnarled tissue slipped along his ribs. Several passing motorists called us immediately after it happened, and we rushed to the site to find one of the most gentle beings we have ever met. 

From his first painful wound dressing until now, fully healed, Rollie did everything he could to make his difficult medical treatments as easy as possible. And when he healed, he set about nurturing the babies. 

Meet this giant love--Rollie--today.

Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="149206" average="4.84" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="10052223"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
