<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</id>
 <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
 <title>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <author>
  <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2008-08-02T09:14:56+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kvhgOBjGlyE</id>
  <yt:videoId>kvhgOBjGlyE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sparkling recovery of collapsed and anorexic street puppy.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kvhgOBjGlyE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-05T12:57:52+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-05T14:25:57+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sparkling recovery of collapsed and anorexic street puppy.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kvhgOBjGlyE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kvhgOBjGlyE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>When we first saw this skinny puppy it looked like he had been hit by a car, but then his neighbors told us that he had stopped eating and suddenly was unable to stand. When we examined him in the hospital we determined by his nasal discharge, diarrhea and loss of appetite that he probably had canine distemper, a virus that can be fatal and for which there is no direct treatment. Because distemper sufferers often develop what's called secondary pneumonia, we gave him preventive antibiotics and were so happy that he began eating within the first day. He was so sensitive that it seemed like love was as important to him as food itself and we wondered if his condition could have improved without it. He didn't stand for quite a few days, and when he did, he seemed to be propelled by his will to give love. Meet Sparkle now!
Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="28646" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="297804"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kM_MEp-zpqE</id>
  <yt:videoId>kM_MEp-zpqE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Healing a cow's huge wound after crocodile attack (graphic footage)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kM_MEp-zpqE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-01T12:52:53+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-11T06:53:40+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Healing a cow's huge wound after crocodile attack (graphic footage)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kM_MEp-zpqE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kM_MEp-zpqE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>We really didn't believe a crocodile had attacked this cow when the neighbors called to report her injury. But she had been grazing just near Madar Lake, which is home to small crocodiles who have been seen by many farmers over the years. When we saw her wound, we gasped, and we believed. This probably wasn't a false report; we think she really was attacked by a crocodile. Nothing else could explain the jagged edges of this enormous, deep and life-threatening wound. We were unable to suture it closed because there was insufficient skin remaining. We closed the wound with a smaller flap of skin, and stitched into place thread which would secure daily wound dressings for more than 100 days to come. Meet beautifully-healed Emma today. 
Many bandages may be needed but unimaginable pain CAN disappear. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

This video includes actual footage from surgery and is intended for educational and inspirational purposes to encourage viewers to support street animal rescue, volunteering and protection of animals everywhere.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="48467" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="424192"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:jAQJwEOgcs8</id>
  <yt:videoId>jAQJwEOgcs8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Feeding hungry animals on silent streets during lockdown in Udaipur.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jAQJwEOgcs8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-27T14:28:33+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-27T15:07:54+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Feeding hungry animals on silent streets during lockdown in Udaipur.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/jAQJwEOgcs8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jAQJwEOgcs8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Lockdown in India has been so hard for street animals whose normal source of food comes from vendors, leftovers from restaurants or human tiffins, and the kindness of people who casually have the habit of sharing their last roti with a passing dog or cow; who feed the crispy end of their samosa at the chaiwala to the little tail-wagger at his feet; sabjiwalas who offer their damaged fruit and vegetables to whatever big beauty is wandering by. With the lockdown, the streets are silent and most of the usual sources of food for street animals disappeared overnight.  Like thousands--perhaps millions--of people across India, we realized a few days into the lockdown that the problem was quickly becoming urgent. As you can see from these faces, each individual is beautifully grateful.
And so are we, to the donors who have provided 2000 chapatis a day and money for the kibble, the rice, the dal, the petrol, and to the animal lovers across India to whom we dedicate this little video.

Every street animal needs friends. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="28746" average="4.98" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="211456"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:J-5QoQ2-hyI</id>
  <yt:videoId>J-5QoQ2-hyI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Nearly-impossible recovery of young street dog with two deadly conditions.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J-5QoQ2-hyI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-23T12:09:07+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-27T05:43:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Nearly-impossible recovery of young street dog with two deadly conditions.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/J-5QoQ2-hyI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/J-5QoQ2-hyI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Two deadly conditions meant survival was unlikely for this emaciated young street dog. Half her face had been eaten by maggots and she was also suffering from the often- fatal canine distemper virus. For many days we prepared ourselves for the chance that she would &quot;go down hill&quot; because fighting that virus calls for incredible strength. To have your strength simultaneously used to heal from a devastating and huge wound, it's just hard to imagine anyone surviving. Her body seemed so fragile and defeated when we rescued her. But her strength must have come from her soul. After weeks of treatment and love, meet Juliet now! 
For street animals in anguish, let's give happiness. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="34206" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="482581"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:MNHpua0lqQo</id>
  <yt:videoId>MNHpua0lqQo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Mother cow lavishes love on her wounded baby</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MNHpua0lqQo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-16T13:09:00+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-09T06:19:49+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Mother cow lavishes love on her wounded baby</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/MNHpua0lqQo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/MNHpua0lqQo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

A serious wound covered in flies caused this baby intense distress. We brought both the calf (Moon) and his mother (Jupiter) to Animal Aid for his several weeks of treatment. As soon as his wound was cleaned and bandaged, his mood lightened incredibly, and he constantly invited his mom to play. It was as if he felt so secure with her always by his side that he was the perfect little patient, and she was the perfect loving angel always in the wings. 
In most dairies, including the backyard dairies in villages, when a baby is only a couple of days old, they are taken from their anguished mother cows or tied apart from her to prevent the baby from nursing or having any physical contact. Watching Jupiter and Moon, it's very clear that snuggling, grooming and touching is as important as sunlight and air. But Jupiter couldn't clean and bandage Moon's wound. That's where you come in</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="31099" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="295908"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:9OVqMtjoTEk</id>
  <yt:videoId>9OVqMtjoTEk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Growing gravel instead of skin: older dog rescued with advanced mange</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9OVqMtjoTEk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-13T14:25:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T18:48:45+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Growing gravel instead of skin: older dog rescued with advanced mange</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/9OVqMtjoTEk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/9OVqMtjoTEk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

The crusting from advanced mange was encasing this older dog as if he was growing gravel instead of skin. Though mange is curable, he was made so frail by this terrible skin disease that we knew he could lose his life in his battle. He touched our hearts with his quiet, understated determination. But though he was subtle, his nature was so incredibly sweet that everyone loved him as soon as they looked into his innocent eyes. And when he was healed, he was as beautiful on the outside as he was, all along, on the inside. Meet Ramu today. You can help a downcast dog lift his head again. In hope.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="22218" average="4.95" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="372749"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:id2OHz_Z-FA</id>
  <yt:videoId>id2OHz_Z-FA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Beloved street dog before and after: rescued from road accident.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=id2OHz_Z-FA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-06T12:14:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:21:03+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Beloved street dog before and after: rescued from road accident.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/id2OHz_Z-FA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/id2OHz_Z-FA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

Kali is a &quot;community dog&quot; with several families watching over her, but she has no guardian considering her as a personal possession and she lives like other street dogs in her neighborhood, traipsing here and there. When Kali was hit by a bike, her neighbors were distraught, but they had probably never carried a dog before, and when they saw that she couldn't get up, they called us to help her. We thought initially that she might have a spine injury because she couldn't bear weight on any of her legs, but after a few days we came to believe it might have been a head injury that caused her problems balancing and a sense of disorientation after she began to be able to stand and move a little bit. Her loving nature would not hear of giving up, though, and she most cheerfully loved her physio-therapy sessions. Gradually, her orientation returned, and we were able to bring her back to the loving neighbors who she had missed so much. Kali's reunion with them is beautiful. Happiness is...getting someone home soon. 
Rescued on: 13/Feb/2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="17636" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="189287"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vv9OkwR_YKw</id>
  <yt:videoId>vv9OkwR_YKw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Abused bull gives only sweetness to everyone.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vv9OkwR_YKw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-29T12:58:45+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:20:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Abused bull gives only sweetness to everyone.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vv9OkwR_YKw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vv9OkwR_YKw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

Angelo is a bull who we found in excruciating pain with multiple ropes digging through the flesh of his front leg clear to the bone. The wound was a result of someone having tightly tied his leg to his horns--a devastating technique used by ignorant farmers to keep cows from escaping, and to prevent bulls from mating because they cannot lift their heads. Usually a single rope is tied, and you often see cows crouched and hobbling down the roads with their heads bent low, and you can almost feel the horrendous neck strain. But in Angelo's case, the abuse was compounded with time and perhaps with the extra shortness of the rope. He very likely had no owner but the dairyman whose cows lived in this bull's neighborhood perhaps only wanted to breed his cows artificially using the sperm of foreign breeds, which are often thought to produce more milk. For Angelo, it almost ended his life. But Angelo, whose only experience with human hands had been to suffer human cruelty, just radiated sweetness. Even during daily wound dressings that must have sometimes been painful, Angelo seemed to understand that we were trying our best to help him. His eyes are soft; his face composed and loving.  Within a month, his bandages could come off, and this is the &quot;person&quot; Angelo is when his suffering is all behind him. 
Let's turn cruelty to kindness.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="40626" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="383559"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:iNhKiMNuKIo</id>
  <yt:videoId>iNhKiMNuKIo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Baby piglet Olivia's beautiful life (and near death rescue)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iNhKiMNuKIo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-24T12:58:36+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:20:09+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Baby piglet Olivia's beautiful life (and near death rescue)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/iNhKiMNuKIo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/iNhKiMNuKIo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

Olivia's story is a simple rescue of a piglet with a wound in her neck. Her treatment and recovery are made sweeter by loving care from people, which she desperately needed because she is very young and we couldn't find her mother. But there's another story here--about her intelligence, humor, playfulness, and sensitivity. Qualities most pigs had at birth, but were never allowed to explore or develop. By the time you have finished watching this happy little 4-minute video, thousands of pigs will have been killed in the meat industry. Each of these individuals have qualities like Olivia's. Each one wanted to think, to create, to play, to feel this magical earth beneath her little toes, just like Olivia is doing now. #EveryPigIsOlivia 
Precious. Life.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="36973" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="870111"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:8JqXutdrA5Y</id>
  <yt:videoId>8JqXutdrA5Y</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Animals in disasters--10 rescues to make your heart stand still.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8JqXutdrA5Y"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-19T14:29:41+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:19:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Animals in disasters--10 rescues to make your heart stand still.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/8JqXutdrA5Y?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/8JqXutdrA5Y/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

Stuck, caught, trapped, these animals tried with all their strength to free themselves but they couldn't do it alone. They would have died where they were if not for help. Our human species has a lot to apologize for to the animals, but when these angels were at the brink of death, they got what they so desperately needed and deserved: freedom. Be a part of our rescue team.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="202049" average="4.78" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="16278699"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:qv0GcsfE8Tw</id>
  <yt:videoId>qv0GcsfE8Tw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rescue of abandoned male calf starved for food, and for his mother's love</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qv0GcsfE8Tw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-12T13:54:30+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:19:13+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rescue of abandoned male calf starved for food, and for his mother's love</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/qv0GcsfE8Tw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/qv0GcsfE8Tw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

Little Rish's ordeal ends so happily, but mosts male calves are not as lucky as Rish. We found him collapsed and half starved, abandoned to fend for himself in a world of boundary walls, fences, roads full of cars and garbage. He was too weak to stand. We scooped him up and brought him back to life with food and the snuggles he desperately missed from his mother, who is probably chained in a dairy, broken-hearted for missing him. We can each do so much to lighten this load of suffering. Reduce and eliminate the use of all animal products in what we eat, wear and use. It's easier than you might think. And life will be so much sweeter for the animals who share the world with us.
Every day for animals should be beautiful.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="53536" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2273618"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:QeDcQQn5FsI</id>
  <yt:videoId>QeDcQQn5FsI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>After losing her eye, unable to walk, sweet mother recovers and sees her puppies again.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QeDcQQn5FsI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-08T13:22:32+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:18:41+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>After losing her eye, unable to walk, sweet mother recovers and sees her puppies again.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/QeDcQQn5FsI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/QeDcQQn5FsI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

Blunt trauma from being hit by a car had caused this older mother dog's eye to escape its socket and the muscles were ruptured. Her hip was also dislocated and she couldn't bear any weight. But she was keeping close to her babies. Luckily, they were almost weaning age, and the kindest neighbor promised to feed them when the rescue team arrived. Watch this magnificent mother's patience and trust during a healing road 10 weeks long. After her eye was removed, the greater challenge would prove to be walking. At 8 weeks, she still couldn't bear weight and we were losing hope. But she just needed a few more days! Now spayed and reunited with her plump happy puppies, meet Betty now.  For gentle old girls who need extra time to heal.
Rescued on: 11 Jan 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="86404" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1973404"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:bZ2b_oQmYxU</id>
  <yt:videoId>bZ2b_oQmYxU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Horrific pain crushed this dog's smile, but his pure joy was waiting</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bZ2b_oQmYxU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-01T13:59:34+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-17T05:54:15+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Horrific pain crushed this dog's smile, but his pure joy was waiting</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/bZ2b_oQmYxU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/bZ2b_oQmYxU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Once you see how delightful this incredibly sweet dog is, it will be hard to imagine he could be so sad in his suffering from a serious wound on his head.  But powered by his passionate will to live and smile again, his response to medical care and love amazed us when he fully healed within 2 weeks.  
When pain lifts a spirit can rise.
Rescued : 13 Feb 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="36684" average="4.98" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="305657"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:AsbG2qyNnxs</id>
  <yt:videoId>AsbG2qyNnxs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Bull grew but the rope did not, healing an excruciating wound</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AsbG2qyNnxs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-03-27T13:34:04+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:17:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Bull grew but the rope did not, healing an excruciating wound</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/AsbG2qyNnxs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/AsbG2qyNnxs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

The blood gradually began to ooze from the deep huge forehead wound caused by a rope squeezing tighter and tighter over months. Ownerless, we cannot fathom what moved someone to bind this poor gentle boy in the first place, only to then turn him loose to find his food on roadside plants and grasses. He grew, but the rope, of course, did not. When we found him, he was starting to fade away. Pain had dulled his appetite and he'd grown weary of fighting it. But within hours we had the maggots out of the wound, flushed away all the dirt and blood, and soothed him with a snug bandage that we would change daily for 7 weeks. We're so eager for you to meet Socrates here. The best remedy for human mistreatment of animals is extra kindness. 
Rescue date : 16 January 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="143713" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="8651465"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:p23dlV53Wy0</id>
  <yt:videoId>p23dlV53Wy0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Little puppy's face doubled in size from infection, rescued.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p23dlV53Wy0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-03-21T11:35:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-16T13:16:57+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Little puppy's face doubled in size from infection, rescued.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/p23dlV53Wy0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/p23dlV53Wy0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Please make a donation to help rescue street animals: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html

Poor little one. Fluid had collected in the tissue around his cheeks and jaws, giving this sweet boy a big balloon face from an infected wound on his forehead. His blood-encrusted face was in so much pain that even enduring the wound cleaning was hard for him, but he was brave and so strong that within 5 days he was ready to go home to his mother and siblings, cheerful, bouncing and already beloved by everyone who met him. Fare thee well wee Timothy!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="37299" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="598908"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
