<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</id>
 <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
 <title>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <author>
  <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2008-08-02T09:14:56+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:id2OHz_Z-FA</id>
  <yt:videoId>id2OHz_Z-FA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Beloved street dog before and after: rescued from road accident.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=id2OHz_Z-FA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-06T12:14:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-06T15:32:34+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Beloved street dog before and after: rescued from road accident.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/id2OHz_Z-FA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/id2OHz_Z-FA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Kali is a &quot;community dog&quot; with several families watching over her, but she has no guardian considering her as a personal possession and she lives like other street dogs in her neighborhood, traipsing here and there. When Kali was hit by a bike, her neighbors were distraught, but they had probably never carried a dog before, and when they saw that she couldn't get up, they called us to help her. We thought initially that she might have a spine injury because she couldn't bear weight on any of her legs, but after a few days we came to believe it might have been a head injury that caused her problems balancing and a sense of disorientation after she began to be able to stand and move a little bit. Her loving nature would not hear of giving up, though, and she most cheerfully loved her physio-therapy sessions. Gradually, her orientation returned, and we were able to bring her back to the loving neighbors who she had missed so much. Kali's reunion with them is beautiful. Happiness is...getting someone home soon. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html
Rescued on: 13/Feb/2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="14892" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="140823"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vv9OkwR_YKw</id>
  <yt:videoId>vv9OkwR_YKw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Abused bull gives only sweetness to everyone.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vv9OkwR_YKw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-29T12:58:45+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-06T09:17:30+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Abused bull gives only sweetness to everyone.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vv9OkwR_YKw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vv9OkwR_YKw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Angelo is a bull who we found in excruciating pain with multiple ropes digging through the flesh of his front leg clear to the bone. The wound was a result of someone having tightly tied his leg to his horns--a devastating technique used by ignorant farmers to keep cows from escaping, and to prevent bulls from mating because they cannot lift their heads. Usually a single rope is tied, and you often see cows crouched and hobbling down the roads with their heads bent low, and you can almost feel the horrendous neck strain. But in Angelo's case, the abuse was compounded with time and perhaps with the extra shortness of the rope. He very likely had no owner but the dairyman whose cows lived in this bull's neighborhood perhaps only wanted to breed his cows artificially using the sperm of foreign breeds, which are often thought to produce more milk. For Angelo, it almost ended his life. But Angelo, whose only experience with human hands had been to suffer human cruelty, just radiated sweetness. Even during daily wound dressings that must have sometimes been painful, Angelo seemed to understand that we were trying our best to help him. His eyes are soft; his face composed and loving.  Within a month, his bandages could come off, and this is the &quot;person&quot; Angelo is when his suffering is all behind him. 
Let's turn cruelty to kindness. Please donate. www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="36418" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="315582"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:iNhKiMNuKIo</id>
  <yt:videoId>iNhKiMNuKIo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Baby piglet Olivia's beautiful life (and near death rescue)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iNhKiMNuKIo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-24T12:58:36+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-04-29T11:14:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Baby piglet Olivia's beautiful life (and near death rescue)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/iNhKiMNuKIo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/iNhKiMNuKIo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Olivia's story is a simple rescue of a piglet with a wound in her neck. Her treatment and recovery are made sweeter by loving care from people, which she desperately needed because she is very young and we couldn't find her mother. But there's another story here--about her intelligence, humor, playfulness, and sensitivity. Qualities most pigs had at birth, but were never allowed to explore or develop. By the time you have finished watching this happy little 4-minute video, thousands of pigs will have been killed in the meat industry. Each of these individuals have qualities like Olivia's. Each one wanted to think, to create, to play, to feel this magical earth beneath her little toes, just like Olivia is doing now. #EveryPigIsOlivia 
Precious. Life. Please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="35219" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="816051"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:8JqXutdrA5Y</id>
  <yt:videoId>8JqXutdrA5Y</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Animals in disasters--10 rescues to make your heart stand still.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8JqXutdrA5Y"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-19T14:29:41+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-05T09:46:13+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Animals in disasters--10 rescues to make your heart stand still.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/8JqXutdrA5Y?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/8JqXutdrA5Y/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Stuck, caught, trapped, these animals tried with all their strength to free themselves but they couldn't do it alone. They would have died where they were if not for help. Our human species has a lot to apologize for to the animals, but when these angels were at the brink of death, they got what they so desperately needed and deserved: freedom. Be a part of our rescue team. Please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="146940" average="4.84" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="10116932"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:qv0GcsfE8Tw</id>
  <yt:videoId>qv0GcsfE8Tw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rescue of abandoned male calf starved for food, and for his mother's love</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qv0GcsfE8Tw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-12T13:54:30+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-04-13T06:04:31+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rescue of abandoned male calf starved for food, and for his mother's love</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/qv0GcsfE8Tw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/qv0GcsfE8Tw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Little Rish's ordeal ends so happily, but mosts male calves are not as lucky as Rish. We found him collapsed and half starved, abandoned to fend for himself in a world of boundary walls, fences, roads full of cars and garbage. He was too weak to stand. We scooped him up and brought him back to life with food and the snuggles he desperately missed from his mother, who is probably chained in a dairy, broken-hearted for missing him. We can each do so much to lighten this load of suffering. Reduce and eliminate the use of all animal products in what we eat, wear and use. It's easier than you might think. And life will be so much sweeter for the animals who share the world with us.
Every day for animals should be beautiful. Please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="51811" average="4.91" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2136834"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:QeDcQQn5FsI</id>
  <yt:videoId>QeDcQQn5FsI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>After losing her eye, unable to walk, sweet mother recovers and sees her puppies again.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QeDcQQn5FsI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-08T13:22:32+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-04-13T05:20:54+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>After losing her eye, unable to walk, sweet mother recovers and sees her puppies again.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/QeDcQQn5FsI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/QeDcQQn5FsI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Blunt trauma from being hit by a car had caused this older mother dog's eye to escape its socket and the muscles were ruptured. Her hip was also dislocated and she couldn't bear any weight. But she was keeping close to her babies. Luckily, they were almost weaning age, and the kindest neighbor promised to feed them when the rescue team arrived. Watch this magnificent mother's patience and trust during a healing road 10 weeks long. After her eye was removed, the greater challenge would prove to be walking. At 8 weeks, she still couldn't bear weight and we were losing hope. But she just needed a few more days! Now spayed and reunited with her plump happy puppies, meet Betty now.  For gentle old girls who need extra time to heal, please donate:  www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html
Rescued on: 11 Jan 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="84916" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1931524"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:bZ2b_oQmYxU</id>
  <yt:videoId>bZ2b_oQmYxU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Horrific pain crushed this dog's smile, but his pure joy was waiting</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bZ2b_oQmYxU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-04-01T13:59:34+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-04-17T16:09:41+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Horrific pain crushed this dog's smile, but his pure joy was waiting</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/bZ2b_oQmYxU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/bZ2b_oQmYxU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Once you see how delightful this incredibly sweet dog is, it will be hard to imagine he could be so sad in his suffering from a serious wound on his head.  But powered by his passionate will to live and smile again, his response to medical care and love amazed us when he fully healed within 2 weeks.  
When pain lifts a spirit can rise. Please donate.
www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html
Rescued : 13 Feb 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="35922" average="4.98" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="291850"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:AsbG2qyNnxs</id>
  <yt:videoId>AsbG2qyNnxs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Bull grew but the rope did not, healing an excruciating wound</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AsbG2qyNnxs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-03-27T13:34:04+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-04-10T06:40:50+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Bull grew but the rope did not, healing an excruciating wound</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/AsbG2qyNnxs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/AsbG2qyNnxs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The blood gradually began to ooze from the deep huge forehead wound caused by a rope squeezing tighter and tighter over months. Ownerless, we cannot fathom what moved someone to bind this poor gentle boy in the first place, only to then turn him loose to find his food on roadside plants and grasses. He grew, but the rope, of course, did not. When we found him, he was starting to fade away. Pain had dulled his appetite and he'd grown weary of fighting it. But within hours we had the maggots out of the wound, flushed away all the dirt and blood, and soothed him with a snug bandage that we would change daily for 7 weeks. We're so eager for you to meet Socrates here. The best remedy for human mistreatment of animals is extra kindness. Please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.donate.html
Rescue date : 16 January 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="131061" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7558300"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:p23dlV53Wy0</id>
  <yt:videoId>p23dlV53Wy0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Little puppy's face doubled in size from infection, rescued.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p23dlV53Wy0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-03-21T11:35:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-03-21T12:10:08+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Little puppy's face doubled in size from infection, rescued.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/p23dlV53Wy0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/p23dlV53Wy0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Poor little one. Fluid had collected in the tissue around his cheeks and jaws, giving this sweet boy a big balloon face from an infected wound on his forehead. His blood-encrusted face was in so much pain that even enduring the wound cleaning was hard for him, but he was brave and so strong that within 5 days he was ready to go home to his mother and siblings, cheerful, bouncing and already beloved by everyone who met him. Fare thee well wee Timothy! For little guys with big problems, please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="35013" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="540983"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:28H7g4k3pEA</id>
  <yt:videoId>28H7g4k3pEA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Scalded and suffering donkey rescued and healed.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=28H7g4k3pEA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-03-16T12:55:35+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-03-16T13:09:21+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Scalded and suffering donkey rescued and healed.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/28H7g4k3pEA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/28H7g4k3pEA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>How Noori's burns and deep wounds were caused we'll never know. He may have been rolled in a car accident. He went missing from his owner one day, and was found later by workers at a construction site. From the looks of him, he hadn't eaten for several days, and while he hid in pain, maggots took over the wounds. His whole being seemed to cry out in silent innocence. We cleaned his wounds and changed his bandages every day for 5 months, and as Noori healed, his little light shined brighter and brighter. For animals who deserve better, please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="42836" average="4.91" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1703691"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:1Vq_9LcJkc8</id>
  <yt:videoId>1Vq_9LcJkc8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Worried old paralyzed dog rescued. After 2 months of therapy meet Buster now.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Vq_9LcJkc8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-03-12T13:03:26+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-03-15T00:44:32+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Worried old paralyzed dog rescued. After 2 months of therapy meet Buster now.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/1Vq_9LcJkc8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/1Vq_9LcJkc8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>He no longer could walk. This gentle boy was hit by a car and his spine was damaged. He couldn't bear weight, his hind feet flexed backwards and we thought he might be paralyzed for life. But little by little we saw signs of progress and neither he nor his caregivers would give up. He didn't have blood or fractures, but life as he knew it appeared to be over. After 6 weeks of therapy, meet gorgeous Buster today! Beautiful things happen when you try.  Please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="85959" average="4.95" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3736747"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:LAfMqxHNHH8</id>
  <yt:videoId>LAfMqxHNHH8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Puppy screams for help locked in rock-solid tar.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LAfMqxHNHH8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-03-05T13:31:27+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-03-08T00:13:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Puppy screams for help locked in rock-solid tar.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/LAfMqxHNHH8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/LAfMqxHNHH8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Three gorgeous puppies were encased in hardened road tar when our rescue team arrived, and their sibling had died from the toxic hardened tar. Two of the three had made their way back to their mother with tar over half their little bodies. 

But one was stuck to the earth, and to avoid pulling her skin off, rescuers had to cut and pry big slabs of stone and tar to carry with her to the hospital where all 3 puppies would undergo hours of labor as Animal Aid staff and volunteers softened the tar by soaking it in cooking oil and pulling it off little bit by bit.

The puppies' little faces could not have looked more forlorn. By the time the tar was removed, they were soooo exhausted. But all the more WONDERFUL to see them playing in joy after a good night's sleep in the furry warmth of their Momma.

Removing tar is difficult, but LOVE is easy. Please donate: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="122463" average="4.95" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4764480"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:IsEvvn63-NI</id>
  <yt:videoId>IsEvvn63-NI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog's neck torn open saved by surgery</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IsEvvn63-NI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-02-29T10:21:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-03-30T21:54:46+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog's neck torn open saved by surgery</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/IsEvvn63-NI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/IsEvvn63-NI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Her skin hung heavily on her throat, detached by a 4-inch cut that exposed all of this sweet dog's neck muscles. She would need stitches to survive, and when our rescue team arrived, she let us scoop her up without the slightest resistance.  We were relieved to see that the edges of the cut were clean enough that suturing was possible.  When she healed, she simply glowed. We named her Sunny-day, and wow, just look at her now! Please donate for life-saving surgery: www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="46120" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1299445"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:-jR9cRc82Ag</id>
  <yt:videoId>-jR9cRc82Ag</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Badly injured elderly dog insists on belly rubs!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-jR9cRc82Ag"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-02-23T10:44:23+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-03-15T17:25:57+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Badly injured elderly dog insists on belly rubs!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/-jR9cRc82Ag?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/-jR9cRc82Ag/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>With a horribly infected neck wound and a second painful wound on her stomach, this badly injured dog had the heart to ask her rescuers for belly rubs! Isn't this older dog, who we've named Muriel, telling us so clearly that love helps us heal?  Please donate! www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate.html</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="23690" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="252483"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
