<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</id>
 <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
 <title>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <author>
  <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2008-08-02T09:14:56+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:zU5ydE4_ChM</id>
  <yt:videoId>zU5ydE4_ChM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Injured and emotional, street puppy needed to be home in order to heal.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zU5ydE4_ChM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-10-09T13:30:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-10-09T18:37:06+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Injured and emotional, street puppy needed to be home in order to heal.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/zU5ydE4_ChM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/zU5ydE4_ChM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Most puppies adapt almost overnight to their hospital stay, flourishing in the stimulation and play and love our Puppytown. But little Fluffy, with a badly injured hip, seemed filled with a homesickness he just couldn't get over. 

Probably hit by a passing vehicle, his hip was badly bruised and he couldn't bear any weight. He needed bedrest, food and cuddles. But even after a week,  he continued to seem sad, and would hardly try to stand. He barely even played with the other puppies. 

When Fluffy was rescued, we noticed his mother and father watching from down the road. Could this be why his heart seemed broken? Although he was still limping, we decided to try an early release, to see if being with his parents again would help him rally. And the moment he saw his neighbors, a different, joyous mood emerged. 

We kept in good contact with the family close by, who told us he was doing well. But we hardly recognized Fluffy on our one-month visit. Meet him now! 

You can turn sad, to happy. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="19984" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="180999"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:RHo9grPiiJU</id>
  <yt:videoId>RHo9grPiiJU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Look what love can do. Paralysed street dog's rescue and recovery.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RHo9grPiiJU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-10-01T13:23:55+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-10-01T13:29:25+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Look what love can do. Paralysed street dog's rescue and recovery.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/RHo9grPiiJU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RHo9grPiiJU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>How easy it might have been to miss this stranded, paralysed young dog altogether. He didn't make a sound. He just kept still, because it hurt him too much to move at all. 

Meet Precious, a young boy so sweet you'll feel you've met a real spirit, an angel. He had suffered trauma to his spine and could no longer bear weight on his hind legs. We gave a six week protocol of bed rest and light physiotherapy sessions and hoped his backward-flexed toes did not mean he would never walk again.

But days went by without progress. We were starting to lose heart. 
But Precious wasn't losing heart. 

For those who need more time: Please donate.
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="24164" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="434931"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:rb_IsrDHBGk</id>
  <yt:videoId>rb_IsrDHBGk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Tragedy struck this dreamy dog, and rescue saved her.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rb_IsrDHBGk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-09-19T13:18:43+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-10-05T02:02:52+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Tragedy struck this dreamy dog, and rescue saved her.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/rb_IsrDHBGk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/rb_IsrDHBGk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Elegant and subtle, this gorgeous lady dog was wounded by what appears to have been animal bites. It's possible that the bites abscessed but were covered with this girl's abundant fur, and no one could see the wounds. Compounding the problem were maggots, who bored tunnels into the necrotic tissue. 

When the dead tissue was sloughed off, the fur came with it, and now this dog's caring neighbor could see, astonished, the massive damage. He called us right away, and so began Dreamy's healing process. She relaxed with us right away, because she is one who had already experienced loving human comfort. Dreamy would have died without rescue. Instead, she healed in just 3 weeks, and we spayed her before returning her to her neighborhood and caring friend. 

Beautiful outcomes start with trying. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="25691" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="229175"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:PgBFZNLu-Y8</id>
  <yt:videoId>PgBFZNLu-Y8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Tender-hearted donkey's neck wounded ear-to-ear, now rescued and healed.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PgBFZNLu-Y8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-09-13T14:29:46+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-19T15:19:28+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Tender-hearted donkey's neck wounded ear-to-ear, now rescued and healed.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/PgBFZNLu-Y8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PgBFZNLu-Y8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Lacerated, infected with bacteria and maggots, the massive wound encircled this donkey like a hideous necklace of pain. This injury was caused by the friction of a rope bound far too tight. At first the gentle victim was terrified of being touched, but as days turned to weeks in his beautiful healing process, this sweet little guy gained trust, confidence and strength. 

We've named him Samson, after the famous story of small Samson and the giant named Goliath. Someday with your help animal cruelty will stop. For all the meek and mild, let your love give strength. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="31456" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="909870"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:08IB-QdwIMA</id>
  <yt:videoId>08IB-QdwIMA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Healing a massive wound on a small street puppy.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=08IB-QdwIMA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-09-05T13:42:19+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-12T16:28:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Healing a massive wound on a small street puppy.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/08IB-QdwIMA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/08IB-QdwIMA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Jeelu was hiding as many animals do when they are suffering acute pain. Normally cheerful and always charming, this young teenage puppy must have had her skin snagged by a passing vehicle and the wound was so wide that stitching it closed was not an option. She needed several weeks of daily wound care, flushing, re-bandaging and rest in order to stabilize. 

The final stage of healing could take place outside the hospital. With a kind and caring family in her home neighborhood, we knew it would be safer to return her where human and animal friends would welcome her, and avert the danger of exposure to the viruses other hospital patients can carry. 

Checking on her every week, we watched Jeelu flourish, and you can too. 
For small animals with big wounds, please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="43762" average="4.87" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1662644"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:FZep-ic-1Rs</id>
  <yt:videoId>FZep-ic-1Rs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog's forearm degloved yet her tail wagged as rescuers arrived (graphic footage).</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FZep-ic-1Rs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-08-29T13:05:34+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-03T02:11:49+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog's forearm degloved yet her tail wagged as rescuers arrived (graphic footage).</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/FZep-ic-1Rs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/FZep-ic-1Rs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Before she collapsed in pain, Aisha made it all the way back to her neighbor's house to show them how desperately she needed help. When she saw her rescuers, her tail wagged with relief. 

Most of the skin of her forearm was torn off in this horrible degloving accident. But luckily there were no fractures and because her neighbors alerted us immediately, we arrived before exposure to air and dirt could cause more damage to the tissue. 

Aisha seems to fill everyone around her with light. Real angels are among us. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate

#desidogs #streetdogs #streetanimalrescue</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="32303" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="337174"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:d69VQ0wZMgE</id>
  <yt:videoId>d69VQ0wZMgE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Emaciated and sick with mange, street dog blossoms from love.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d69VQ0wZMgE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-08-23T13:46:28+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-23T13:53:50+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Emaciated and sick with mange, street dog blossoms from love.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/d69VQ0wZMgE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/d69VQ0wZMgE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>We got a call that a street dog was covered in mange. We hadn't expected to find a dog so emaciated. We're not sure if the hunger had made her vulnerable to mange, or if mange had so disturbed her that she could no longer even search for food. We were so relieved that she started eating right away. 

We treated her mange with medicine and daily baths, and waited eagerly for the first signs of recovery. These signs did not happen overnight. In fact it took almost a month of coaxing before Primrose (named for a flower we knew was waiting inside her) started to show signs of happiness. And then, something changed. Suddenly Primrose blossomed with a radiant smile. She started to put on weight and her shining new coat of fur began to grow in. What a sweet, velvety girl she is today. 

For spirits who won't give up, please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="21447" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="260539"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:W0941lVubTg</id>
  <yt:videoId>W0941lVubTg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Abandoned and disabled, getting Pumba back on his feet.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W0941lVubTg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-08-22T14:51:48+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-22T14:51:48+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Abandoned and disabled, getting Pumba back on his feet.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/W0941lVubTg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/W0941lVubTg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This sweet boy was abandoned when his guardians no longer wanted him. He may have lost his ability to walk because he was not allowed to move around. He had no muscle tone at all. And he is one of the most adorable individuals you'll ever meet. 

Watch the beautiful efforts of staff and volunteers to get Pumba back on his feet. 

If you're in India, he is available for adoption to a loving family who promises never to chain him again, and to give this very social boy at least 2 hours every day to exercise and play with dog and human friends. And wherever you live, adopt a rescue dog.  

For more information about adoptions from Animal Aid within India, go to: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/how-to-help/adopt/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="24886" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="350005"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:M3F-1IYg0es</id>
  <yt:videoId>M3F-1IYg0es</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog's huge laceration heals quickly after surgery.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M3F-1IYg0es"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-08-15T13:18:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-21T05:37:43+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog's huge laceration heals quickly after surgery.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/M3F-1IYg0es?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/M3F-1IYg0es/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Meet Lucky-love, who suffered a horrendous laceration but had the good luck of living in a city with a street animal rescue service, AND a caring family who saw his wound just minutes after it happened. They didn't see what hit him, but it looks like he went straight to the family for help. And they knew just what to do: they called Animal Aid and within a few hours Lucky-love was in our surgery having the huge wound repaired. 

Lucky-love doesn't live inside anyone's house. He has neighborhood friends both animals and humans and lives a life of cheerful adventure on a peaceful street with kind neighbors. How lucky we were to see his home turf and be reminded that life for many street dogs is beautiful, when there is a caring family and a responsive rescue team, who he turned to for one last cuddle before rejoining his neighborhood friends.

When it's a question of helping someone who hurts, the answer is Yes. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="57188" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2348971"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:L_9S_enEaJE</id>
  <yt:videoId>L_9S_enEaJE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Abandoned bull's harness had cut to the bone, rescued.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L_9S_enEaJE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-08-09T12:23:07+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-21T03:20:31+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Abandoned bull's harness had cut to the bone, rescued.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/L_9S_enEaJE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/L_9S_enEaJE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>When Guddu was a calf, his mother's owner tied a rope around his head and made sure he only got a minimum of his mother's milk so that most of it could be sold. For dairy farmers around the world, bulls are &quot;surplus&quot; and are gotten rid of in several ways. 

When Guddu was abandoned and left on the road, his owner left the harness on, probably not thinking his bull would even live long enough to outgrow it. Somehow, Guddu did live and grow--enough so that his halter almost took his life. The wounds it caused behind his ears, horns and on his nose, are very hard to look at, let alone imagine enduring. 

But beautiful Guddu was just the gentlest sweetheart every step of the way. Even bulls are fragile. 

Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="46161" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="564311"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:nZm6WANloos</id>
  <yt:videoId>nZm6WANloos</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Surgery saves street dog with huge tumor.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nZm6WANloos"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-07-31T10:04:44+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-13T15:19:59+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Surgery saves street dog with huge tumor.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/nZm6WANloos?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/nZm6WANloos/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Time was running out for this old street dog. We rescued her just in time for life-saving surgery. An enormous and rapidly-growing abdominal tumor was within weeks --maybe days--of growing into her vital organs. Janvi's astounding peacefulness is a deep part of her nature. The trust she gave us can probably be credited to the kindness of her human neighbors who were so glad to welcome her back after surgery. Janvi has every chance for a bright future, and she has a glowing present life, too. With help, even a big problem can disappear. 

Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="57150" average="4.86" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2681589"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:wfSZGjBfxxY</id>
  <yt:videoId>wfSZGjBfxxY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Unbearable neck pain makes old dog's entire body rigid.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wfSZGjBfxxY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-07-24T14:16:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-13T15:18:48+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Unbearable neck pain makes old dog's entire body rigid.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/wfSZGjBfxxY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/wfSZGjBfxxY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Whoever says animals can't speak hasn't met Orlando. His sorrowful cries told a group of strangers that he was in excruciating pain and needed help. His worrying eyes expressed his confusion when we brought him to the examination table. And his adoring smile announced as clear as a bell that he loved his care-giver, Dhapu. Meet Orlando, whose injuries were invisible, so he told us all about them. Animals can speak. They say &quot;I hurt.&quot; They say &quot;I feel better now.&quot; And they say Thank You. 

Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="62521" average="4.92" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1478453"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:EjQ_R7C21lM</id>
  <yt:videoId>EjQ_R7C21lM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>So many wounds on a tiny body, puppy's beautiful recovery (graphic footage).</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EjQ_R7C21lM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-07-17T14:31:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-24T11:59:17+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>So many wounds on a tiny body, puppy's beautiful recovery (graphic footage).</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/EjQ_R7C21lM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/EjQ_R7C21lM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Multiple wounds tore open this puppy's neck, shoulders and ear, we rescued this puppy as he sat trembling and woozy with pain. We hurriedly gave the beautiful little victim pain medicine, hydration drip, bandaging and food, but the best part of his rescue was holding him close and experiencing the marvel of his recovery. Within days, Tiggy's incredibly playfulness and boundless affection took over. 
There's nothing better than a happy ending. 

Please donate. https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="135121" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4710541"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:OwU0A2MlEBI</id>
  <yt:videoId>OwU0A2MlEBI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Puppy's lower lip was completely torn off, extraordinary recovery (graphic footage)</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OwU0A2MlEBI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-07-05T10:38:38+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-05T23:56:49+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Puppy's lower lip was completely torn off, extraordinary recovery (graphic footage)</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/OwU0A2MlEBI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/OwU0A2MlEBI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>When we got the call that a puppy was covered in blood we had no idea how bad it could be. The entire skin, muscle and tissue flap that attaches to a dog's lower gums had been ripped away from the bone. As soon as we examined her in the hospital we realized that surgery was the only way to save her life, and even if we saved it today, we weren't sure what might happen to the exposed jaw during the coming days.

This angel's lower lips, and all the skin under the jaw, had to be removed. There was simply nothing to attach it to. The gum tissue wasn't strong enough to hold sutures. And she had to be able to open her mouth to eat. Even bandaging the area would be impossible.  We had never before performed a surgery to remove so much tissue from a dog's muzzle.

Watch this simply extraordinary recovery. We've called this little hero Joy, and you'll see why.

Emergencies can have happy endings. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="105915" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2256413"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:nZ0z6ZNyol8</id>
  <yt:videoId>nZ0z6ZNyol8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Mange almost took his life, but what a happy boy now!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nZ0z6ZNyol8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-27T13:30:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-07-03T11:25:06+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Mange almost took his life, but what a happy boy now!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/nZ0z6ZNyol8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/nZ0z6ZNyol8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The family who occasionally feeds this street dog could barely recognize him when he showed up in front of their house after a long disappearance. Hairless, his face was encrusted and blistered with mange, and his skin was almost purple from scratching. But he responded to medical help incredibly fast. He was accustomed to human kindness and treating him was a pleasure. We were able to return him to his neighborhood within just a few weeks, neutered and mange-free, and you can see in the final scenes that Duggu was just ecstatic to be back with his people. 

Let's get someone home. Healed. 
Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="24908" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="460998"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
