<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</id>
 <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
 <title>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g"/>
 <author>
  <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2008-08-02T09:14:56+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:rpDwm0QO_3w</id>
  <yt:videoId>rpDwm0QO_3w</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog's fear melts when his life-threatening wound is healed.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rpDwm0QO_3w"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-12-12T13:06:31+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-12-12T14:53:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog's fear melts when his life-threatening wound is healed.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/rpDwm0QO_3w?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/rpDwm0QO_3w/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Jason's wound was massive. All the skin of his front forelimb was pulled off when a vehicle tire caught the skin in its tread.  His pain was hard to imagine, and we watched his face stilled with worry when we gently flushed his wound. But this little wonder-boy's fear melted as soon as his wound was bandaged. Without rescue, Jason would definitely not be alive today. 

Thank you for your part in giving Jason his very own future. For Someone &quot;out there,&quot; tomorrow will come because of you. 

Please donate. https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="24986" average="4.95" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="336317"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:JIxhfVPn5Ms</id>
  <yt:videoId>JIxhfVPn5Ms</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog with fractured pelvis and face wound lay dying, but just meet her now!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JIxhfVPn5Ms"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-12-05T14:00:31+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-12-05T14:02:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog with fractured pelvis and face wound lay dying, but just meet her now!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/JIxhfVPn5Ms?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/JIxhfVPn5Ms/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The blood on her face was what alarmed our rescue team. But that wasn't this beautiful girl's worst problem. Hit by a passing vehicle, Julie had also sustained a fracture to her pelvis. Healing her facial laceration would require daily wound dressings but within days, her wounds had closed. But her pelvis injury required 6 weeks of serious bed rest in order to heal. 

While confined to a kennel, our staff gave her nurturing care every day, but she was understandably extremely eager for the day when bed rest would be over! And when that day came, Julie took full advantage. Watch this gorgeous wobbly whirlwind take the world by storm! 

Healing is beautiful. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="26900" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="214447"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:hrnY91JLDMM</id>
  <yt:videoId>hrnY91JLDMM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rescue of suffocating puppies, mother trapped in collapsed sand.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hrnY91JLDMM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-11-27T13:56:27+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-11-27T16:35:48+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rescue of suffocating puppies, mother trapped in collapsed sand.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/hrnY91JLDMM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/hrnY91JLDMM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Digging had to be lightning fast, but gentle. A mother dog was completely stuck in sand that had collapsed in a construction site. Right away we found one puppy alive and safe; we knew there would be more, but how deep? We could only remove the sand handful by handful to avoid injuring the mama dog's body and any babies who, by a miracle, might be somehow still able to breathe inside the rubble. 

Sadly, not all the puppies survived, but one little fighter was still alive in the dark depths of suffocation. We could hardly believe our eyes when the sandy mound began to wiggle. We whisked him out and placed the two babies and their exhausted mama in a kennel in our ambulance to let them rest. Then we searched for a safe new spot to make a home. We laid out blankets of burlap and when we brought the relieved threesome, this mother seemed to tell us this was &quot;just right.&quot; 

We returned a week later to find that thanks to the food provided by their neighbor every night when he returned from work, they were thriving.

When you can't save them all, save one (or two!)
Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="37854" average="4.87" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1116380"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:1fOw2_6f168</id>
  <yt:videoId>1fOw2_6f168</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>A car crushed Gracey's leg, but not her spirit!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1fOw2_6f168"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-11-22T13:34:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-12-15T01:36:37+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>A car crushed Gracey's leg, but not her spirit!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/1fOw2_6f168?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/1fOw2_6f168/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Beautiful Gracey kept still as a statue. Her leg was crushed. Blood vessels had ruptured, bones broken and displaced, muscle torn away. Her trauma was acute, and she held herself steady, as if not wanting to spend another drop of energy. Everything she had was being used to stay conscious. Her neighbor sat solemnly by, ensuring that she wouldn't try to run and hide from her pain. She trusted him, and waited. 

Our medical team brought her to our hospital, stabilized her dehydration with a drip, and in the morning we realized that we would not be able to save her leg. We hoped she would have the will to cope with her loss. She revealed very little; staying quiet, calm and alert. Had we guessed what kind of nature she had, we might have guessed &quot;peaceful.&quot; 

But that wouldn't have been quite right. We didn't realize until a few days later that we had an astounding lightning bolt on our hands, filled with the spirit of bubbly joy.

Emergency rescue begins with love. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="26034" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="185996"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:UZt7GCZ7nbY</id>
  <yt:videoId>UZt7GCZ7nbY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Suffering silently, little donkey needed urgent help.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UZt7GCZ7nbY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-11-14T13:00:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-11-15T21:39:34+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Suffering silently, little donkey needed urgent help.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/UZt7GCZ7nbY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/UZt7GCZ7nbY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Growing at a very fast rate, this poor little donkey's wound, filled with maggots, would soon kill him. During monsoon season, many donkeys are given a rest, but their owners may not see them for weeks at a time. Luckily, a passing driver saw the gaping wound and called us to the rescue. We found a very deep hole filled with hundreds of maggots. But we also found one of the most modest, sweet and loveable Beings we've ever met. 

We called him Chauncy, because it sounded formal and adorable, like him. Someone suffering in silence can heal with a song in their heart. 

Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="29227" average="4.92" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="769529"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:w_udNKGoGcc</id>
  <yt:videoId>w_udNKGoGcc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Hiding, delirious and desperately wounded, rescue of the cutest dog.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w_udNKGoGcc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-11-07T13:30:03+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-12-11T11:42:26+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Hiding, delirious and desperately wounded, rescue of the cutest dog.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/w_udNKGoGcc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/w_udNKGoGcc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>We never know what to expect when a wounded dog is hiding in a sewer drain, but when they do that, it's always bad. Desperately wounded animals seek relief in the water, but with wounds as serious as KC's, the pain persists, maddeningly. 

KC's wound was filled with maggots. He threw his head around wildly, almost delirious with pain. When our rescue team arrived, he tried to get away, but, exhausted, he could only take a few steps before we had him. Once we had removed the maggots, cleaned and snuggly bandaged his head, we found KC to be absolutely kingly in his cuteness, so loving that even before he took his first bite of food after his anesthesia wore off, he gave us one of those big-nose camera kisses. 

So that's what KC stands for. King of Cuteness, and you'll see why here. 

Your love can reach deep and lift high. 
Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="33823" average="4.98" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="271036"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:uWe-Q45Kiag</id>
  <yt:videoId>uWe-Q45Kiag</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Severe mange, wounded and starving, but this sweet dog won't give up!</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uWe-Q45Kiag"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-10-31T13:30:03+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-12-07T01:44:31+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Severe mange, wounded and starving, but this sweet dog won't give up!</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/uWe-Q45Kiag?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/uWe-Q45Kiag/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Antonio's truly astonishing recovery would not have been possible for a weaker spirit.

Advanced mange had ravaged his body, starvation had further weakened him and then, in the ultimate blow, a serious wound between his shoulders had become infested with maggots. We weren't sure if the combination of these extremely painful conditions had broken his spirit along with his resistance. But from day 2 onward we watched astounded as our medical treatment, food and love went to work.

Meet mange survivor, wound survivor, starvation survivor: unforgettable Antonio.

Someone hurting can glow again.

Please donate: 
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="38892" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="330842"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Kv9LHPYhyMw</id>
  <yt:videoId>Kv9LHPYhyMw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Legs tied together and left to die, donkey recovers from unimaginable cruelty.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kv9LHPYhyMw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-10-27T14:26:05+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-12-13T01:49:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Legs tied together and left to die, donkey recovers from unimaginable cruelty.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Kv9LHPYhyMw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/Kv9LHPYhyMw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This is Bansi and we must tell you from the beginning--he was rescued, completely healed and he has flourished. The beginning of the video is particularly heart-breaking, and the question that will probably fill your heart and mind as you watch it is simply &quot;Why?&quot; Why would the owners tie this donkey so cruelly? What deranged mind is behind this? To what purpose? Sometimes the answer &quot;Ignorance&quot; is not sufficient. We immediately began the 2 month treatment process for Bansi and he healed beautifully. He also happens to be adorable, innocent, agreeable, quiet. He's happy now and police arrested and jailed his cruel owner.

There are about 600 working donkeys in Udaipur. 

We are working to save as many as we can, with medical treatment, police and legal aid, and donkey education. Please donate:
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="160190" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7662295"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:7uLBQY9azuE</id>
  <yt:videoId>7uLBQY9azuE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Near-fatal wound couldn't compete with this dog's cheerful heart.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7uLBQY9azuE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-10-18T13:45:50+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-11-01T14:13:51+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Near-fatal wound couldn't compete with this dog's cheerful heart.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/7uLBQY9azuE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7uLBQY9azuE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Gregory may be old, tottering, toothless and arthritic, but wow, does he have something to teach us all about the strength of a cheerful heart. Gregory's head wound had become large as a saucer and filled with deadly maggots. He writhed on the ground in pain and despair when rescuers arrived to help him. 

His agitated stiff body went limp the moment he was comforted by the rescue team and once Gregory was in our care, we worried that his wound was too advanced for any medical treatment to help. But we didn't know Gregory! This old boy had a puppy's capacity to abandon himself to cuddles, pleasure and love, with a life-force that shines like the sun. 

For the happy-hearted animals who need urgent care, please donate.
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="54085" average="4.97" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="522015"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:zU5ydE4_ChM</id>
  <yt:videoId>zU5ydE4_ChM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Injured and emotional, street puppy needed to be home in order to heal.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zU5ydE4_ChM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-10-09T13:30:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-10-09T18:37:06+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Injured and emotional, street puppy needed to be home in order to heal.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/zU5ydE4_ChM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/zU5ydE4_ChM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Most puppies adapt almost overnight to their hospital stay, flourishing in the stimulation and play and love our Puppytown. But little Fluffy, with a badly injured hip, seemed filled with a homesickness he just couldn't get over. 

Probably hit by a passing vehicle, his hip was badly bruised and he couldn't bear any weight. He needed bedrest, food and cuddles. But even after a week,  he continued to seem sad, and would hardly try to stand. He barely even played with the other puppies. 

When Fluffy was rescued, we noticed his mother and father watching from down the road. Could this be why his heart seemed broken? Although he was still limping, we decided to try an early release, to see if being with his parents again would help him rally. And the moment he saw his neighbors, a different, joyous mood emerged. 

We kept in good contact with the family close by, who told us he was doing well. But we hardly recognized Fluffy on our one-month visit. Meet him now! 

You can turn sad, to happy. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="29074" average="4.92" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="552141"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:RHo9grPiiJU</id>
  <yt:videoId>RHo9grPiiJU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Look what love can do. Paralysed street dog's rescue and recovery.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RHo9grPiiJU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-10-01T13:23:55+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-10-01T13:29:25+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Look what love can do. Paralysed street dog's rescue and recovery.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/RHo9grPiiJU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RHo9grPiiJU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>How easy it might have been to miss this stranded, paralysed young dog altogether. He didn't make a sound. He just kept still, because it hurt him too much to move at all. 

Meet Precious, a young boy so sweet you'll feel you've met a real spirit, an angel. He had suffered trauma to his spine and could no longer bear weight on his hind legs. We gave a six week protocol of bed rest and light physiotherapy sessions and hoped his backward-flexed toes did not mean he would never walk again.

But days went by without progress. We were starting to lose heart. 
But Precious wasn't losing heart. 

For those who need more time: Please donate.
https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="26976" average="4.93" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="542606"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:rb_IsrDHBGk</id>
  <yt:videoId>rb_IsrDHBGk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Tragedy struck this dreamy dog, and rescue saved her.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rb_IsrDHBGk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-09-19T13:18:43+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-10-27T01:37:14+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Tragedy struck this dreamy dog, and rescue saved her.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/rb_IsrDHBGk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/rb_IsrDHBGk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Elegant and subtle, this gorgeous lady dog was wounded by what appears to have been animal bites. It's possible that the bites abscessed but were covered with this girl's abundant fur, and no one could see the wounds. Compounding the problem were maggots, who bored tunnels into the necrotic tissue. 

When the dead tissue was sloughed off, the fur came with it, and now this dog's caring neighbor could see, astonished, the massive damage. He called us right away, and so began Dreamy's healing process. She relaxed with us right away, because she is one who had already experienced loving human comfort. Dreamy would have died without rescue. Instead, she healed in just 3 weeks, and we spayed her before returning her to her neighborhood and caring friend. 

Beautiful outcomes start with trying. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="27372" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="259280"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:PgBFZNLu-Y8</id>
  <yt:videoId>PgBFZNLu-Y8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Tender-hearted donkey's neck wounded ear-to-ear, now rescued and healed.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PgBFZNLu-Y8"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-09-13T14:29:46+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-19T15:19:28+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Tender-hearted donkey's neck wounded ear-to-ear, now rescued and healed.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/PgBFZNLu-Y8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PgBFZNLu-Y8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Lacerated, infected with bacteria and maggots, the massive wound encircled this donkey like a hideous necklace of pain. This injury was caused by the friction of a rope bound far too tight. At first the gentle victim was terrified of being touched, but as days turned to weeks in his beautiful healing process, this sweet little guy gained trust, confidence and strength. 

We've named him Samson, after the famous story of small Samson and the giant named Goliath. Someday with your help animal cruelty will stop. For all the meek and mild, let your love give strength. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="35105" average="4.89" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1066899"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:08IB-QdwIMA</id>
  <yt:videoId>08IB-QdwIMA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Healing a massive wound on a small street puppy.</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=08IB-QdwIMA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-09-05T13:42:19+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-12T16:28:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Healing a massive wound on a small street puppy.</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/08IB-QdwIMA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/08IB-QdwIMA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Jeelu was hiding as many animals do when they are suffering acute pain. Normally cheerful and always charming, this young teenage puppy must have had her skin snagged by a passing vehicle and the wound was so wide that stitching it closed was not an option. She needed several weeks of daily wound care, flushing, re-bandaging and rest in order to stabilize. 

The final stage of healing could take place outside the hospital. With a kind and caring family in her home neighborhood, we knew it would be safer to return her where human and animal friends would welcome her, and avert the danger of exposure to the viruses other hospital patients can carry. 

Checking on her every week, we watched Jeelu flourish, and you can too. 
For small animals with big wounds, please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="47070" average="4.88" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1761052"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:FZep-ic-1Rs</id>
  <yt:videoId>FZep-ic-1Rs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</yt:channelId>
  <title>Dog's forearm degloved yet her tail wagged as rescuers arrived (graphic footage).</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FZep-ic-1Rs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Animal Aid Unlimited, India</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4kyYTypYb3mQ6ZL25kly6g</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-08-29T13:05:34+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-12-12T02:48:22+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Dog's forearm degloved yet her tail wagged as rescuers arrived (graphic footage).</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/FZep-ic-1Rs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/FZep-ic-1Rs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Before she collapsed in pain, Aisha made it all the way back to her neighbor's house to show them how desperately she needed help. When she saw her rescuers, her tail wagged with relief. 

Most of the skin of her forearm was torn off in this horrible degloving accident. But luckily there were no fractures and because her neighbors alerted us immediately, we arrived before exposure to air and dirt could cause more damage to the tissue. 

Aisha seems to fill everyone around her with light. Real angels are among us. Please donate: https://www.animalaidunlimited.org/donate

#desidogs #streetdogs #streetanimalrescue</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="33234" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="350956"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
