<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
 <title>CNN</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw"/>
 <author>
  <name>CNN</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2005-10-02T16:06:36+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:6tFxNQjF4qA</id>
  <yt:videoId>6tFxNQjF4qA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Murdaugh family saga a tangled web of secrets and murder</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6tFxNQjF4qA"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-18T19:20:33+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T19:37:00+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Murdaugh family saga a tangled web of secrets and murder</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/6tFxNQjF4qA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/6tFxNQjF4qA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A powerful family. A deadly boating accident. Two mysterious slayings. Drug addiction, stolen money and a botched shooting in an alleged insurance fraud scheme.
It sounds like someone took a list of sordid elements and stuffed them all into a crime thriller so twisty it could only be fiction.
But the tortuous tale of the Murdaughs, a prominent South Carolina family with shadowy secrets, is real. And it's far from over.
The story took a fresh turn this week when investigators arrested patriarch Alex Murdaugh for allegedly hiring a hit man to kill him in a failed attempt to collect millions in life insurance for his surviving son, Buster. This came three months after Murdaugh's wife and other son were gunned down on the family's secluded estate.
These events led authorities to open investigations into several other mysterious deaths -- dating back years -- with apparent ties to the Murdaughs.
Now the family's legacy of influence is crumbling and the rural area around Hampton, some 75 miles west of Charleston, is buzzing with theories. The evolving saga has inspired at least one podcast and gripped amateur sleuths around the state -- and the nation.
#MartinSavidge #CNN #Newsroom</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="692" average="4.80" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="14239"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:o8sBzbnTfXU</id>
  <yt:videoId>o8sBzbnTfXU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Smerconish: What social media doesn't show us about Gabby Petito's life</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o8sBzbnTfXU"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-18T18:58:07+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T18:58:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Smerconish: What social media doesn't show us about Gabby Petito's life</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/o8sBzbnTfXU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/o8sBzbnTfXU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>CNN's Michael Smerconish says new revelations about the negative effects of Instagram and social media made him think about the case of Gabby Petito, the 22-year-old who has not been heard from since going on a road trip with her fiance.

#Smerconish #GabbyPetito #CNN</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="1496" average="4.75" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="36703"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:G0a7Age0hlA</id>
  <yt:videoId>G0a7Age0hlA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Are JLo and Ben Affleck headed for married bliss?</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G0a7Age0hlA"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-18T17:39:53+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T17:51:53+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Are JLo and Ben Affleck headed for married bliss?</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/G0a7Age0hlA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/G0a7Age0hlA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Are Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck going to be Bennifer 2.0 forever? Has Britney Spears gotten “Lucky” with her engagement to Sam Asghari or is the relationship “Toxic”? In this episode of “Pop Off,” CNN entertainment reporter Lisa Respers France discusses the celebrity couples who are taking their summer romances into fall. She also talks to the stars of Apple TV+’s “The Morning Show,” Billy Crudup and Hasan Minhaj. And for all the Lambs out there: we pop back to the #JusticeforGlitter movement, remembering Mariah Carey’s infamous “Glitter” 20 years after the movie and soundtrack released. 

Watch “Pop Off&quot; with Lisa for a sassy, no-nonsense take on entertainment and real life's biggest issues every Saturday on CNN’s YouTube channel.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="591" average="3.77" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="12884"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:GLpyOuqpcPI</id>
  <yt:videoId>GLpyOuqpcPI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Bodycam footage raises more questions about missing woman</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GLpyOuqpcPI"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-18T00:16:27+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T10:35:26+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Bodycam footage raises more questions about missing woman</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/GLpyOuqpcPI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/GLpyOuqpcPI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>CNN has obtained the bodycam footage from the Moab Police Department that shows Gabby Petito and her boyfriend Brian Laundrie after they were pulled over by police last month. CNN's Athena Jones reports.

#CNN #News</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="3249" average="4.75" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="181293"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:z_qMkrxCqOw</id>
  <yt:videoId>z_qMkrxCqOw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Georgia prosecutor quietly pursues case against Trump</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z_qMkrxCqOw"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-18T00:14:41+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T10:31:00+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Georgia prosecutor quietly pursues case against Trump</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/z_qMkrxCqOw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/z_qMkrxCqOw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Criminal investigators in Georgia have been quietly conducting interviews, collecting documents and working to build a line of communication with congressional investigators as they aim to build a case against former President Donald Trump for his alleged attempts to overturn the state's 2020 presidential election results.

#CNN #News</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="10455" average="4.73" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="432409"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:UB4Yxp05LMw</id>
  <yt:videoId>UB4Yxp05LMw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>'A mistake': US admits it killed 10 civilians in Kabul drone strike</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UB4Yxp05LMw"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-17T20:24:30+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T07:18:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>'A mistake': US admits it killed 10 civilians in Kabul drone strike</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/UB4Yxp05LMw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/UB4Yxp05LMw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>A United States military investigation into a deadly Kabul drone strike on a vehicle in August has found it killed 10 civilians and the driver and that the vehicle targeted was likely not a threat associated with ISIS-K, announced Gen. Frank McKenzie, the top general of US Central Command, at the Pentagon on Friday.
McKenzie told reporters that the strike was a &quot;mistake&quot; and offered an apology.
&quot;This strike was taken in the earnest belief that it would prevent an imminent threat to our forces and the evacuees at the airport, but it was a mistake and I offer my sincere apology,&quot; he said.
McKenzie added that he is &quot;fully responsible for this strike and this tragic outcome.&quot;
The Pentagon had maintained that at least one ISIS-K facilitator and three civilians were killed in what Chairman of the Joint Chiefs Gen. Mark Milley had previously called a &quot;righteous strike&quot; on the compound on August 29. The investigation released Friday found that all of those killed in the residential compound were civilians.
In the lead up to the strike, drone operators surveilled the courtyard for up to 4 to 5 minutes. In that time, a male driver left the vehicle. One child was parking the vehicle and other children were present in the car and the courtyard -- as CNN had been told by the Ahmadi family.

#CNN #News</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="4391" average="2.10" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="168522"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:sAp8hEEVeoo</id>
  <yt:videoId>sAp8hEEVeoo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Pence weighs 2024 presidential run amid rocky relationship with Trump</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sAp8hEEVeoo"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-17T19:43:09+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T10:35:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Pence weighs 2024 presidential run amid rocky relationship with Trump</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/sAp8hEEVeoo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/sAp8hEEVeoo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Mike Pence is adding staffers for his brand-new office in downtown Washington -- inching closer to a possible White House run even as his standing worsens with former President Donald Trump and his base of supporters.
The former vice president's ramp-up comes as Trump appears to be making good on his declaration to Pence that &quot;I don't want to be your friend anymore.&quot; That quote, first reported this week, is attributed to Trump in a forthcoming book by journalists Bob Woodward and Robert Costa.
The last conversation between the two Republican leaders was a phone call from Trump in April, Republican sources tell CNN, wishing Pence well as the former vice president recovered from heart surgery.
Pence isn't waiting to make up with his former running mate -- nor is he waiting for the former President to make up his own mind about his political future. People around Pence rejected the idea that he would hold off on his 2024 planning until Trump announces whether he'll run.
&quot;Mike is going to look at this and say, 'Where am I being called to serve?' &quot; said one person close to Pence. &quot;That's not going to be thwarted by any man or woman.&quot;
&quot;If he feels called to do this,&quot; the adviser went on, &quot;it's not going to be because of who else is in the race.&quot;
#MichaelWarren #CNN #InsidePolitics</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="1888" average="4.29" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="114632"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:3TxQjgjJAE8</id>
  <yt:videoId>3TxQjgjJAE8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Republican cites 'toxic'' GOP as main reason he will not run in 2022</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3TxQjgjJAE8"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-17T19:15:47+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T18:02:56+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Republican cites 'toxic'' GOP as main reason he will not run in 2022</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/3TxQjgjJAE8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/3TxQjgjJAE8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Rep. Anthony Gonzalez of Ohio, one of 10 House Republicans who voted to impeach former President Donald Trump earlier this year, announced Thursday that he will not run for reelection in 2022.
&quot;While my desire to build a fuller family life is at the heart of my decision, it is also true that the current state of our politics, especially many of the toxic dynamics inside our own party, is a significant factor in my decision,&quot; Gonzalez said in a statement.
Gonzalez had previously argued that Trump's rhetoric at the &quot;Stop the Steal&quot; rally ahead of the insurrection on January 6 and the fact that the former President did little to stop those actions swayed him to back the impeachment charges. That decision unearthed profound anger in his northeast Ohio district, kicking off a localized fight over the future of the Republican Party that pit the two-term congressman against irate constituents eager to expel any member of the party who crossed the former President.
Trump, for his part, campaigned against the lawmaker in June, rallying for primary opponent Max Miller, a former Trump aide, in his first return to the campaign trail after the January 6 attack on the US Capitol.
Trump said in a statement Friday that Gonzalez &quot;decided to quit after enduring a tremendous loss of popularity&quot; following the impeachment vote.
Wyoming Rep. Liz Cheney, another one of the 10 House Republicans who voted for impeachment, said the former President's statement about Gonzalez &quot;reminds us all, once again, that Trump is at war with the Constitution.&quot;
The Ohio Republican Party Central Committee had voted in May to censure Gonzalez and call for his resignation.
A former NFL player first elected to the House in 2018, Gonzalez was one of only 35 House Republicans who voted later that month to establish an independent commission to investigate the insurrection, which Senate Republicans later blocked.
#CNN #News #InsidePolitics</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="4435" average="3.79" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="168365"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:mhYrmZHP-EY</id>
  <yt:videoId>mhYrmZHP-EY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Reporter shares shocking aerial footage of US border crisis</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mhYrmZHP-EY"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-17T18:05:28+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T10:32:51+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Reporter shares shocking aerial footage of US border crisis</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/mhYrmZHP-EY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mhYrmZHP-EY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>More than 9,500 migrants, many of them Haitians fleeing a country torn apart by a coup and an earthquake, have arrived at the US border and are living under a bridge near Texas. Thousands of additional migrants are expected to arrive at the border in the coming days. CNN's Rosa Flores got an exclusive aerial tour of the area.

#RosaFlores #CNN #ErinBurnettOutFront</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="3497" average="3.91" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="181709"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:KfJ1UvKoPaY</id>
  <yt:videoId>KfJ1UvKoPaY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Keilar: GOP supports right-wing rally even if they won't be there</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KfJ1UvKoPaY"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-17T17:50:37+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T10:55:51+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Keilar: GOP supports right-wing rally even if they won't be there</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/KfJ1UvKoPaY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/KfJ1UvKoPaY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>CNN's Brianna Keilar says that despite Republicans keeping the upcoming right-wing rally to support those arrested in the January 6 capitol riot at arms length, their public rhetoric shows they support the ideas behind the event.
#CNN #News #BriannaKeilar</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="5365" average="4.68" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="232534"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:nBsXXSBHWNU</id>
  <yt:videoId>nBsXXSBHWNU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>This Citizen-style app helps keep Afghans in Kabul safe</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nBsXXSBHWNU"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-17T14:15:45+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T07:40:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>This Citizen-style app helps keep Afghans in Kabul safe</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/nBsXXSBHWNU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/nBsXXSBHWNU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Ehtesab -- which roughly translates to &quot;accountability&quot; -- is an Afghan-created app that verifies instances of explosions, power outages, checkpoints, and other need-to-know information in Kabul. Since the Taliban took control of the city, the app has seen a surge in downloads.

Produced by John General
Supervising Producer: Logan Whiteside

#CNN
#Kabul
#Afghanistan</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="654" average="4.17" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="19347"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:stBnP5ZxjTc</id>
  <yt:videoId>stBnP5ZxjTc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Don Lemon: Trump and GOP have poisoned the US electoral system</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=stBnP5ZxjTc"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T17:26:40+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T16:18:58+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Don Lemon: Trump and GOP have poisoned the US electoral system</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/stBnP5ZxjTc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/stBnP5ZxjTc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>CNN's Don Lemon says that the American electoral has been poisoned by Donald Trump's election lie that is now baked into the Republican party.
#CNN #DonLemon #DonLemonTonight</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="8527" average="4.07" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="238852"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:7_txZZH9i_8</id>
  <yt:videoId>7_txZZH9i_8</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>School district bans books on Rosa Parks and Malala. Now students want answers</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7_txZZH9i_8"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T17:15:17+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T15:20:18+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>School district bans books on Rosa Parks and Malala. Now students want answers</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/7_txZZH9i_8?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7_txZZH9i_8/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Students in a southern Pennsylvania school district are battling the latest example of panic spreading over how history and race are taught in schools across the US.
&quot;I don't think a moral compass will let you ban books about equality and loving each other,&quot; Central York High School senior Christina Ellis told CNN.
Ellis is among the students protesting a book ban in York, Pennsylvania, and questions whether the officials who decided to remove certain reading materials from the curriculum even read the resources they deem controversial. She was joined by other teens protesting in front of Central York High School this week.
On Monday, students, parents and other community members debated during a virtual school board meeting about the list of anti-racism books and resources that were banned from the curriculum by the Central York school board last year.
Last October, the all-White school board unanimously banned a list of educational resources that included a children's book about Rosa Parks, Malala Yousafzai's autobiography and CNN's Sesame Street town hall on racism. CNN's Evan McMorris-Santoro reports.

#CNN #Evan McMorrisSantoro #DonLemonTonight</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="4944" average="4.76" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="155615"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:pC4JDpDkRZg</id>
  <yt:videoId>pC4JDpDkRZg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Cooper: Milley's concerns about Trump remarkable, but not surprising</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pC4JDpDkRZg"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T16:09:00+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-18T16:26:31+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Cooper: Milley's concerns about Trump remarkable, but not surprising</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/pC4JDpDkRZg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pC4JDpDkRZg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>CNN's Anderson Cooper says that Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff Gen. Mark Milley's concern about former President Donald Trump reported in &quot;Peril,&quot; a forthcoming book by Washington Post reporters Bob Woodward and Robert Costa are remarkable, but not surprising because past Trump officials have raised similar concerns.
#AndersonCooper #AC360 #CNN</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="1935" average="4.09" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="74230"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:R_V8RV6WibY</id>
  <yt:videoId>R_V8RV6WibY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</yt:channelId>
  <title>A dead housekeeper and a hitman: Murdaugh family mystery gets more strange</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R_V8RV6WibY"/>
  <author>
   <name>CNN</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCupvZG-5ko_eiXAupbDfxWw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2021-09-16T16:04:17+00:00</published>
  <updated>2021-09-17T11:53:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>A dead housekeeper and a hitman: Murdaugh family mystery gets more strange</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/R_V8RV6WibY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/R_V8RV6WibY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Alex Murdaugh, the South Carolina lawyer whose wife and son were shot and killed in June, plans to voluntarily surrender to police  on charges related to a subsequent insurance fraud scheme, his lawyer told CNN.
According to court documents, Murdaugh arranged for a former client to kill him so that his surviving son could collect a life insurance payout of about $10 million.
One of Murdaugh's lawyers, Jim Griffin, told CNN that they have been informed an arrest warrant has been issued for Murdaugh on charges of conspiracy to commit insurance fraud. Murdaugh plans to voluntarily surrender at the Hampton County jail by 2 p.m., according to Griffin.
Murdaugh was shot in the head on a roadway September 4 but survived. A family spokesperson had previously blamed the shooting on an unidentified man in a blue truck. However, Murdaugh admitted to authorities Monday that he had conspired with a man -- identified by police as Curtis Edward Smith -- to kill him as part of the scheme, according to an affidavit to support charges against Smith.
Murdaugh decided to end his own life but believed his life insurance policy had a suicide exclusion, his other attorney Dick Harpootlian said, and that the scheme &quot;was an attempt on his part to do something to protect&quot; his eldest and only living child.
Additionally, state investigators have announced the opening of two other investigations regarding the 2015 unsolved death of a teen as well as the 2018 death of the Murdaugh family's housekeeper.
The killings of his wife and son on June 7 have not been solved, and Murdaugh has denied responsibility.

#CNN #News</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="1343" average="4.54" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="97465"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
