<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 19:32:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Message from Kim Jong-un amid speculation</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Some signs of life have emerged from the North Korean presidency after weeks of speculation on the health of the country's leader, Kim Jong-un.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/message-from-kim-jongun-amid-speculation/news-story/7456df843da187b99463095c17ed8a26</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Afghan men reject virus social distancing</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Afghan authorities are struggling to impose lockdowns to prevent the spread of the coronavirus in a province bordering Iran where the outbreak is widening due to an influx of Afghan returnees and men refusing to adhere to social distancing.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/afghan-men-reject-virus-social-distancing/news-story/f914bcc3137f897a0ece81a9243aca40</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Spanish children allowed out after weeks</title>
		<description><![CDATA[On foot, on skateboards and on scooters, Spanish children have emerged from their homes for the first time after six long weeks of living under one of Europe's strictest coronavirus lockdowns.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/spanish-children-allowed-out-after-weeks/news-story/285e253533bcfcd63ae8f4d7e09deeff</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Trump scraps virus briefing for second day</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The White House coronavirus task force will not hold a briefing for the second consecutive day, as US President Donald Trump takes a break from the spotlight.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/trump-scraps-virus-briefing-for-second-day/news-story/c8407379ef8a033220d29456ede1a99d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Who might replace Kim Jong-un?</title>
		<description><![CDATA[North Korea has never announced who would follow leader Kim Jong-un in the event he is incapacitated, and with no details known about his young children, analysts say his sister and loyalists could form a regency until a successor is old enough to take over.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/who-might-replace-kim-jongun/news-story/37fa0310e90d32d8b650abaf10f3277d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>UK has no lockdown exit strategy in sight</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Britain's stand-in leader has resisted pressure to explain how the government plans to ease a coronavirus lockdown that has been in place for a month, warning that hasty action could result in a second peak of infections.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/uk-has-no-lockdown-exit-strategy-in-sight/news-story/be8dee9a81b86ae394a46c6b1e367803</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>UK PM Boris Johnson back at Downing St</title>
		<description><![CDATA[British Prime Minister Boris Johnson is back at his Downing St office after recovering from COVID-19.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/uk-pm-boris-johnson-back-at-downing-st/news-story/805dbe6d53476e091196e95e691f0434</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Indonesia reports 23 new virus deaths</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Indonesia has reported 275 new coronavirus cases, raising the total to 8882, data provided by health ministry official Achmad Yurianto shows.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/indonesia-reports-23-new-virus-deaths/news-story/30c2d60dfeb765a1ee0a6a9554646885</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Top cop killed in horror city crash</title>
		<description><![CDATA[One of South Australia’s top-ranking and most decorated police officers has been killed in a horrific high-speed crash that also claimed the life of another woman.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/adelaide-crash-horrific-multivehicle-collision-on-cross-rd-urrbrae/news-story/a90b8596f9d5c92c5b7788da17d9c98d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Tenth virus death in Tas, one new case</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A 90-year-old man from Tasmania's coronavirus-hit northwest has become the tenth person in the state to die from COVID-19.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/tenth-virus-death-in-tasmania/news-story/80f03b6a51543bf67a4bc1351402ea47</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>