<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 19:28:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Deadly cyclone cuts power to 5m homes</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Millions are in darkness in Bangladesh's coastal districts after fierce winds and rains triggered by cyclone Amphan snapped the power supply to the region, according to the head of Bangladesh's Rural Electricity Board.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/deadly-cyclone-cuts-power-to-5m-homes/news-story/aeaf7ac805248fa14d6b4bacb109f789</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Egypt takes 1% from salary for virus fund</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Egypt will deduct 1.0 per cent from people's salaries for 12 months beginning on July 1 to offset the economic repercussions of the coronavirus, according to a draft law approved by the cabinet.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/egypt-takes-1-from-salary-for-virus-fund/news-story/9d53cb025b486539149f19c23000f3ce</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Philippines &#8216;illegal health facility&#8217; shut</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Philippine police have shut down an illegal health facility and pharmacy that allegedly treated Chinese citizens suspected of being infected with the coronavirus, officials say.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/philippines-illegal-health-facility-shut/news-story/fcbf11b71edf65f62c04095b96ec5beb</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US watchdog firing not retaliation: Pompeo</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has declined to say why he recommended firing the State Department's inspector general, but added he should have done it earlier and rejected claims his decision was motivated by political retaliation.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-watchdog-firing-not-retaliation-pompeo/news-story/83dd5c54a6bcc1c5de7be3b51b87b52c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Twitter trials user control of replies</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Twitter is testing new settings which will allow users to control who is allowed to reply to their posts on the social media platform, a potential major change.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/twitter-trials-user-control-of-replies/news-story/23e0183cf6afafc2460e37523348472d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China barley row to benefit France, Canada</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A prohibitive Chinese import tariff on Australian barley will benefit other suppliers without changing the bleak global outlook caused by large stocks and depressed beer demand, analysts and traders say.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-barley-row-to-benefit-france-canada/news-story/7ea59d8d30ace0b3187eebc67c7fc6b8</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Romanian president fined for minority joke</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A Romanian discrimination watchdog has fined President Klaus Iohannis over a remark seen as abusive toward the country's Hungarian minority.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/romanian-president-fined-for-minority-joke/news-story/9d2a0c2f53a1cc5dd9733339bad4b832</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Italy daily coronavirus death toll steady</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Deaths from the COVID-19 epidemic in Italy has climbed by 161 against 162 the day before, the Civil Protection Agency says, while the daily tally of new cases fell to 665 from 813 on the prior day.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/italy-daily-coronavirus-death-toll-steady/news-story/5cd6d122120af94fe3e83b349bc456f2</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Virus peak appears to have passed: Russia</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Russia appears to have passed the peak of its wave of coronavirus infections, enabling authorities to "cautiously remove" quarantine restrictions, Prime Minister Mikhail Mishustin says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/virus-peak-appears-to-have-passed-russia/news-story/5a42507477265831a2ec6cddcb7bd6bb</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rwanda genocide suspect seeks France trial</title>
		<description><![CDATA[One of the most wanted fugitives in Rwanda's 1994 genocide, Felicien Kabuga, has appeared before a French court days after his arrest but a decision on his fate has been delayed until next week.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/rwanda-genocide-suspect-seeks-france-trial/news-story/8597a818b50c0d0addf73af58aa6969e</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>