<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 04:41:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Protests rock US over Floyd&#8217;s arrest death</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Demonstrators marched, stopped traffic and in some cases lashed out violently at police as protests erupted Friday in dozens of U.S. cities following the killing of George Floyd after a white officer pressed a knee into his neck while taking him into custody in Minnesota. In Phoenix, Denver, Las Vegas, Los Angeles and beyond, thousands of protesters carried signs that said: "He said I can't breathe. Justice for George." They chanted ""No justice, no peace" and "Say his name. George Floyd."]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-protesters-torch-police-station/news-story/c192f51a394a71a485f81a43a49c4310</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Weinstein faces new rape claims</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein, currently serving a 23 year prison term for rape, has been hit with a new lawsuit that claims he raped an additional four women, one of whom was just 17 years old at the time.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/weinstein-faces-new-rape-claims/news-story/794f66b892f5eadf02248bb219bf1322</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Traditional owners lash Rio heritage claim</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Traditional owners in Western Australia's north have criticised Rio Tinto's "outrageous" public response after it destroyed a significant indigenous site dating back 46,000 years.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/traditional-owners-lash-rio-heritage-claim/news-story/169177eb4b541304b5a279c9e797482d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Qld man critical after shooting</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A man is in critical condition after being shot in the stomach during a confrontation in north Queensland.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/qld-man-critical-after-shooting/news-story/7236a0a415e4568c25ceb28638ce6cc2</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Anti-vax protesters defy restrictions</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Hundreds of anti-vaccination protesters have defied social-distancing measures at rallies across Australia.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/antivax-protesters-defy-restrictions/news-story/bae847a2971fe78e0c2f24839d1ab4e2</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Restrictions ease as holidays begin</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The easing of COVID-19 restrictions will be put to the test over this and next weekend as Australians enjoy public holidays.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/australia-makes-progress-on-virus-response/news-story/928872be5ff4aa79db74fa174fdbad75</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US officer on murder charge over Floyd</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The white Minneapolis police officer who pressed his knee into George Floyd's neck has been arrested and charged with murder, as authorities impose overnight curfews to try to stem violent protests over police killings of African Americans that have spread from Minneapolis and other US cities.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-officer-ignored-fellow-cops-concerns/news-story/e39a83a986a6e343015aa2e17138844b</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>More COVID cases from Vic school, hotel</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Nearly a dozen new coronavirus cases have been confirmed in Victoria, including three more cases linked to a Melbourne school and four from a hotel used to quarantine returned travellers.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/victoria-high-school-students-in-isolation/news-story/02b4573f54fc70783aaffbf5cc0aac67</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US &#8216;terminating&#8217; relationship with WHO</title>
		<description><![CDATA[With new US economic numbers highlighting the rough road ahead for a hoped-for rebound, President Donald Trump has taken aim at the World Health Organisation and China, blaming both for their roles in the pandemic's devastation.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-terminating-relationship-with-who/news-story/019d0f7b7faa85e86240b82f08780a63</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Zero new cases in Qld as sewage tested</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Scientists will sift through the sewage of a central Queensland town to try and determine the source of a COVID-19 infection that claimed the life of a 30-year-old man.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/blackwater-sewage-tested-for-virus-source/news-story/d594d952d400d09e47aa4aaede9f60f0</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>