<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 03:40:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Trump says China wants him to lose US vote</title>
		<description><![CDATA[President Donald Trump says China's handling of the coronavirus is proof that Beijing "will do anything they can" to make him lose his re-election bid in November.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/trump-says-china-wants-him-to-lose-us-vote/news-story/dff16fae0640bc914ea73d49a6dae38a</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s factory activity unexpectedly dips</title>
		<description><![CDATA[China's factory activity unexpectedly shrank in April, a private-sector survey showed, as the coronavirus pandemic shattered global demand, causing a substantial drop in export orders and more layoffs.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/chinas-factory-activity-expands-in-april/news-story/150b331a89c065368cfe48afa8f25d38</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Person crushed to death at Vic business</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A person has been crushed to death at a Melbourne stone supplier business.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/person-crushed-to-death-at-vic-business/news-story/f20c464bc48bc20cdf513914e8f0e74f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>COVID gold surge boosts Aust export prices</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Investors turning to safe-haven bullion and soaring demand for scrap metal helped push Australian export prices higher during a COVID-affected March quarter, but this was offset by softer petrol demand amid widespread lockdowns.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/covid-gold-surge-boosts-aust-export-prices/news-story/9d6be88f0b72166acb16cd9d55a43827</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Newcrest announces $1.1b capital raising</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Australia's largest listed goldminer has announced a $1.1 billion equity raising, in part to fund its $US460 million ($A703 million) further stake in a goldmine in southeast Ecuador.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/newcrest-announces-11b-capital-raising/news-story/3267712e20699063b3ae8335053b0d1f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Tesla profit up, Musk hits out at lockdown</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Tesla has reported a small first-quarter net profit as its CEO ranted about the legality of government stay-home orders issued to prevent the coronavirus from spreading.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/tesla-profit-up-musk-hits-out-at-lockdown/news-story/dec9952d253940a2d4301ddaccc09fa3</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Facebook cites ad sales drop due to virus</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Facebook has reported "a significant reduction in the demand for advertising" over the last three weeks of the first quarter of 2020, although the social media giant says that had stabilised in the first part of April.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/facebook-cites-ad-sales-drop-due-to-virus/news-story/ca6232911b3a0f4837f4f2dd9aae4211</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Data on drug raises hopes in virus fight</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The United States' top infectious disease official says experimental antiviral drug remdesivir will become the standard of care for COVID-19 after early results from a key clinical trial showed it helped patients recover more quickly from the illness caused by the coronavirus.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-expert-fauci-upbeat-on-virus-drug/news-story/94548a97a8382867c791fc482f6e6b8c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>UK virus death toll 2nd-highest in Europe</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The United Kingdom now has Europe's second-highest official death toll from the coronavirus pandemic, according to new figures that cover fatalities in all settings including in nursing homes.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/uk-virus-death-toll-2ndhighest-in-europe/news-story/988ffa04a26d1d852524cfd2cb86b36a</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>French virus death toll rises above 24,000</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The number of people who have died from the coronavirus infection in France has risen by 427 to 24,087, with the rate of increase slightly speeding up again after slowing on previous day, the health ministry says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/french-virus-death-toll-rises-above-24000/news-story/8403f40d6c41f0e316d58375d2d54033</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>