<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Latest News and News Headlines | Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 15:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress/5.8.1" -->

	<item>
		<title>BTS dance through UN to promote youth solutions for planet</title>
		<description><![CDATA[It wasn't exactly the screaming audience BTS is accustomed to but the Korean pop sensations had another sort of world stage Monday as they addressed the United Nations.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/bts-dance-through-un-to-promote-youth-solutions-for-planet/news-story/fc6165f740a7f53a70a26d266a8bcf49</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>&#8216;Hotel Rwanda&#8217; hero sentenced to 25 years on terror charges</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Paul Rusesabagina, the "Hotel Rwanda" hero who became a fiercely outspoken government critic, was sentenced on Monday to 25 years in prison on terrorism charges after what his supporters labelled a politically motivated show trial.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/hotel-rwanda-hero-to-learn-verdict-in-terror-trial/news-story/78240ef4dfcc128d1f94befa9b8f370a</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Shock at Russia university campus as gunman kills six</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A gunman killed six people on a university campus in Russia on Monday before being detained, investigators said, leaving students and teachers shaken and terrified.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/six-dead-after-gunman-opens-fire-on-russian-campus/news-story/e107aafeb83a363a1fc72d684b0a2a2b</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Russia opposition claims mass fraud after Putin party sweeps vote</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Russia's opposition accused the authorities of mass voter fraud after election results Monday showed the ruling United Russia party winning a sweeping majority in parliament.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/putins-party-set-to-retain-parliament-majority-after-polls/news-story/a3bd2b0ec332a40c289fc82127a7b7a5</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Global stocks sink on Evergrande contagion fears</title>
		<description><![CDATA[World stocks sank Monday as trading floors were gripped by contagion fears from the expected collapse of debt-plagued Chinese property giant Evergrande, with investors also on red alert over spiking wholesale gas costs.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/hong-kong-leads-equity-selloff-as-evergrande-fears-spread/news-story/ac24d651f05578bbbde2507e26695251</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lava engulfs 100 homes as Canary Islands volcano erupts</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A surge of lava destroyed around 100 homes on Spain's Canary Islands a day after a volcano erupted, forcing 5,500 people to leave the area, local authorities said on Monday. ]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/lava-engulfs-100-homes-as-canary-islands-volcano-erupts/news-story/2a8db2dc423635ea75088b9c29ef71d5</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US to end travel bans for vaccinated passengers</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The United States announced Monday it will lift Covid travel bans on all air passengers in November if they are fully vaccinated and undergo testing and contact tracing.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-to-end-travel-bans-for-vaccinated-passengers/news-story/cba85ff4440caa2b9c283618525f5035</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Trudeau future on the line as Canadians vote in pandemic election</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Voters lined up Monday to cast ballots in Canadian elections that are headed for a photo finish, with liberal Prime Minister Justin Trudeau's bid for a third term threatened by rookie conservative leader Erin O'Toole's strong challenge.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/trudeau-future-on-the-line-as-canadians-vote-in-pandemic-election/news-story/01b00b2c6375f810101054b20ef53d29</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Afghan women outraged by new Taliban restrictions on work</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Fears were mounting in Afghanistan on Monday as the Taliban tightened their grip on women's rights, slashing access to work and denying girls the right to secondary school education.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/afghan-women-outraged-by-new-taliban-restrictions-on-work/news-story/115ad10cac175a87100a34d4d6b5f3a9</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US to lift Covid travel ban for vaccinated EU, UK passengers: reports</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The United States will lift an 18-month-old travel ban on the European Union and Britain, allowing vaccinated travelers to enter beginning in November, reports said Monday.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-to-lift-covid-travel-ban-for-vaccinated-eu-uk-passengers-reports/news-story/b0585661662d72fd424b22f71686ac5c</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>
