<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 21:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Huawei CFO loses key court fight in Canada</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Huawei's chief financial officer Meng Wanzhou has been dealt a setback by a Canadian court as she tries to avoid extradition to the US to face bank fraud charges.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/huawei-cfo-loses-key-court-fight-in-canada/news-story/ff1c1a13f5b3775fbaad9eae89b18a05</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Dinosaurs &#8216;may have been cannibals&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Carnivorous dinosaurs that roamed the planet 150 million years ago may have resorted to cannibalism when food was scarce, scientists believe.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/dinosaurs-may-have-been-cannibals/news-story/27d5cf0727322448c4853bd08b737d0c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>NT Labor backflips on state of finances</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The Northern Territory government will try to provide financial forecasts before the August election after previously ruling it out due to the coronavirus pandemic.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/nt-labor-backflips-on-state-of-finances/news-story/4648a5455b50eeb3d9c6bfc99d47b529</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>New crew may fly in to move WA virus ship</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A replacement crew could be sent to Western Australia to sail a livestock carrier back to the Middle East before the northern summer ban, with sending the sheep to local abattoirs considered a last resort.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/new-crew-may-fly-in-to-move-wa-virus-ship/news-story/40d01aaae92433fc0f0ebf9269054eb8</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Aust, UK to start free trade deal talks</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Australia will soon begin talks for a "gold-standard" free trade deal with the United Kingdom.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/aust-uk-to-start-free-trade-deal-talks/news-story/002cdf8d6854824f9383fb18a8187459</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rwanda&#8217;s Kabuga says charges are &#8216;lies&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Rwandan genocide suspect Felicien Kabuga has called the charges against him "lies" as he appeared before the Paris Court of Appeal.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/rwandan-genocide-suspect-in-paris-court/news-story/7d5dd9397fe7f094efb163b92f84a73b</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Hong Kong anthem bill spurs protests</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Hong Kong police have fired pepper pellets and made 300 arrests as thousands of people took to the streets to voice anger over national security laws proposed by China, that has raised international alarm over freedoms in the city.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-expands-hong-kong-security-laws/news-story/567de412a84adab023e3a8bb217dae22</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>NASA set to resume human spaceflight</title>
		<description><![CDATA[SpaceX, the private rocket company of billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk, is set to launch two Americans into orbit from Florida on a mission that would mark the first spaceflight of NASA astronauts from US soil in nine years.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/weather-better-for-spacex-astronaut-launch/news-story/a275b00440c74b6dcca6db6829392fde</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Article weight-shamed me: Mehajer lawyer</title>
		<description><![CDATA[In a claim describing Salim Mehajer as one of Australia's most disliked people, a high-profile defence lawyer says a Sydney gossip column made out she sleeps with clients and unfairly exposed her to ridicule for her manner of dress and weight.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/gossip-column-weightshamed-me-lawyer/news-story/3253ca560f4c91c57d4da0828f4fc4b9</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>SpaceX set for debut astronaut mission</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Entrepreneur Elon Musk's SpaceX is set to launch two American astronauts to the International Space Station from NASA's Kennedy Space Center in Florida, ending the US space agency's nine-year hiatus in human spaceflight.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/spacex-set-for-debut-astronaut-mission/news-story/3aa43f67823e3bedbb885bc5efb3e7d3</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>