<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 18:55:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>US demonstrators vow to sustain momentum</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US protesters stirred by the death of George Floyd have vowed to turn an extraordinary outpouring of grief into a sustained movement as demonstrations shifted to a calmer, but no less determined, focus on addressing racial injustice.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-demonstrators-vow-to-sustain-momentum/news-story/67e7aa6095a87b792e6e0ba61da86bc5</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China warns against travel to Australia</title>
		<description><![CDATA[China's Ministry of Culture and Tourism has advised the public to avoid travelling to Australia, citing racial discrimination and violence against Chinese people in connection with the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-warns-against-travel-to-australia/news-story/75066feb7fd371a97e062f4845e5d6b4</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US street renamed Black Lives Matter Plaza</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Washington DC mayor Muriel Bowser has renamed a street in front of the White House "Black Lives Matter Plaza" and had the slogan painted in huge yellow letters on the roadway in an apparent rebuke of US President Donald Trump's militaristic response to protests over police brutality.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-street-renamed-black-lives-matter-plaza/news-story/b05fd0e7a0cf922d93288cc6b038472d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Italy has 85 virus deaths, 518 new cases</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Deaths from the COVID-19 epidemic in Italy have climbed by 85 against 88 the day before, the Civil Protection Agency says, while the daily tally of new cases jumped to 518 from 177 on the prior day.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/italy-has-85-virus-deaths-518-new-cases/news-story/7c0d35fc075adc414ce8e304e76c7d0e</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Seven bodies found inside burning US house</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US police responding to a call about a shooting in Alabama have found seven people dead inside a home that had been set on fire, local media reports say.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/seven-bodies-found-inside-burning-us-house/news-story/94ccd187f517595e440469c7a781a26e</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Wear masks in public, WHO says in update</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The World Health Organisation has updated its guidance to recommend that governments ask everyone to wear fabric face masks in public areas where there is a risk of transmission of COVID-19 to help reduce the spread of the pandemic disease.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/wear-masks-in-public-who-says-in-update/news-story/cc7bbe25ab1e94bb3f0a2b78e4755fe1</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US air strikes hit Taliban in Afghanistan</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US forces have carried out two sets of air strikes against the Taliban, in western and southern Afghanistan, a US military spokesman says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-air-strikes-hit-taliban-in-afghanistan/news-story/3175be5e020115efdfb4a68b64f52d99</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>&#8216;Not over til no virus in the world&#8217;: WHO</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Some countries have seen "upticks" in COVID-19 cases as lockdowns ease, and populations must continue to protect themselves against the coronavirus, the World Health Organization (WHO) says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/not-over-til-no-virus-in-the-world-who/news-story/daa11357775128b5128378bd84c658ba</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Car maker Bentley to cut up to 1000 jobs</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Bentley is to cut up to 1000 jobs under a "voluntary release program" and cannot rule out future compulsory redundancies, the luxury car maker has announced.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/car-maker-bentley-to-cut-up-to-1000-jobs/news-story/8285f76e7d2066064176c7cf5835a2ed</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>California mayor quits over &#8216;racist&#8217; email</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The mayor of a Southern California city has resigned following an email in which he stated he didn't "believe there's ever been a good person of colour killed by a police officer" locally.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/california-mayor-quits-over-racist-email/news-story/97749723d9976bbaa137784631aab329</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>