<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 19:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>No cases in China, virus spikes elsewhere</title>
		<description><![CDATA[New coronavirus cases in China have fallen to zero for the first time but surged in India and overwhelmed hospitals across Latin America - both in countries lax about lockdowns and those lauded for firm, early confinement.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/no-cases-in-china-virus-spikes-elsewhere/news-story/da03037c506a3115f4e3c09b4455b3d4</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China &#8216;may set up HK intelligence agency&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[China's new national security legislation may be used to establish a domestic intelligence agency in Hong Kong similar to the colonial-era Special Branch, the territory's former leader Leung Chun-ying says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-may-set-up-hk-intelligence-agency/news-story/bb0ed41b4483ec20ea5f74f722f41d68</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>French virus patients continue to decrease</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The number of people in hospital with coronavirus in France has fallen by 205 to 17,178, continuing a gradual decline that has lasted more than five weeks since a high of 32,292 on April 14.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/french-virus-patients-continue-to-decrease/news-story/b165df143787b74fb027363b8f067c08</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Ukraine MP found shot dead in his office</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A Ukrainian MP has been found shot dead in his office, the deputy interior minister Anton Gerashchenko says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/ukraine-mp-found-shot-dead-in-his-office/news-story/b9ad3e3893a8861f1417ced3712a31cb</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Pandemic teaches humility: US justice</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US chief Justice John Roberts has told graduating seniors at his son's high school that the coronavirus has "pierced our illusion of certainty and control" and he counselled the students to make their way with humility, compassion and courage in a world turned upside down.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/pandemic-teaches-humility-us-justice/news-story/a02bacdc5c4b32860c62ad24b21ce5bf</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Italy&#8217;s daily coronavirus death toll dips</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Italy has recorded 119 new deaths from the COVID-19 epidemic against 130 the day before, the Civil Protection Agency says, while the daily tally of new cases rose marginally to 669 from 652 on the prior day.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/italys-daily-coronavirus-death-toll-dips/news-story/13f83698a42297f9830d7a03cb08d8e1</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Amphan death toll hits 100 amid protests</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The death toll from cyclone Amphan in India and Bangladesh has exceeded 100 as thousands of residents in the eastern metropolis of Kolkata held protests and road blockades over the failure to have power and drinking water supplies restored.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/amphan-death-toll-hits-100-amid-protests/news-story/e6701c6e0d57d01913eac106ef39a96f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Man takes hostage in Russian bank branch</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A man has taken at least one hostage in a bank branch in Moscow, threatening an explosion before police managed to arrest him, several Russian news agencies report.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/man-takes-hostage-in-russian-bank-branch/news-story/c12f3f98b859d3b84658beb2736b543d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>UK PM Johnson resists calls to sack aide</title>
		<description><![CDATA[British Prime Minister Boris Johnson has resisted calls from opposition parties to sack adviser Dominic Cummings after he travelled 400 km to northern England while his wife showed COVID-19 symptoms.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/uk-pm-johnson-resists-calls-to-sack-aide/news-story/098e94b972f3f6c3064074fad4016500</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Mass protests at Spain govt virus response</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Several thousand followers of Spain's far-right Vox party have gathered in Madrid and other cities to protest the government's handling of the coronavirus outbreak.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/mass-protests-at-spain-govt-virus-response/news-story/64b3fccbe8d7f1972af785442ca69145</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>