<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 01:33:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>State’s top cop killed in horror city crash</title>
		<description><![CDATA[One of South Australia’s top-ranking and most decorated police officers has been killed in a horrific high-speed crash that also claimed the life of another woman.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/adelaide-crash-horrific-multivehicle-collision-on-cross-rd-urrbrae/news-story/a90b8596f9d5c92c5b7788da17d9c98d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Tenth virus death in Tas, one new case</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A 90-year-old man from Tasmania's coronavirus-hit northwest has become the tenth person in the state to die from COVID-19.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/tenth-virus-death-in-tasmania/news-story/80f03b6a51543bf67a4bc1351402ea47</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>NSW man &#8216;joined terror org Al-Nusra Front&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A Sydney man has been charged after allegedly fighting for an al-Qaeda-linked Syrian terrorist group "for months at a time" in 2012 and 2013.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/nsw-man-joined-terror-org-alnusra-front/news-story/74e174252e4c32c8af447397a2e104ba</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Messaging the key to SA virus compliance</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Clear messaging is vital to ensure people understand why restrictions must remain in place as coronavirus infections continue to fall, South Australian health authorities say.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/sa-virus-cases-continue-to-fall/news-story/751b571848c5c6a8957450ccccd205b6</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US officer who shot Justine Damond appeals</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The former US police officer who shot dead Australian life coach Justine Ruszczyk Damond in an alley claims his murder and manslaughter convictions should be overturned because a Minneapolis jury was shielded from hearing his ambush fears.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-officer-who-shot-justine-damond-appeals/news-story/dc537520b7a3691bcc07f38f11b0b793</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US Navy recommends return of fired captain</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The top Navy officer has recommended the reinstatement of the aircraft carrier captain fired for sending a fraught email to commanders pleading for faster action to protect his crew from a coronavirus outbreak, officials familiar with the investigation say.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-navy-recommends-return-of-fired-captain/news-story/50fd60f2f3f5d801f606cdf6f228f466</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Brazil&#8217;s virus cases jump, testing falters</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Cases of the new coronavirus are overwhelming hospitals, morgues and cemeteries across Brazil as the country veers closer to becoming one of the world's pandemic hot spots.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/brazils-bolsonaro-in-crisis-mode/news-story/4c39f91a85ba6c44236fe44a2be73dc7</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China sees more imported coronavirus cases</title>
		<description><![CDATA[China's northwestern province of Shaanxi has reported seven new imported cases of the novel coronavirus, all in citizens returning home from Russia, even as domestic cases in the country have been largely curbed.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-sees-more-imported-coronavirus-cases/news-story/9de1a6d2d8e414ca86e3a5abb2852835</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>VC recipient has own mini Anzac service</title>
		<description><![CDATA[When Australia's oldest surviving Victoria Cross recipient stepped onto his front lawn before dawn on Anzac Day, he was pleasantly surprised to find he was far from alone.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/vc-recipient-has-own-mini-anzac-service/news-story/b7d4724cca73a551602c04a66bcfdee9</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Qld war widows recognised on Anzac Day</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Anzac Day is always an emotional day for war widows and this Anzac Day, when the traditional services were stopped, it was even more so.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/qld-war-widows-recognised-on-anzac-day/news-story/010ca1af0f4292b357128693b93313e4</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>