<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Latest News and News Headlines | Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 12:02:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress/5.8" -->

	<item>
		<title>Norway marks decade since Breivik massacre with anti-extremism plea</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Survivors of Norway's worst massacre since World War II called on Thursday for the country to stand up against the hatred that motivated right-wing extremist Anders Behring Breivik's killing spree exactly 10 years ago.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/norway-marks-decade-since-breivik-massacre-with-antiextremism-plea/news-story/ca99bab5dcfee520fb5aef4e181d8045</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China says WHO plan to audit labs in Covid origins probe &#8216;arrogant&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[China on Thursday said a WHO proposal to audit Chinese labs as part of further investigation into the origins of the coronavirus pandemic showed "disrespect" and "arrogance towards science".]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-says-who-plan-to-audit-labs-in-covid-origins-probe-arrogant/news-story/a2fff937f8a44961c65c138dde5315f2</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Madagascar says it foiled bid to assassinate president, six arrested</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Madagascar said Thursday it had foiled an attempt to assassinate President Andry Rajoelina and arrested six people, two of whom were French nationals.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/madagascar-prosecutors-say-foiled-assassination-bid-on-president/news-story/69b192d81c22ff27091bce9be3b47cbd</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Reason petrol will get cheaper</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Australian petrol is expected to get cheaper after a decision to increase global fuel production.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/motoring/on-the-road/petrol-to-get-cheaper-thanks-to-opec-decision-to-up-oil-production/news-story/2f68c7b6773b080d98b6fbb04445ff53</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Tokyo Olympics opening ceremony director fired over old Holocaust skit</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Tokyo 2020 organisers on Thursday fired the show director for the Olympic opening ceremony on the eve of the event over a decades-old skit referencing the Holocaust, in the latest blow for organisers of the pandemic-delayed Games.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/tokyo-olympics-opening-ceremony-director-fired-over-old-holocaust-skit/news-story/bf14d3ab6bdebf1b264fe0f0171c98fb</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Chinese city picks through the debris after record rains kill 33</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Piles of cars were strewn across a central Chinese city Thursday as shocked residents picked through the debris of a historic deluge that claimed at least 33 lives, with rescue efforts ongoing and hundreds seeking to find their relatives.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/chinese-city-picks-through-the-debris-after-record-rains-kill-33/news-story/f4fcfe7b8a226fa3b78c3fa75ebdcf7d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Ceremonies chief sacked on eve of troubled Tokyo Olympics</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The director of the Tokyo Olympics opening ceremony was fired for jokes about the Holocaust on Thursday, causing fresh embarrassment a day before the pandemic-delayed Games finally get under way.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/ceremonies-chief-sacked-on-eve-of-troubled-tokyo-olympics/news-story/cc53c6a8b90678f30ca87769a98d7556</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>860-day first in ‘wild’ NRL clash</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The brave and brutal Raiders prevailed in the most ferocious and physical game of football seen in the NRL this year to upset the Eels 12-10 and fire up their finals chances.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/nrl/nrl-fans-applaud-860day-first-in-canberra-raiders-win-over-parramatta-eels/news-story/b6a2a55f15441824c53a3da21e6dc42d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Fowler guides Fever to big win</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A signature effort from star goaler Jhaniele Fowler has helped West Coast Fever underline their Super Netball championship credentials with a 64-50 drubbing of the Melbourne Vixens in their rescheduled round 8 clash.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/netball/jhaniele-fowler-guides-west-coast-fever-to-big-win-over-melbourne-vixens/news-story/066e153ee4d94b57795e2f11fccd26f7</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>‘Harsh’: NRL coach takes aim at Broncos</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Craig Bellamy has called the Broncos’ decision to bench Melbourne-bound Origin star Xavier Coates “a little bit harsh”, questioning what the relegation would do to Coates’ confidence.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/nrl/its-a-bit-harsh-storm-coach-craig-bellamy-hits-out-at-brisbane-broncos-over-treatment-of-xavier-coates/news-story/4c2e8eb6d0971e3dc7b0ba9a7013c559</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>
