<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Latest News and News Headlines | Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 01:56:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress/5.8.1" -->

	<item>
		<title>Trudeau future on the line as Canadians vote in pandemic election</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Canadian elections headed for a photo finish Monday with liberal prime minister Justin Trudeau, who is seeking a third term, threatened by a strong challenge from rookie conservative leader Erin O'Toole.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/trudeau-future-on-the-line-as-canadians-vote-in-pandemic-election/news-story/01b00b2c6375f810101054b20ef53d29</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Canberra records 7 new cases</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Chief Minister Andrew Barr has cautioned it’s too early to celebrate just yet after Canberra recorded only seven new cases on Monday.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/act-records-seven-new-locally-acquired-covid19-cases/news-story/a9c740ac745f97ff77746b2596999ee0</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Television&#8217;s best bring glamour to Emmys red carpet</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Television's A-list returned to the red carpet in high style for the Emmys on Sunday -- a more traditional display of sartorial savoir faire after the pajamas and hoodies seen at last year's mostly virtual event.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/televisions-best-bring-glamour-to-emmys-red-carpet/news-story/63aaddf0dfecc80ad65e25d116bbc3c7</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Pro-Kremlin party on track for majority after crackdown</title>
		<description><![CDATA[President Vladimir Putin's United Russia party was on track to win a strong majority in a parliamentary vote, results showed Monday, after an election that followed an unprecedented crackdown on the opposition.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/putins-party-set-to-retain-parliament-majority-after-polls/news-story/a3bd2b0ec332a40c289fc82127a7b7a5</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>‘Fair bit of pressure’: Grand Final switch flicked</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The pressure of meeting their own expectations at the Western Bulldogs is equal to any Melbourne players are carrying as they seek to end the longest active AFL premiership drought in Saturday’s Grand Final.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/afl/afl-grand-final-western-bulldogs-star-caleb-daniel-says-his-teammates-have-kicked-up-a-gear-for-grand-final-week/news-story/6f7c4f97ea58baf1d137a2c74463c4bf</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>‘Maybe not friends’: France slams ScoMo</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The former French Ambassador to Australia has ripped into Scott Morrison for his defence of the AUKUS submarine deal, claiming the Prime Minister lied about warning France about it.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/maybe-were-not-friends-french-ambassador-claims-scomo-offered-no-warning-about-aukus-deal/news-story/467293b479eca4741c116ba5ced54751</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>New region in lockdown over one case</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The regional NSW town of Cowra will go into lockdown at 5pm on Monday after a boy attended school while infected with the coronavirus.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/cowra-nsw-to-go-into-lockdown-after-nineyearold-boy-tests-positive/news-story/1ebb7b7ba2e4260a46c3b7c1c307ec38</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>PM jets off to US after landmark pact</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The peace and freedom of the Indo-Pacific region will be at the top of Scott Morrison’s agenda as he jets off to Washington for four days of talks set to be dominated by regional security.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/work/scott-morrison-heads-to-washington-for-talks-with-biden-bojo/news-story/0b27f087ebea37c8ceb6519f2bcbcfa9</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>In-person Emmys return as Netflix eyes TV&#8217;s top prize with &#8216;The Crown&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Television's top stars gathered for the first time in two years on Sunday at the Emmy Awards, where "The Crown" took four awards in the first hour and is tipped to finally win the small screen's biggest prize for Netflix.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/inperson-emmys-return-as-netflix-eyes-tvs-top-prize-with-the-crown/news-story/c35c90c59b0d1e5dd9b0f0f2780d7c0f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>South Korea&#8217;s Ko wins weather-hit Portland Classic</title>
		<description><![CDATA[World number two Ko Jin-Young capped a 69 with a curling birdie putt on the 18th hole to capture the Portland Classic, which was shortened to 54 holes for the second straight year due to poor weather.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/south-koreas-ko-wins-weatherhit-portland-classic/news-story/32c6645e3fff992b3a400d9a7d731a38</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>
