<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Latest News and News Headlines | Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 07:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress/5.8.1" -->

	<item>
		<title>Police outsmart Melbourne protesters</title>
		<description><![CDATA[More than 50 anti-vaccination and anti-lockdown protesters have been arrested after a day of turbulent demonstrations in Melbourne.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/police-outsmart-antilockdown-protesters-in-melbourne/news-story/92ac80060bd90786f1a542e5a8c74ca2</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Global law firm stops representing HKU in Tiananmen sculpture row</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A top global law firm will no longer represent the University of Hong Kong in seeking the removal of a Tiananmen memorial from its campus after it came under heavy criticism in the United States for helping China purge dissent, the Washington Post reported.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/global-law-firm-stops-representing-hku-in-tiananmen-sculpture-row/news-story/9d65a1321da011fa826e26770bc335a6</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Nature Strip wins turf&#8217;s biggest price, The Everest</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Star sprinter Nature Strip, ridden by James McDonald, lived up to his billing as favourite to win the world's richest turf race, The Everest, in front of thousands of cheering punters in Sydney on Saturday.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/nature-strip-wins-turfs-biggest-price-the-everest/news-story/6adf59ff12cd3e6d729191264eb1a173</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lausanne tackles toxic soil after shock discovery</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Lausanne, the capital of Olympic sport overlooking Lake Geneva, is reeling after discovering that much of its soil is polluted with toxic compounds belched out by an old incinerator.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/lausanne-tackles-toxic-soil-after-shock-discovery/news-story/f3ee1235a4d23856b7ea6f195c55332a</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>France marks first anniversary since teacher killed over Mohammed cartoon</title>
		<description><![CDATA[France will pay tribute to schoolteacher Samuel Paty on Saturday, one year after he was beheaded by an extremist after showing his class cartoons of the Muslim Prophet Mohammed.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/france-marks-first-anniversary-since-teacher-killed-over-mohammed-cartoon/news-story/08214ed7a41c923b8b9000989b366a63</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Vibrant Afghan radio reduced to religious relic</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Radio station Urooj once teemed with journalists producing news bulletins, but since the Taliban came to town, Ebrahim Parhar sits alone, broadcasting hours of religious sermons.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/vibrant-afghan-radio-reduced-to-religious-relic/news-story/5c7c5e7c35652d2d5677b78b41744402</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Dozens fewer new virus cases in NSW</title>
		<description><![CDATA[NSW appears to be getting on top of its Delta outbreak as it marches towards the key 80 per cent double jabbed target, with 319 new locally transmitted cases of Covid-19 recorded on Saturday, down from almost 400 yesterday.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/nsw-records-319-new-local-covid19-cases/news-story/bfc8b642c1d4725fc4b93fc7b8ed8e4c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Champagne time: NSW hits 80 per cent</title>
		<description><![CDATA[NSW has hit the sought-after 80 per cent vaccination rate it raced so swiftly towards, even earlier than expected on the first lockdown-free weekend in months.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/nsw-hits-vaccine-milestone-faster-than-expected-new-premier-declares/news-story/9b4e82fa548626df7cf7e2e6fd79aa84</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>‘Throw the book’ at Covid breacher</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The Tasmanian Premier has called for a harsher penalty for the NSW man who left hotel quarantine and forced part of the state into a snap three-day lockdown.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/national/fine-doesnt-fit-the-crime-premier-calls-for-harsher-penalty-for-quarantine-breacher-who-caused-lockdown/news-story/cce32cacbe78cf6f0e04fd7ef18df9be</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Victorian teenager dies with Covid</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A 15-year-old girl is among Victoria’s seven Covid-19 deaths overnight, while the number of cases in the state’s hospitals has surged.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/tragic-victorian-teenager-dies-with-covid-and-a-number-of-other-conditions/news-story/c80f5928d64346626b52ab5a42e90fb2</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>
