<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 19:07:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Google makes Meet video conferencing free</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Alphabet Inc's Google says any user will soon be able to host free video conferences on Meet, turning its previously business-only tool into a bigger rival to Zoom and others battling for users during the coronavirus outbreak.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/google-makes-meet-video-conferencing-free/news-story/2d74cef218ab5e173721133e8dcd2a50</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Swiss schools, restaurants reopen in May</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Switzerland is planning to end its lockdown sooner than originally planned, with shops, markets and schools all set to open on May 11, as well as museums, libraries and restaurants, the government says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/swiss-schools-restaurants-reopen-in-may/news-story/a3342232a8a31047ee516c092a92ab7f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>UK virus death toll 2nd-highest in Europe</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The United Kingdom now has Europe's second-highest official death toll from the coronavirus pandemic, according to new figures that cover fatalities in all settings including in nursing homes.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/uk-virus-death-toll-2ndhighest-in-europe/news-story/988ffa04a26d1d852524cfd2cb86b36a</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>French virus death toll rises above 24,000</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The number of people who have died from the coronavirus infection in France has risen by 427 to 24,087, with the rate of increase slightly speeding up again after slowing on previous day, the health ministry says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/french-virus-death-toll-rises-above-24000/news-story/8403f40d6c41f0e316d58375d2d54033</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Finland to reopen schools, daycares in May</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Finland will reopen schools and daycare centres after May 13, having kept them mostly closed since March 18 due to the coronavirus pandemic, the government says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/finland-to-reopen-schools-daycares-in-may/news-story/16f0f9c90f9dbc589d905854f6bec2f6</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Guinea-Bissau PM has coronavirus: report</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The prime minister of the west African country of Guinea-Bissau and several other senior officials have tested positive for COVID-19, the Lusa news agency reports.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/guineabissau-pm-has-coronavirus-report/news-story/3b376d58f328afb913adf64685f5d3fb</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Bosnia virus cases surge as lockdown eased</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Bosnia has reported its sharpest daily rise in new coronavirus infections this month after its two autonomous regions had gradually begun to ease lockdowns.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/bosnia-virus-cases-surge-as-lockdown-eased/news-story/f398d93f4c42da7b09f7097637392491</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Italy death toll falls, new cases stable</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Deaths from the COVID-19 epidemic in Italy have climbed by 323 against 382 the day before, the Civil Protection Agency says, while the daily tally of new infections stood at 2086, broadly stable from 2091 on the previous day.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/italy-death-toll-falls-new-cases-stable/news-story/4c3a628d961ac5ae1c1a76c5acdd8c6c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lebanon deposits money safe: central bank</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Lebanese central bank governor Riad Salameh has defended his record, rejecting criticism from the prime minister that he was to blame for a financial crisis and assuring savers there was no need for a haircut on their deposits.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/lebanon-deposits-money-safe-central-bank/news-story/d34ca14cb9aafbc3a94c35ff3278a65c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Elon Musk pushes for US economy to reopen</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Eccentric entrepreneur Elon Musk, the chief of electric carmaker Tesla, has been using his large platform on social media to call for reopening the US economy quickly amid extended shutdowns due to the coronavirus pandemic.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/elon-musk-pushes-for-us-economy-to-reopen/news-story/d969490c0dedf5c698c87e345a3fcc33</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>