<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 21:04:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Mexico eyes &#8216;happiness&#8217; alternative to GDP</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Mexico will create a happiness index as an alternative to the gross domestic product (GDP), which is not a good indicator of well-being, President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/mexico-eyes-happiness-alternative-to-gdp/news-story/6137eaa024f909e93d56fbc9d314a3f0</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>&#8216;Terror-related&#8217; shooter at US base killed</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US authorities say an active shooter injured one person before being killed by security forces at a navy military base in the state of Texas, in what is being called a "terrorism-related" incident.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/terrorrelated-shooter-at-us-base-killed/news-story/a0b6a01cdfc93a281a79e2a80181d0d4</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lebanon at risk of a major food crisis: PM</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Lebanon's financial meltdown could tip the country into a full-blown food crisis, as people hit by soaring prices and the fallout of COVID-19 become unable to afford even basics like bread, the prime minister has warned.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/lebanon-at-risk-of-a-major-food-crisis-pm/news-story/715c4532dad03c06b91dc9a08675d3f4</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Fed govt clampdown on litigation funders</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The federal government plans to impose new regulatory measures on litigation funders who stump up the cash to support class action lawsuits.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/fed-govt-clampdown-on-litigation-funders/news-story/0d1180448d4d826366277a9eb0714e5d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Italy arrests &#8216;corrupt&#8217; Sicily virus tsar</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Sicily's coronavirus emergency co-ordinator has been arrested along with nine other people on suspicion of corruption and rigging of health sector tenders while in his previous role, police on the Italian island say.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/italy-arrests-corrupt-sicily-virus-tsar/news-story/ef2ff405f7a2ad639467ec9ea7543c65</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US says 1700 tests damaged on way to lab</title>
		<description><![CDATA[More than 1700 people in the US state of Florida will have to be retested for the coronavirus after their state-administered tests were damaged while being transported to the lab for analysis.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-says-1700-tests-damaged-on-way-to-lab/news-story/7aee722ec93eeaeae26761030cb50112</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>European virus tracking apps face setbacks</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Doubts are growing over whether ambitious plans by European governments to use contact-tracing apps to fight the spread of the coronavirus will be able to be implemented with any real effectiveness soon.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/european-virus-tracking-apps-face-setbacks/news-story/f76945013b7170db77f1b403aa9f9911</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China doesn&#8217;t get Canada&#8217;s judiciary: PM</title>
		<description><![CDATA[China does not appear to understand that Canada's judiciary is independent, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau says, taking a rare public swipe at officials in Beijing at a time when bilateral ties are poor.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-doesnt-get-canadas-judiciary-pm/news-story/98b534020836638e9ff5d93b4c3c935b</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Cyclone hits India, Bangladesh, 85 dead</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Wide swathes of the coasts of India and Bangladesh have been flooded and millions of people remain without power, after the most powerful cyclone to hit the region in more than decade left dozens dead and a trail of destruction.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/deadly-cyclone-cuts-power-to-5m-homes/news-story/aeaf7ac805248fa14d6b4bacb109f789</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Oxfam to close 18 offices worldwide</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Oxfam International, one of the world's leading aid agencies, is to severely curtail its work because of the financial strain caused by the coronavirus pandemic, including the closure of operations in 18 countries at the potential cost of more than 2,000 jobs.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/oxfam-to-close-18-offices-worldwide/news-story/d65f344281a8e308230051cd47fbbe8f</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>