<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Trump vows to use military, police shot</title>
		<description><![CDATA[At least five US police officers have been hit by gunfire during violent protests over the death of a black man in police custody, hours after President Donald Trump vowed to use the military to halt the unrest.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-urges-law-and-order-amid-demo-clashes/news-story/64487467c7371071788d470cd2f55342</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>WA man had photos of girls bound, gagged</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A man caught with sexual images of young children, including some who were bound, gagged and obviously distressed, has been sentenced to 14 months in a Western Australian prison.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/wa-man-had-photos-of-girls-bound-gagged/news-story/33039c5bd34e04579bc10bfc631a48b4</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Autopsies clash on cause of Floyd&#8217;s death</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A medical examiner's office has ruled that the death of George Floyd, the black man whose killing in Minneapolis police custody last week triggered nationwide protests, was a homicide and that he died from asphyxiation.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/floyd-family-to-release-own-autopsy-result/news-story/4c1eedc11b4b0f640f5591510b47ffe0</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Florida suspends officer for pushing woman</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Fort Lauderdale police have suspended an officer after video showed he pushed a kneeling black woman to the ground during protests, escalating a clash where bottles were thrown and tear gas was fired.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/fort-lauderdale-police-officer-suspended/news-story/c53b2d3e43d57225b1b863c980962620</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Obama urges US criminal justice reform</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Former US president Barack Obama has penned a lengthy essay urging his country to "get to work" to enact criminal justice reform and address systemic racism after a weekend of protests over the death of George Floyd at the hands of Minneapolis police.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/obama-urges-us-criminal-justice-reform/news-story/21cea88f8c68eed8518de4cb9c3c4d7e</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Swedish PM to appoint coronavirus inquiry</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Sweden will launch an inquiry into the country's handling of the pandemic before the northern summer, Prime Minister Stefan Lofven has said in a newspaper interview amid growing criticism over nursing home deaths and the lack of testing.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/swedish-pm-to-appoint-coronavirus-inquiry/news-story/e6b6d3534a84b23266dfe31b40054759</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>French COVID-19 cases in hospitals dip</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The French health ministry says people should continue taking protective measures against the coronavirus even as cases in hospitals and intensive care continue to fall.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/french-covid19-cases-in-hospitals-dip/news-story/c4ffe4b92e12caa590f802bead29da27</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>UK contact-tracing going well, govt says</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Britain's coronavirus test-and-trace system is working well and some of the thousands of contact-tracers who have been recruited are not yet fully occupied, Health Secretary Matt Hancock says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/uk-contacttracing-going-well-govt-says/news-story/733c3caccf883a8341e475890abc78ac</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Spain reports no daily coronavirus death</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Spain says it's reporting no deaths in a 24-hour period from the coronavirus for the first time since March.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/spain-reports-no-daily-coronavirus-death/news-story/90eeebe4ede025c5d16c622de20de15e</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Iran MP says 230 killed in November unrest</title>
		<description><![CDATA[An Iranian MP says 230 people were killed in November's anti-government protests in Iran, the official news agency reports.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/iran-mp-says-230-killed-in-november-unrest/news-story/40702db664e96bd3d134e980a4ea8c7d</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>