<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:34:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>US VP&#8217;s staff tests positive for virus</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Vice President Mike Pence's press secretary has the coronavirus, the White House says, making her the second person who works at the White House complex known to test positive for the virus this week.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-vps-staff-tests-positive-for-virus/news-story/4f9a33bf285aa66009e2f8e97e584d47</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Zero cases as Qld eases virus restrictions</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Queensland has recorded its third day of zero cases this week as the state continues to stifle the spread of coronavirus.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/qld-to-begin-easing-virus-restrictions/news-story/7d73325e789af7e6b3a4451345c278d6</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Roadmap in place but big task still ahead</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Federal government frontbencher Dan Tehan says Australia still faces a big task rebuilding the economy, even though it now has a road map to steer it out of the coronavirus crisis.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/states-have-power-on-relaxing-virus-rules/news-story/bb68b65206300fb44a12b459a51fe499</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Mother&#8217;s Day hugs a no-no in New Zealand</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Hugs and visits to mums across New Zealand have been banned this Mother's Day by Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern, seeking a final push from Kiwis to end the country's lockdown.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/mothers-day-hugs-a-nono-in-new-zealand/news-story/b8f9a8e087e991b11f5051d4eaf43847</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>NSW man behind bars after brother stabbed</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A Sydney man is behind bars accused of stabbing his older brother and attacking his brother's car.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/nsw-man-behind-bars-after-brother-stabbed/news-story/7252004da009410f6b1d16c4e0822559</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>NSW boy, 4, in hospital after snake bite</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A young boy has been flown to Brisbane after he was bitten by a snake in northern NSW.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/nsw-boy-4-in-hospital-after-snake-bite/news-story/77e3e022f06fd94568f12c1ee67eb5bf</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Aide to US VP Pence has coronavirus</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US Vice President Mike Pence's press secretary has the coronavirus, the White House says, making her the second person who works there known to test positive for the virus this week.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/aide-to-us-vp-pence-has-coronavirus/news-story/c4cb993538f185408296230c54bffb4f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Californians to get president postal votes</title>
		<description><![CDATA[California has become the first US state to order mail-in ballots be issued to all registered voters for the November presidential elections as a result of the coronavirus pandemic.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/californians-to-get-president-postal-votes/news-story/8d9bc059d0061f629fd20ad6336a1418</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Queen hails British resilience on VE Day</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Queen Elizabeth has honoured those who died in World War II on the 75th anniversary of Victory in Europe Day and used the occasion to say she was proud of how people had responded to the coronavirus pandemic.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/queen-hails-british-resilience-on-ve-day/news-story/d0e00381f9bfe3fa47a5b1bf398e1647</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Virus lockdowns mute VE Day across Europe</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Europe has marked the 75th anniversary of the end of World War II in low-key fashion because of coronavirus lockdown restrictions across the continent.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/virus-lockdowns-mute-ve-day-across-europe/news-story/0b5fb734cfc4f75485bb91792686a11c</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>