<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 11:44:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>EU trade chief slams UK approach to talks</title>
		<description><![CDATA[There is no real sign that Britain is approaching trade talks with the European Union with a plan to succeed and it appears set to blame any post-Brexit fall-out on the economic shock from COVID-19, the EU's trade chief says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/eu-trade-chief-slams-uk-approach-to-talks/news-story/474c2c15904d6197ddb6b15e24f93f00</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rio Tinto faces climate heat at AGM</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Global miner Rio Tinto has recommended shareholders vote against forcing it to set targets around the emissions of its steel-making customers, putting it on a collision course with investors over its climate policies.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/rio-tinto-faces-climate-heat-at-agm/news-story/0627c5fa96927c788eff6ed9ee50a982</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Russian virus cases rise to daily record</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The number of identified cases of the coronavirus in Russia has climbed by a new daily record of more than 11,200, pushing the total past 177,000, according to a federal monitoring service.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/russian-virus-cases-rise-to-daily-record/news-story/ae86ee026ce8a14452d35f3e923b338f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Indonesia tasks China over burials at sea</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Indonesia has summoned China's ambassador to clarify the deaths of four Indonesian crew from two Chinese-flagged vessels, Indonesia's foreign ministry says, after rights groups alleged the crew were mistreated and exploited.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/indonesia-tasks-china-over-burials-at-sea/news-story/ee4f103f2234484d0b162fd6502e92fb</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Pakistan to lift coronavirus lockdown</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Pakistan's coronavirus lockdown will be lifted on Saturday, Prime Minister Imran Khan says, despite the fact that the number of cases in the country is still accelerating.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/pakistan-to-lift-coronavirus-lockdown/news-story/3ae376fdf37847590ecec5b7bf6d2a43</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>ViacomCBS Q1 profit slumps on ad decline</title>
		<description><![CDATA[ViacomCBS says first-quarter profit tumbled as the company suffered a 19 per cent decline in advertising revenue due in part to the cancellation of the NCAA "March Madness" men's basketball championship this year.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/viacomcbs-q1-profit-slumps-on-ad-decline/news-story/b5574b81008afc274bca086b7fb7affc</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Philippine broadcaster fights shut order</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The Philippines' biggest broadcaster has asked the Supreme Court to quash an order by the telecoms regulator to shut down its operations, saying it undermined freedom of speech and the public right to information.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/philippine-broadcaster-fights-shut-order/news-story/bc16ec2dc55a6c47a354c70c11775ecc</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Nintendo profit jump as people stay home</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Japanese video-game maker Nintendo Co. has scored a 33 per cent jump in annual profit, as people stuck at home turn to playing games amid the coronavirus pandemic.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/nintendo-profit-jump-as-people-stay-home/news-story/2a8e734b5e14c7a7a8b90ede6236f080</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>China, US trade negotiators to hold talks</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Trade negotiators from the United States and China will hold a phone call as early as next week, Bloomberg reports, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/china-us-trade-negotiators-to-hold-talks/news-story/128ecdf5068dbea8cff1ef09720f66b1</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>PM Morrison joins club of virus champions</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Australia has been given a seat at the table of a select group of countries which responded quickly to the COVID-19 outbreak and are now restoring their economies to normal.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/pm-morrison-joins-club-of-virus-champions/news-story/0f56a94c5afa000b52cea6432fe2a5c0</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>