<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 19:12:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Second coronavirus wave feared after demos</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Europe could face a surge of COVID-19 infections in the coming weeks caused by mass protests in the continent over the last days, politicians, European Union officials and experts say.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/second-coronavirus-wave-feared-after-demos/news-story/d10df2430deabd69219ea65943c1d29e</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>UK govt eyes potential wealth tax: banker</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Britain's finance ministry is canvassing private bankers over how the country's richest citizens might help pay for the soaring cost of coronavirus relief packages, with potential tax hikes likely to sit high on the agenda.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/uk-govt-eyes-potential-wealth-tax-banker/news-story/461a4adeb4a3aba3300eacfd125bc0b0</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>New virus cases hit daily record in Sweden</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Sweden has announced its highest daily tally of coronavirus infections, a record 1474 new cases that authorities say is due to a long-delayed surge in testing.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/new-virus-cases-hit-daily-record-in-sweden/news-story/09778c4f8f2ccd5e6c2bac034dcad3f2</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US army officer regrets Trump church walk</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Top US military officer Mark Milley says he was wrong to have accompanied President Donald Trump on a walk to a church through Lafayette Square, where he was photographed in his combat uniform with the presidential entourage.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/us-army-officer-regrets-trump-church-walk/news-story/8b669b5d23c92469cbbe95fbceb140e3</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Thai temple bars foreigners on virus fears</title>
		<description><![CDATA[One of Thailand's major tourist attractions is barring entry to foreigners, professing fear that they could spread the coronavirus.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/thai-temple-bars-foreigners-on-virus-fears/news-story/c2bd5f3827c06ef960879a26b09ad804</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Italy records 53 new deaths, 379 new cases</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Italy has registered 379 new cases of COVID-19, mostly in the northern region of Lombardy where the outbreak first exploded in Europe.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/italy-records-53-new-deaths-379-new-cases/news-story/1bb8c6804c4beeee3463d2505b4ff47e</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Slovak teacher killed in knife attack</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A young man armed with a knife has attacked several people in a Slovakian primary school, killing a teacher and injuring four others.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/slovak-teacher-killed-in-knife-attack/news-story/c18a3f4b9156aa1906fa17f7f9aa6f8c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Doctor warns India faces virus &#8216;time bomb&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[India has reported a record of nearly 10,000 new coronavirus cases, with health services in the worst-hit cities of Mumbai, New Delhi and Chennai swamped by the rising infections.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/doctor-warns-india-faces-virus-time-bomb/news-story/71b5604106a1f4e15d85c9751786b3a6</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Russian mayor charged over spill response</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Russian authorities have charged the head of the remote Arctic city of Norilsk with criminal negligence over what investigators say was his bungled response to a major environmental disaster.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/russian-mayor-charged-over-spill-response/news-story/48dfe31ab446adf25a43990df79ee86c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Banksy stolen from Bataclan found in Italy</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Italian authorities have unveiled a stolen artwork by the British artist Banksy that was painted as a tribute to the victims of the 2015 terrorist attacks at the Bataclan music hall in Paris.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/banksy-stolen-from-bataclan-found-in-italy/news-story/1c633bb07dc6f0606190dd38794ad5c1</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>