<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Latest News and News Headlines | Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 20:19:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress/5.8.1" -->

	<item>
		<title>Trudeau, O&#8217;Toole blitz key battlegrounds ahead of Canada&#8217;s Monday election</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Canada's Liberal prime minister Justin Trudeau and his main rival, rookie Conservative leader Erin O'Toole, made their final pitches to voters in key battlegrounds Sunday on the eve of snap elections as the two remain virtually tied in public opinion polls.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/trudeau-otoole-blitz-key-battlegrounds-ahead-of-canadas-monday-election/news-story/1fae81edc77bb221dc7b3c4c08e9ff85</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Pro-Kremlin party on track for majority after crackdown</title>
		<description><![CDATA[President Vladimir Putin's United Russia party was on track to win a strong majority in a parliamentary vote, results showed Sunday, after an election that followed an unprecedented crackdown on the opposition.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/putins-party-set-to-retain-parliament-majority-after-polls/news-story/a3bd2b0ec332a40c289fc82127a7b7a5</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>In-person Emmys return as Netflix eyes TV&#8217;s top prize with &#8216;The Crown&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Television's top stars will gather in person for the first time in two years at Sunday's Emmys, where Netflix is tipped to finally win the small screen's biggest prize for "The Crown."]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/inperson-emmys-return-as-netflix-eyes-tvs-top-prize-with-the-crown/news-story/c35c90c59b0d1e5dd9b0f0f2780d7c0f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Biden asks for early talks with Macron amid submarine row</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US President Joe Biden has requested early talks with French President Emmanuel Macron, France said on Sunday, in an apparent effort to mend fences after a row over a submarines contract sparked rare tensions between the allies.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/france-accuses-australia-us-of-lying-in-escalating-crisis/news-story/af5346a07c2d9f6348d45fcd06f5b971</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Hong Kong elite selects powerful new &#8216;patriots only&#8217; committee</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Hong Kong's political elite began selecting a powerful committee on Sunday which will choose the city's next leader and nearly half the legislature under a new "patriots only" system imposed by Beijing.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/hong-kong-elite-selects-powerful-new-patriots-only-committee/news-story/08b2ae3cc93053730183d0333c55fd1a</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Living with Alzheimer&#8217;s: China&#8217;s health time bomb</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The first time Chen Shaohua went missing and was picked up by police, the 68-year-old's family put it down to confusion.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/living-with-alzheimers-chinas-health-time-bomb/news-story/539815c73cef098b7d4a85aea6659926</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>McNealy rallies late to grab share of the lead at Fortinet Championship</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Jim Knous and Maverick McNealy both birdied their final holes of the round to top a crowded leaderboard at The Fortinet Championship, the first PGA Tour event of the new season. ]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/mcnealy-rallies-late-to-grab-share-of-the-lead-at-fortinet-championship/news-story/86b4273348a8aaad5f9021048d18f142</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Myanmar military convoy hit by roadside bomb near Yangon: junta</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Myanmar anti-junta dissidents have carried out a bomb attack on security forces near Yangon, with several killed in an ensuing firefight, the military and media said.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/myanmar-military-convoy-hit-by-roadside-bomb-near-yangon-junta/news-story/a6d99a2c743f4b56d6dc54a0ed905cb6</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Ex-inmates decry worsening state of New York&#8217;s &#8216;hellhole&#8217; jail</title>
		<description><![CDATA[It's held disgraced producer Harvey Weinstein, rapper Tupac Shakur and ex-IMF chief Dominique Strauss-Kahn: New York's notorious Rikers Island prison is now under intense scrutiny over the deaths of at least nine inmates this year.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/exinmates-decry-worsening-state-of-new-yorks-hellhole-jail/news-story/21985c6501b9c8cc33511bd1a47c2c10</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Fed expected to stay cautious as economy sends mixed signals</title>
		<description><![CDATA[With the United States on the upswing from the Covid-19 pandemic, the Federal Reserve is expected to weigh in next week on whether the economy is healthy enough to begin withdrawing stimulus measures credited with aiding the revival.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/fed-expected-to-stay-cautious-as-economy-sends-mixed-signals/news-story/d2e5a4d3e6f5fe1de98a19d7a5a075a4</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>
