<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Latest News and News Headlines | Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:00:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress/5.8.1" -->

	<item>
		<title>Chaos puts Victorian construction at risk</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Construction figures are bracing for a snap industry-wide shutdown in response to violent protests in Melbourne.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/victorian-government-to-announce-twoweek-lockdown-of-construction-industry-after-protests/news-story/8394dbf36642008c2836e33ba16c4711</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Hong Kong leads equity sell-off as Evergrande fears spread</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Asian markets sank Monday on fears about contagion from a possible collapse of teetering property giant China Evergrande, while sentiment was also dragged by the Federal Reserve's plans to taper monetary policy, surging Delta infections and signs of weakness in the global recovery.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/hong-kong-leads-equity-selloff-as-evergrande-fears-spread/news-story/ac24d651f05578bbbde2507e26695251</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Russia opposition claims mass fraud after Putin party sweeps vote</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Russia's opposition accused the authorities of mass voter fraud as election results on Monday showed the ruling United Russia party winning a sweeping majority in parliament. ]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/putins-party-set-to-retain-parliament-majority-after-polls/news-story/a3bd2b0ec332a40c289fc82127a7b7a5</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Teen cleared of murder acting in self defence</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A teenager who fired a shotgun blast into his drug-affected neighbour’s chest at point blank range during a fatal altercation over a barking dog has been found not guilty of murder after a judge found he was acting in self defence.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/why-teen-who-gunned-down-neighbour-was-found-not-guilty-of-murder/news-story/d44aaa7e8d3ae29bf7b4be462a09c99e</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>‘Pay-off’ concerns in Malka Leifer case</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A social worker was worried an alleged victim of Malka Leifer wanted a “possible pay-off” and feared she could be sued if she made a statement to police, a court has been told.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/social-worker-concerned-about-payoffs-for-alleged-victims-of-malka-leifer/news-story/e28e385ed94e31c85a558a9fd52871b5</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>McGowan caught in jam by own border ban</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Western Australia’s border closure with NSW could make it difficult for Premier Mark McGowan to attend his defamation trial against billionaire Clive Palmer without being forced to quarantine upon his return.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/wa-hard-border-could-complicate-premier-mark-mcgowans-defamation-case-against-billionaire-clive-palmer/news-story/df7f189bc2e6189ccc5870851c0cb5ed</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Afghan women outraged by new Taliban restrictions on work</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The Taliban's effective ban on women working sank in on Monday, sparking rage over the dramatic loss of rights after millions of female teachers and girls were barred from secondary school education.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/afghan-women-outraged-by-new-taliban-restrictions-on-work/news-story/115ad10cac175a87100a34d4d6b5f3a9</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Evil killer may have another victim</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The brother of a woman killed by her monster ex-partner has shared why he thinks the man could have killed a different woman seven years earlier.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/peter-keoghs-horror-past-outlined-in-maria-james-inquest/news-story/e8c5523687490b38464ae6d0e32005dd</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Germany&#8217;s DAX down as index grows from 30 to 40 firms</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The DAX fell two percent in early trading on Monday to its lowest level since July, as the blue-chip stock market index grew from 30 to 40 companies in the biggest overhaul in its 33-year history.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/germanys-dax-index-grows-from-30-to-40-firms-in-revamp/news-story/ecfcf31e21d39a783104c31fa56be576</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>‘Everything just clicked’: secret to Brownlow success</title>
		<description><![CDATA[There was a time Ollie Wines thought leaving Port Adelaide would be best for his career, and he even had trust issues with coach Ken Hinkley.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/afl/brownlow-medal-ollie-wines-reveals-the-mindset-change-that-helped-him-stay-at-port-adelaide-and-win-a-brownlow-medal/news-story/c8e3841859556fabf61fd456d0008ec1</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>
