<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Latest News and News Headlines | Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 16:36:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress/5.7.2" -->

	<item>
		<title>US to evacuate Afghan interpreters as Taliban seize border town</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Thousands of interpreters who aided US and NATO forces in Afghanistan will be evacuated beginning in late July, Washington announced Wednesday, as Taliban insurgents captured a strategic crossing on the Pakistan border from government forces.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/taliban-claims-to-control-key-border-crossing-with-pakistan/news-story/98f1fae1bea3eacd19b175d5c40ef909</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>South African government asks for 25,000 troops to curb unrest</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The South African government on Wednesday sought to to deploy around 25,000 troops to curb unrest, now in its sixth straight day, amid fears of food and fuel shortages as disruption to farming, manufacturing and oil refining began to bite.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/south-africa-unrest-prompts-fears-of-food-and-fuel-shortages/news-story/4facdff89955e67d772804074004b83f</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Britney Spears legal battle back in Los Angeles court</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Three weeks after Britney Spears sensationally called for an end to her "abusive" guardianship, the pop singer's legal battle returned to court Wednesday in Los Angeles.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/britney-spears-legal-battle-heads-back-to-los-angeles-court/news-story/8743a8573ba6d83effc2e2823dc5b0b0</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>#FreeBritney: online army rallies behind &#8216;silenced&#8217; Spears</title>
		<description><![CDATA[When two comedians started a podcast about Britney Spears's quirky Instagram posts, they had no idea it would fuel a global online movement uniting superfans with rights activists in outrage over the star's legal situation.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/freebritney-online-army-rallies-behind-silenced-spears/news-story/8aa83d2d10e8af7946ca0689a3ed736c</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>ECB inches closer to &#8216;digital euro&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[The European Central Bank inched closer to a "digital euro" on Wednesday with the formal launch of a pilot project, but questions remain about potential pitfalls and benefits for eurozone citizens.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/ecb-inches-closer-to-digital-euro/news-story/e12d6a9b4c31c7115c7856db4a8180b8</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Warming, deforestation turn Amazon into source of CO2</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Climate change and deforestation have flipped a large swathe of the Amazon basin from absorbing to emitting planet-warming CO2, a transformation that could turn humanity's greatest natural ally in the fight against global warming into a foe, researchers reported on Wednesday.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/warming-deforestation-turn-amazon-into-source-of-co2/news-story/990eacf38dce7456fe8ccbde35c52ae2</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Global giant’s buy now, pay later move</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Australia’s buy now, pay later sector just got a whole lot more competitive, with shoppers now able to choose PayPal’s offering over local incumbents like Afterpay, while tech giant Apple is believed to be planning a BNPL addition to its mobile phone payment method.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/lifestyle/paypals-buy-now-pay-later-australia-launch-sends-shivers-through-incumbents-afterpay-zip-splitit/news-story/c42b16317b3057d2982cbf0ad7e378bb</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>After virus closures, Shakespeare returns&#8230; outside</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Britain's Royal Shakespeare Company has returned to the stage after an enforced 18-month absence due to the coronavirus pandemic -- at a specially built open-air theatre in the bard's home town.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/after-virus-closures-shakespeare-returns-outside/news-story/faee9c87eb54566232ccad04f13215ad</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Stores in Qld on Covid-19 alert</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Customers who visited a shopping centre in Ipswich may have been exposed to Covid-19 after a person visited the centre before travelling overseas.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/breaking-news/several-exposures-sites-listed-across-ipswich-and-brisbane/news-story/41054cdf3a0cc6342a7d94400bbec80d</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>De Belin breaks silence over Covid breach</title>
		<description><![CDATA[For the St George Illawarra Dragons, it’s been nothing short of a hellish few weeks in the wake of a BBQ hosted by disgraced prop Paul Vaughan.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/nrl/de-belin-among-dragons-stars-apologising-for-covid-breach/news-story/f56adc30ac1defe2b8f1c366ca89e222</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>
