<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Breaking News &#124; Daily Telegraph</title>
	<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au</link>
	<description>We&#039;re for Sydney</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 16:50:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	<!-- generator="WordPress.com" -->

	<item>
		<title>Floyd &#8216;didn&#8217;t deserve to die over $US20&#8217;</title>
		<description><![CDATA[A US congressional panel confronting racial injustice and police violence has heard an impassioned plea from a brother of George Floyd not to let his death in Minneapolis police custody to have been in vain, lamenting that he "didn't deserve to die over $US20".]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/floyd-didnt-deserve-to-die-over-us20/news-story/7ab39f9dca2659feda91dd076619d9cd</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Russian FSB says Crimea terror plot foiled</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Russia's domestic intelligence agency says it has foiled a terrorist plot in Crimea, and that five suspects in the case have been arrested.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/russian-fsb-says-crimea-terror-plot-foiled/news-story/ab19bb55d88d5cf7177ac9fd09d3fa08</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Trump eyes executive order on US policing</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump could take policy action on race and policing via an executive order, his spokeswoman has told Fox News in an interview as lawmakers in Congress move forward with their proposals.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/trump-eyes-executive-order-on-us-policing/news-story/08c2a54659a4163024699ec8732ee329</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>At least 18 feared dead in Afghan mine</title>
		<description><![CDATA[An explosion in a coal mine in Afghanistan's northern province of Samangan is thought to have killed at least 18 people, an official says.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/at-least-18-feared-dead-in-afghan-mine/news-story/4d09357ee325a79a29dcf30be8765e7a</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Managers arrested after Russian fuel spill</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Russian authorities have detained three top managers of an Arctic power plant that leaked almost 20,000 tonnes of diesel fuel into the ecologically fragile region.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/managers-arrested-after-russian-fuel-spill/news-story/058941572f0444215e9f7e1043b9d8e4</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>S.Korea charges groups over North leaflets</title>
		<description><![CDATA[South Korea's government will charge two activist groups that have been floating anti-Pyongyang leaflets and bottles filled with rice to North Korea for breaking the law by sending unauthorised materials to the rival nation.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/skorea-charges-groups-over-north-leaflets/news-story/75d6766cfaff75da09b9cd3cc9c22a07</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>US consumer prices fall for third month</title>
		<description><![CDATA[US consumer prices dropped in May for the third straight month as the coronavirus pandemic pushed the country's economy into a recession.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/business/breaking-news/us-consumer-prices-fall-for-third-month/news-story/393615776f2c3da7c33683cdd8891cb4</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Voting problems in US state of Georgia</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Voters have encountered long lines and problems with voting machines during a chaotic day of in-person balloting in Georgia, the latest US state to struggle to conduct elections amid the health worries of the coronavirus pandemic.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/voting-problems-in-us-state-of-georgia/news-story/4553263b67e72d514cb3c547c9ea8d09</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>NZ preparing for COVID-complicated poll</title>
		<description><![CDATA[New Zealand is planning for its most challenging and expensive election ever on September 19, a poll complicated by COVID-19 and two referendums.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/nz-preparing-for-covidcomplicated-poll/news-story/90c33b000793136b7533865ac2185380</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Sweden halts probe into 1986 murder of PM</title>
		<description><![CDATA[Sweden has dropped its investigation into the unsolved murder of former Swedish Prime Minister Olof Palme, who was shot dead 34 years ago in downtown Stockholm.]]></description>
		<link>https://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/breaking-news/sweden-halts-probe-into-1986-murder-of-pm/news-story/4926a94754741bbed3a6978b3c2fb465</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss>