<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Hope Channel Philippines</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-06-28T12:51:18+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kKp1G3e0t7k</id>
  <yt:videoId>kKp1G3e0t7k</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 12 | Pagharap sa mga Mahirap na Talata</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kKp1G3e0t7k"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-14T13:54:32+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-14T14:08:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 12 | Pagharap sa mga Mahirap na Talata</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kKp1G3e0t7k?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kKp1G3e0t7k/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Tagalog Adult Sabbath School
Weekly Bible Lesson Review
Lesson 12, 2nd Quarter, 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="22" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="234"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:g58DO0UG5Tg</id>
  <yt:videoId>g58DO0UG5Tg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Battle Between Good and Evil Revealed! It's all about you  😱☠️</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g58DO0UG5Tg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-13T13:00:13+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-13T13:58:45+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Battle Between Good and Evil Revealed! It's all about you  😱☠️</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/g58DO0UG5Tg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/g58DO0UG5Tg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Is there anything you can really trust? Where can you find real, authentic answers to life’s greatest questions? “The Great Controversy” outlines a great cosmic battle, between good and evil, and it is centered around you. How can you survive? What is the answer?

In the final episode, we will explore the history of the great battle between good and evil. It will show the fall of Lucifer and demonstrate that God has a plan that will overwhelm the devil’s attack.

This is the fourteenth and final episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-blueprint/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE BLUEPRINT

Have you ever been lost without directions or a map? Did you know that God gave us a roadmap to navigate our lives? In order to read God’s map, we must first understand the great controversy, a cosmic war between God and Satan.  
 
The great controversy began with Lucifer, a heavenly angel, proclaiming in Isaiah 14:14 that he wanted to be “like the Most High.” The problem was that Lucifer wanted to be Holy without following the law of God, which reflects His character of love. God needed a jury to judge Lucifer (who became Satan) fairly and justly (Deuteronomy 19:15), so He created humans, partially to serve as jurors and demonstrate His true character (1 Corinthians 6:2-3). Adam and Eve chose to sin against God, disqualifying them from jury selection, because they were no longer law-abiding citizens. The Gospel was given to restore humanity to be sound jurors, who can distinguish from right and wrong. God knew that we would need a map in order to make our way back to heaven. What is this blueprint?

The Sanctuary is a unique structure that represents God’s house among His people (Exodus 25:8). It is also the blueprint to God’s plan of salvation, with each piece of furniture symbolizing a part of the Gospel message. God shows His plan to deliver His people through this blueprint. 

God also gives prophecies, which are like landmarks through time. Our first landmark is in the book of Daniel, the 70-week prophecy that foretells the first coming of the Messiah (Daniel 9:24-27). Israel is not prepared for Jesus’ coming and rejects Him. When Jesus died on the cross, the veil of the sanctuary was torn in two, signifying the end of the earthly blueprint (Matthew 27:51). 
 
The second landmark, the prophecy of 1260 years, states that the little horn would rise in power (Daniel 7:19, 25). Many Seventh-day Adventists believe that the little horn represents papal Rome and have interpreted this prophecy to symbolize an attempted change in the Christian day of worship from Saturday to Sunday. 

The third landmark, the prophecy of 2300 years, tells us that the sanctuary will be cleansed (Daniel 8:14). We believe that this period of time ended in 1844. Over a period of 500 years, God used the Reformation movement to restore His truth to the world using everyday Christians like you and me. 
 
Finally, we come to our last landmark, the third angel’s message. Revelation 15 and 16 tell us that the seven last plagues are inflicted on those who ignore and reject God’s message. However, those who choose to receive God’s seal are safe (Psalms 91:1-2). The seal of the living God marks the end of our journey (Revelation 7:1-4). 
 
In Revelation 12:10, Satan accuses humanity of falling away from God. However, when God opens the books, heaven’s records show that all our sins have been blotted out. Yes, our merciful God is willing to wipe all our sins away! No matter what you have done, Jesus has enough mercy to cover you. 

#GoodandEvil #Bible #UBP20 #Ep14</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="37" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="333"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:b-8yteM2bbk</id>
  <yt:videoId>b-8yteM2bbk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>LIVE Sabbath Service | June 13, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b-8yteM2bbk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-13T04:03:40+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-13T13:05:36+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>LIVE Sabbath Service | June 13, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/b-8yteM2bbk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/b-8yteM2bbk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description></media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="109" average="4.85" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3324"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:-hqTjqqdm7Q</id>
  <yt:videoId>-hqTjqqdm7Q</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Meaning of Baptism The Ultimate Spiritual Do Over  💧🔥</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-hqTjqqdm7Q"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-12T13:00:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-12T13:55:02+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Meaning of Baptism The Ultimate Spiritual Do Over  💧🔥</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/-hqTjqqdm7Q?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/-hqTjqqdm7Q/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Have you ever just wanted a do-over in life—like hitting the reset button in a video game or selecting “undo” in a document? The #Bible speaks of #baptism as a powerful way to wipe the slate clean and have a totally new start. “The New Life” will unlock the secret to experiencing an all-new abundant life today.

This will be a beautiful study about starting over. It will show you the way to leave the past behind and find real meaning and purpose in your life. 

This is the thirteenth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-new-life/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE NEW LIFE

Have you ever wanted to start over in life? The Bible tells us how we can get a new start.  In this study we will look at the new life– a fresh start that is available through Jesus.

Jesus came from Galilee to the Jordan river to be baptized by John. But John hesitates, knowing he is unworthy. “Jesus replied, ‘It should be done, for we must carry out all that God requires.’ So John agreed to baptize him” (Matthew 3:13-15). Jesus is immersed in the water. As Jesus comes out of the water His ministry begins.
 
Baptism is a crucial part of the Christian life. Not only was Jesus baptized as an example to us, but He also strongly admonished His people to be baptized. Baptism is a symbol of our willingness to accept the Gospel of Jesus. 

The Bible declares that there is only one true method of baptism. It clearly says in Ephesians 4:5, “One Lord, one faith, one baptism.” If so, then there is only one biblical method. We can’t go wrong by following Jesus’ example. 

When Christ was baptized, He went down into the water and came up out of the water. Jesus’ baptism was by full immersion! (Matthew 3: 16-17)

The whole person must be immersed, because the whole person has sinned. In fact, the Greek word “baptizo” or “baptize” means “to dip,” “to immerse.” Romans 6:3-4 says, “Or do you not know that as many of us as were baptized into Christ Jesus were baptized into His death? Therefore we were buried with Him through baptism into death, that just as Christ was raised from the dead by the glory of the Father, even so we also should walk in newness of life.” How can sprinkling or pouring convey this message? 

Baptism is not the end of the Christian life– it is just the beginning! So, accept God’s mercy and begin again with a clean slate! Peter said in Acts 2:38: “Repent, and let every one of you be baptized in the name of Jesus Christ for the remission of sins. . .” Accept the gift of the Holy Spirit’s guidance “. . . and you shall receive the gift of the Holy Spirit”. Accept your place in the family of God.

Through baptism, a person is unified with Christ (Galatians 3:27). Yes, when you are baptized your sins are forgiven. Not only is your life cleansed, but you also receive the Holy Spirit and become part of an international community of faith! 
 
#UBP20 #Ep13</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="21" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="261"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:yBRgu6Pj_MY</id>
  <yt:videoId>yBRgu6Pj_MY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>LIVE Vesper Service | June 12, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yBRgu6Pj_MY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-12T12:26:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-13T03:35:54+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>LIVE Vesper Service | June 12, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/yBRgu6Pj_MY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/yBRgu6Pj_MY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>LIVE Vesper Service | June 12, 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="21" average="4.81" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="826"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:X3dU0FI9UYc</id>
  <yt:videoId>X3dU0FI9UYc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Seventh day Adventist Church Claims to be the Remnant Church of Bible Prophecy  Is it True</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X3dU0FI9UYc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-11T13:00:13+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-11T13:54:26+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Seventh day Adventist Church Claims to be the Remnant Church of Bible Prophecy  Is it True</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/X3dU0FI9UYc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/X3dU0FI9UYc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Have you ever wondered if God has a true church on earth today? Does the Seventh-day Adventist Church fit the description of the remnant according to Bible prophecy?

This is a study that directly follows up on the previous topic. With a call to come out of Babylon, where do we go? In this topic, you will see—from the Bible—the identifying characteristics of God’s end-time remnant.

This is the twelveth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-remnant/


CAMI OETMAN
Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!


THE REMNANT
In the book of Revelation, God speaks of a dragon that makes war with the remnant people, because they have aligned themselves with God. We know that God is the winner of the battle with the dragon. So, how do we recognize this remnant movement who stand with God? 

Revelation tells us this remnant people will keep the commandments of God and have the testimony of Jesus Christ. 

What does it mean to keep the commandments of God? The Ten Commandments were given by God for all people and each commandment has a specific purpose and benefit for the people who obey its teachings. The very same people who keep these commandments will proclaim the three angels’ messages found in Revelation 14. 

The three angels’ messages are: 
The hour of God’s judgment has come. Worship Him who made heaven and earth (Revelation 14:7). God’s last-day church will call for worship of Him as Creator.
Babylon is fallen (Revelation 14:8). God’s church for today does not identify with Babylon. In Revelation 18:4 we see that this church must call people out of Babylon, saying “. . . Come out of her, my people, that ye be not partakers of her sins . . .”
Beware of the beast and his image and his mark (Revelation 14:9-11). God’s people today will tell others how to avoid the mark of the beast. Jesus says these are His three important last-day messages to take to the world. His people will carry out His instruction because they love Him and will warn the world out of their love for others.
So, now we know why it’s important to keep all of God’s commandments. What’s next? The remnant must also have “the testimony of Jesus Christ.” In Revelation 19:10, the Bible explains that “the testimony of Jesus is the spirit of prophecy.” This means that Revelation’s end-time people will also have the gift of prophecy, guided by the Holy Spirit. They will proclaim and teach Bible prophecies to the world. 

So what movement or group of people fit this description? Is there a church that does this today? Yes! Seventh-day Adventism is a rapidly growing Christian denomination, made up of over 18 million members participating in local conferences in over 215 countries. The Adventist movement honors God through teaching and application of a healthy lifestyle, supporting religious freedom and the separation of church and state, and spreading the gospel to every nation, kindred, tongue, and people. It is a movement that accepts men and women of all races, all language groups, all cultures and all creeds. 
 
Do you want to be one of those that keeps the commandments of God and has the testimony of Jesus? This group is open to anyone that believes in the Word of God. Do you feel Him calling you to continue in your walk with Him into more and more light? Today is the day to &quot;follow the lamb wherever He goes” (Revelation 14:4).

Have questions? Need prayer? Visit us at https://bible.awr.org/the-remnant/</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="32" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="547"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:7T7fbpFgbnM</id>
  <yt:videoId>7T7fbpFgbnM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Book of Revelation Predicted the Rise of Protestantism 🤯⛪️</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7T7fbpFgbnM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T13:00:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-10T13:52:15+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Book of Revelation Predicted the Rise of Protestantism 🤯⛪️</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/7T7fbpFgbnM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7T7fbpFgbnM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Is there a master puppeteer behind all that’s going on around the world? Beyond conspiracy theories, there is a clear answer, and #Revelation identifies it through a strange woman, “The Harlot.”

This episode will be a study on the book of Revelation and the rise of Babylon. The #Bible tells people to “come out of Babylon.” How can you know if you’re in it? In this master class, Babylon will be identified from historical  books and the Bible.

This is the eleventh episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-harlot/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE HARLOT

The book of Revelation illustrates two different women to describe two different systems of religion – one that follows Jesus and one that has separated itself from Jesus.

In Revelation 12, there is a striking symbol of a woman dressed in white. In prophecy, a pure woman symbolizes the bride of Jesus or the true church (see Jeremiah 6:2 and Ephesians 5). God compares His church to a beautiful, pure woman who is faithful to her true lover, Jesus. She is undefiled with the corruption of false doctrine.

In Revelation 17, another woman arises. This woman rides upon a scarlet colored beast and the Bible calls her a harlot woman. She has left her true lover, Jesus. The harlot is the apostate system of religion. In this chapter we find that Babylon is a fallen church system that has committed fornication with the kings of the earth, thus symbolizing that instead of gaining its power from God, it obtains its power from the state as it is united with earthly authorities (see Revelation 17:1). 

Verse 3 of Revelation 17 identifies the harlot as blasphemous. She claims to have the power to forgive sins and stand in the place of God (see John 10:33, Matthew 9:2-3).

Rev. 17:4 clearly identifies the dress of the harlot as being “arrayed in purple and scarlet, and adorned with gold and precious stones and pearls . . .” 

Furthermore, this harlot, Babylon, has “in her hand a golden cup full of abominations and the filthiness of her fornication” (Revelation 17:4). She is a fallen system of religion with false doctrine that has confused all the world.

Verse 5 of Revelation 17 says Babylon is a mother, which means she must have children. Protestant denominations came out of Catholicism but have retained some of her false doctrines. These are the daughters of the Mother church.

Furthermore, she is identified as great, clearly showing the parallel between literal Babylon and spiritual Babylon. Like physical Babylon, spiritual Babylon represents a man-made religion established by men, based on human teachings, established on human ideas. There is a form of man-made religion, built by human religious leaders, that stands in opposition to the power of the gospel and the true church that Jesus built. 

IDENTIFYING MARKS OF SPIRITUAL BABYLON BASED ON LITERAL BABYLON

 ·  Babylon has an earthly head who speaks for God and in place of God (see 2 Thessalonians 2:4 and Isaiah 37:16).
·   Babylon was the center of image worship through all of the Old Testament. 
·   It was the center of false teachings about death teaching the immortality of the soul.
·   Babylon was also the center of sun worship. All sun worship came through varying pagan channels (see Ezekiel 8:16). 

God abhors these false systems of worship as they are doctrines of devils. However, God dearly loves His people, even though they may be currently deceived. He warns them to leave Babylon and all its counterfeit teachings!

#UBP20 #Ep11</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="19" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="265"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:RgRL0Dd-qJc</id>
  <yt:videoId>RgRL0Dd-qJc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Clear Messages Live - &quot;Communication Part 2 (Love Languages)&quot;</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RgRL0Dd-qJc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-10T11:04:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-13T03:34:05+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Clear Messages Live - &quot;Communication Part 2 (Love Languages)&quot;</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/RgRL0Dd-qJc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RgRL0Dd-qJc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Clear Messages Live - June 10, 2020
Topic: &quot;Communication Part 2 (Love Language)&quot;
with Pr. Edgar Bryan Tolentino and Shallom Princesa</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="16" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="254"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:hNpQNJG4mCk</id>
  <yt:videoId>hNpQNJG4mCk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Is the Mark of the Beast a Chip, a Vaccine or Something All Together Different 🧐</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hNpQNJG4mCk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-09T13:00:14+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-09T14:02:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Is the Mark of the Beast a Chip, a Vaccine or Something All Together Different 🧐</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/hNpQNJG4mCk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/hNpQNJG4mCk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The mark of the beast has been a hot topic for centuries. Will it be a microchip in the wrist, a universal ID card, or a hidden DNA marker in a vaccine? What is it really? Does the #Bible have insight into this provocative question?

“The Mark” will provide a clear answer to this with an intriguing study on Revelation 13 and the topic of the mark of the beast. What is the mark? Does anyone have it now? How can it be avoided?

This is the tenth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at:

https://bible.awr.org/the-mark/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!THE MARKWhat is this mysterious Mark of the Beast?Who is the beast in the book of Revelation? Is it symbolic? And what does the number 666 really mean?

The good news is that Bible prophecy gives clear answers to these important questions. You’ll want to pay close attention in this episode’s look into The Mark.

In Revelation 13, the Apostle John writes that there are only two groups of people living on earth when Jesus Christ returns. There is the faithful group who worship God and have received His seal. And then there are those who worship the beast and receive a mark on their right hands or on their foreheads. Tragically, unless you know what the beast represents, you’re on track to receiving it.  

Thankfully, the Bible reveals what the Mark of the Beast means while revealing the identity of the beast.  

This beast of Revelation 13 is described as a worldwide religious and political power that would rule for 1,260 years. During this time, the beast would claim to be God and to have the power to forgive sins. Anyone who wouldn’t worship the beast would be persecuted, even to death.  

So, what religious and political power in history fits this identity? It is the Roman Catholic Church, a religious system that became a world power in 538 A.D. and declared itself as the head of all churches. During this time, the Papacy wiped out entire cities and populations in its effort to unite the world under its own religious system. However, in 1798, the Pope was taken captive and the Papal Roman empire crumbled. This is described in verse 3 as a deadly wound.

But the Bible says that this deadly wound would be healed. The beast appears to die but regains its power. Has this happened to the Papal Roman Catholic system?  

Today, the world looks to the Pope as its only hope for peace and unity.  Pope Francis has expressed his eagerness to unite Protestants back to the Catholic Church. To the honest observer, the beast has recovered from the deadly wound.  

Now that we know the unmistakable identity of the beast, what is his mark? The Catholic Record of London makes it clear by stating, “Sunday is our mark of authority . . . the church is above the Bible, and this transference of Sabbath Observance is proof of that fact.”  

The Mark of the Beast is the enforcement of the Papacy’s day of worship – Sunday. Satan gave this beast its power and uses it to work against God’s seal, which is His day – the seventh-day Sabbath.  

The issue is about worship. Do we choose God’s day or a day that man has honored? And could it be that this day of worship will be enforced once again by another world power? You may be surprised at the connection between the United States of America and this second beast in Revelation 13!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="59" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="897"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Eqprg-VuczQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>Eqprg-VuczQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Katotohanan Live - June 9, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Eqprg-VuczQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-09T11:42:31+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-13T03:34:22+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Katotohanan Live - June 9, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Eqprg-VuczQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Eqprg-VuczQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Katotohanan Live - June 9, 2020
with Bro. Johnson Amican and Pr. Bjorn Capiendo</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="15" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="254"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:tYLN9Yuv4qg</id>
  <yt:videoId>tYLN9Yuv4qg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Is Hell Real The One Thing Most Christians Don't Understand About Hell &amp; the Millenium 🔥🔥🔥</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tYLN9Yuv4qg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T13:00:57+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T13:57:56+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Is Hell Real The One Thing Most Christians Don't Understand About Hell &amp; the Millenium 🔥🔥🔥</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/tYLN9Yuv4qg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/tYLN9Yuv4qg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This study will show you a timeline of what will happen after Jesus’ Second Coming. There are many different theories about hell and whether it is a real place. Some believe that people will burn for eternity. Is that true? This in-depth masterclass will provide definitive answers directly from the Bible.  

Other questions that will be addressed include: 
   - How can a God who loves torture people in burning sulfur forever?
   - Is there a second chance to be ready after Jesus takes people to heaven? 
   - Is there an eternally burning hot spot in the middle of the earth? 
   - Is hell the invention of fanatics?
   - Is hell just a state of mind?
 
The Bible provides a provocative answer you cannot miss.

This is the ninth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-desolation/


ABOUT CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!


THE DESOLATION

After the second coming, Revelation 20 tells us that the saints will live and reign with Christ for a thousand years. During the thousand years– the millennium– the book of records will be opened. Saints will look at each person’s record and see the love and the justice of God in deciding their eternal destiny. We will even be able to see the record of the devil and his angels and help to decide their final punishment (1 Corinthians 6:3).

During this time, the devil will be confined to this planet (Revelation 20:2, 3). There will be no one else living on the earth. The devil will have no one to tempt, no war to instigate, no suffering to mastermind. Jailed by the circumstances of an empty planet, he will have time to reflect and to plan his final move.

At the end of the thousand years, God and His saints will return to the earth with the Holy City, the New Jerusalem (Revelation 21:2). God has promised, “Behold, I make all things new” (Revelation 21:5). This glorious third coming is the beginning of creating a new earth. Before this can start, however, one last chapter in the saga of sin must be written.

Our earth, battered and torn, having laid waste for a thousand years, is the scene of this final chapter in the conflict between God and the devil. As the Holy City settles into the Mount of Olives, the power of God gives life to all those who chose not to follow Him (Zechariah 14:4). Revelation 20 describes their number “as the sands of the sea” (Revelation 20:8). The devil will be “loosed out of his prison” and work to convince all these people that it would be easy to overthrow the Holy City, and forever be rid of God, His rules, and His people (Revelation 20:7).

The devil and his angels, with those of all generations who chose against God’s government, prepare to take over the Holy City. As they march toward the city, fire comes down from God out of heaven and devours them (Revelation 20:9).

This is referred to as God’s “strange act” (Isaiah 28:21). It is against His nature to destroy any of His creation. Yet, those who have repeatedly denied His love and despised His invitation of mercy will finally experience eternal separation from God. The effect of their decision is forever. They are forever gone. The fire that devours them is only momentary, but the consequences of that fire are eternal. Those who have chosen to stand with the devil and his angels receive their reward of eternal death. “This is the second death,” Revelation 20:14 states. The fires of hell are the resolution to the last great conflict. They devour those who have forever decided against God.

It is up to us to choose on which side of the Holy City’s walls we will be found. It is our free choice to accept the love of God and stand with Him through eternity, or to choose against Him and be forever separated from God. Will you accept His gift of life?

We want to pray with you. We want to rejoice with you. We want to help you find answers. Visit us today at awr.org/bible</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="27" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="269"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:mvZlePyTLFo</id>
  <yt:videoId>mvZlePyTLFo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>United Bible Study - Episode 11 - Jesus Wept</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mvZlePyTLFo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T12:00:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T12:00:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>United Bible Study - Episode 11 - Jesus Wept</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/mvZlePyTLFo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mvZlePyTLFo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>United Bible Study 
Topic: Jesus Wept
Season 1 | Episode 11

Hosted by: Pastor Bryan Tolentino
Panelist:
Glenn Amican
Mitch Derecho
Linette Tenorio
Dominic Carpentero</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="10" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="194"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:VKtQAOdnvxA</id>
  <yt:videoId>VKtQAOdnvxA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sharing the Vision - Season 3 - Episode 10 - The Great Truth Lost Sight Of</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VKtQAOdnvxA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T11:30:03+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T11:30:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sharing the Vision - Season 3 - Episode 10 - The Great Truth Lost Sight Of</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/VKtQAOdnvxA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/VKtQAOdnvxA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Sharing The Vision
Topic: The Great Truth Lost Sight Of
Season 3 | Episode 10

with Dr. Alexa Tajud and Pastor Edgar Bryan Tolentino</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="11" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="167"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:5mbjp6uS-4s</id>
  <yt:videoId>5mbjp6uS-4s</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Shh... Will the Second Coming be a Secret Discover the Truth  🤯</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5mbjp6uS-4s"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-07T13:00:18+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-07T13:49:36+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Shh... Will the Second Coming be a Secret Discover the Truth  🤯</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/5mbjp6uS-4s?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/5mbjp6uS-4s/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The second coming of Jesus will be the ultimate rescue mission. But will He take His followers in secret or will every eye able to see Him? This will be an in-depth study into the manner of the #SecondComing of Jesus straight from the #Bible.

With this world seemingly spiraling out of control toward certain doom, is there any hope? How will we survive? The Rescue will open our eyes to a plan to save all humanity.

This is the eighth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. #UBP20 #Ep08. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-rescue/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE RESCUE
Does it ever seem like the world is spiraling out of control? Do you ever get the feeling that the end of the world is almost here? The good news is that in the midst of all the chaos, you can be confident that God has a personal rescue plan for you. This plan is none other than the second coming of Jesus Christ!

Why should we learn about what Jesus’ second coming will look like? About 2,000 years ago, the people of Jerusalem were left stunned and unprepared because Jesus’ first coming didn’t match their expectations. Rather than coming as a glorious conqueror, Jesus came meekly as a little baby, born to a poor family. Unlike Jesus’ first coming, you won’t have to wait to hear the news of His second coming—it will be impossible to miss! Still, even though Jesus’ Second Coming will be visible to every eye and audible to every ear, it makes all the difference to know how He will return. 

The Bible declares that at Jesus’ second coming, “. . . every eye will see Him . . .” (Revelation 1:7). His second coming will not be a mysterious event in a desert or a secret rapture. Although some say that Jesus’ second coming will be a secret, the Bible actually warned us in advance against the thought. In Luke 17:23, Jesus tells us that someday people will falsely say “. . .‘Look here!’ or ‘Look there!’ . . .”, but we should not follow them. This is because any person who claims to be fulfilling Jesus’ second coming, but meets privately with a group or an individual, is only an impersonation. As lightning is visible from all angles in the sky, so will His coming be visible from all directions (Luke 17:24). And don’t expect to see Jesus walking down the streets of New York or Tokyo, either. When Jesus returns, the righteous will “. . . meet Him in the air.” (1 Thessalonians 4:17)!  Finally, Jesus reminds us that we must always be prepared because no one knows the exact time of His coming (Matthew 24:36).

Jesus’ second coming will be the climax of earth’s history. He will rescue His followers from death, pain, and disease. Those who have died following Jesus will come forth from the grave alive with new, indestructible bodies. The bodies of His faithful followers will be instantly transformed, as quickly as the “. . . the twinkling of an eye . . .” (1 Corinthians 15:51-52). Today is the day to choose to follow Him, because “. . . now is the day of salvation.” (2 Corinthians 6:2). Your eternal destiny is hanging on the choices you make. 

In John 14:2, 3 Jesus promised, “. . . I go to prepare a place for you. And if I go and prepare a place for you, I will come again and receive you to Myself, that where I am, there you may be also.” Jesus has prepared a beautiful home for us in heaven, so beautiful that no one can fully grasp just how glorious it will be (1 Corinthians 2:9). The best way to find out is to be ready to meet Him when He comes!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="18" average="4.78" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="326"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vZstmceDtQo</id>
  <yt:videoId>vZstmceDtQo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 11 | Ang Biblia at ang Propesiya</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vZstmceDtQo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-07T11:49:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-09T15:49:18+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 11 | Ang Biblia at ang Propesiya</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vZstmceDtQo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vZstmceDtQo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Tagalog Adult Sabbath School
Weekly Bible Lesson Review
Lesson 11, 2nd Quarter, 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="238" average="4.93" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="7590"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
