<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Hope Channel Philippines</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-06-28T12:51:18+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:hNpQNJG4mCk</id>
  <yt:videoId>hNpQNJG4mCk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Is the Mark of the Beast a Chip, a Vaccine or Something All Together Different 🧐</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hNpQNJG4mCk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-09T13:00:14+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-09T14:02:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Is the Mark of the Beast a Chip, a Vaccine or Something All Together Different 🧐</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/hNpQNJG4mCk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/hNpQNJG4mCk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The mark of the beast has been a hot topic for centuries. Will it be a microchip in the wrist, a universal ID card, or a hidden DNA marker in a vaccine? What is it really? Does the #Bible have insight into this provocative question?

“The Mark” will provide a clear answer to this with an intriguing study on Revelation 13 and the topic of the mark of the beast. What is the mark? Does anyone have it now? How can it be avoided?

This is the tenth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at:

https://bible.awr.org/the-mark/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!THE MARKWhat is this mysterious Mark of the Beast?Who is the beast in the book of Revelation? Is it symbolic? And what does the number 666 really mean?

The good news is that Bible prophecy gives clear answers to these important questions. You’ll want to pay close attention in this episode’s look into The Mark.

In Revelation 13, the Apostle John writes that there are only two groups of people living on earth when Jesus Christ returns. There is the faithful group who worship God and have received His seal. And then there are those who worship the beast and receive a mark on their right hands or on their foreheads. Tragically, unless you know what the beast represents, you’re on track to receiving it.  

Thankfully, the Bible reveals what the Mark of the Beast means while revealing the identity of the beast.  

This beast of Revelation 13 is described as a worldwide religious and political power that would rule for 1,260 years. During this time, the beast would claim to be God and to have the power to forgive sins. Anyone who wouldn’t worship the beast would be persecuted, even to death.  

So, what religious and political power in history fits this identity? It is the Roman Catholic Church, a religious system that became a world power in 538 A.D. and declared itself as the head of all churches. During this time, the Papacy wiped out entire cities and populations in its effort to unite the world under its own religious system. However, in 1798, the Pope was taken captive and the Papal Roman empire crumbled. This is described in verse 3 as a deadly wound.

But the Bible says that this deadly wound would be healed. The beast appears to die but regains its power. Has this happened to the Papal Roman Catholic system?  

Today, the world looks to the Pope as its only hope for peace and unity.  Pope Francis has expressed his eagerness to unite Protestants back to the Catholic Church. To the honest observer, the beast has recovered from the deadly wound.  

Now that we know the unmistakable identity of the beast, what is his mark? The Catholic Record of London makes it clear by stating, “Sunday is our mark of authority . . . the church is above the Bible, and this transference of Sabbath Observance is proof of that fact.”  

The Mark of the Beast is the enforcement of the Papacy’s day of worship – Sunday. Satan gave this beast its power and uses it to work against God’s seal, which is His day – the seventh-day Sabbath.  

The issue is about worship. Do we choose God’s day or a day that man has honored? And could it be that this day of worship will be enforced once again by another world power? You may be surprised at the connection between the United States of America and this second beast in Revelation 13!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="33" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="232"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Eqprg-VuczQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>Eqprg-VuczQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Katotohanan Live - June 9, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Eqprg-VuczQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-09T11:42:31+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-09T12:06:14+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Katotohanan Live - June 9, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Eqprg-VuczQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Eqprg-VuczQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Katotohanan Live - June 9, 2020
with Bro. Johnson Amican and Pr. Bjorn Capiendo</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="12" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="185"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:tYLN9Yuv4qg</id>
  <yt:videoId>tYLN9Yuv4qg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Is Hell Real The One Thing Most Christians Don't Understand About Hell &amp; the Millenium 🔥🔥🔥</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tYLN9Yuv4qg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T13:00:57+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T13:57:56+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Is Hell Real The One Thing Most Christians Don't Understand About Hell &amp; the Millenium 🔥🔥🔥</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/tYLN9Yuv4qg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/tYLN9Yuv4qg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This study will show you a timeline of what will happen after Jesus’ Second Coming. There are many different theories about hell and whether it is a real place. Some believe that people will burn for eternity. Is that true? This in-depth masterclass will provide definitive answers directly from the Bible.  

Other questions that will be addressed include: 
   - How can a God who loves torture people in burning sulfur forever?
   - Is there a second chance to be ready after Jesus takes people to heaven? 
   - Is there an eternally burning hot spot in the middle of the earth? 
   - Is hell the invention of fanatics?
   - Is hell just a state of mind?
 
The Bible provides a provocative answer you cannot miss.

This is the ninth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-desolation/


ABOUT CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!


THE DESOLATION

After the second coming, Revelation 20 tells us that the saints will live and reign with Christ for a thousand years. During the thousand years– the millennium– the book of records will be opened. Saints will look at each person’s record and see the love and the justice of God in deciding their eternal destiny. We will even be able to see the record of the devil and his angels and help to decide their final punishment (1 Corinthians 6:3).

During this time, the devil will be confined to this planet (Revelation 20:2, 3). There will be no one else living on the earth. The devil will have no one to tempt, no war to instigate, no suffering to mastermind. Jailed by the circumstances of an empty planet, he will have time to reflect and to plan his final move.

At the end of the thousand years, God and His saints will return to the earth with the Holy City, the New Jerusalem (Revelation 21:2). God has promised, “Behold, I make all things new” (Revelation 21:5). This glorious third coming is the beginning of creating a new earth. Before this can start, however, one last chapter in the saga of sin must be written.

Our earth, battered and torn, having laid waste for a thousand years, is the scene of this final chapter in the conflict between God and the devil. As the Holy City settles into the Mount of Olives, the power of God gives life to all those who chose not to follow Him (Zechariah 14:4). Revelation 20 describes their number “as the sands of the sea” (Revelation 20:8). The devil will be “loosed out of his prison” and work to convince all these people that it would be easy to overthrow the Holy City, and forever be rid of God, His rules, and His people (Revelation 20:7).

The devil and his angels, with those of all generations who chose against God’s government, prepare to take over the Holy City. As they march toward the city, fire comes down from God out of heaven and devours them (Revelation 20:9).

This is referred to as God’s “strange act” (Isaiah 28:21). It is against His nature to destroy any of His creation. Yet, those who have repeatedly denied His love and despised His invitation of mercy will finally experience eternal separation from God. The effect of their decision is forever. They are forever gone. The fire that devours them is only momentary, but the consequences of that fire are eternal. Those who have chosen to stand with the devil and his angels receive their reward of eternal death. “This is the second death,” Revelation 20:14 states. The fires of hell are the resolution to the last great conflict. They devour those who have forever decided against God.

It is up to us to choose on which side of the Holy City’s walls we will be found. It is our free choice to accept the love of God and stand with Him through eternity, or to choose against Him and be forever separated from God. Will you accept His gift of life?

We want to pray with you. We want to rejoice with you. We want to help you find answers. Visit us today at awr.org/bible</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="23" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="182"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:mvZlePyTLFo</id>
  <yt:videoId>mvZlePyTLFo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>United Bible Study - Episode 11 - Jesus Wept</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mvZlePyTLFo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T12:00:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T12:00:23+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>United Bible Study - Episode 11 - Jesus Wept</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/mvZlePyTLFo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mvZlePyTLFo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>United Bible Study 
Topic: Jesus Wept
Season 1 | Episode 11

Hosted by: Pastor Bryan Tolentino
Panelist:
Glenn Amican
Mitch Derecho
Linette Tenorio
Dominic Carpentero</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="7" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="139"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:VKtQAOdnvxA</id>
  <yt:videoId>VKtQAOdnvxA</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sharing the Vision - Season 3 - Episode 10 - The Great Truth Lost Sight Of</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VKtQAOdnvxA"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-08T11:30:03+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-08T11:30:04+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sharing the Vision - Season 3 - Episode 10 - The Great Truth Lost Sight Of</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/VKtQAOdnvxA?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/VKtQAOdnvxA/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Sharing The Vision
Topic: The Great Truth Lost Sight Of
Season 3 | Episode 10

with Dr. Alexa Tajud and Pastor Edgar Bryan Tolentino</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="6" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="100"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:5mbjp6uS-4s</id>
  <yt:videoId>5mbjp6uS-4s</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Shh... Will the Second Coming be a Secret Discover the Truth  🤯</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5mbjp6uS-4s"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-07T13:00:18+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-07T13:49:36+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Shh... Will the Second Coming be a Secret Discover the Truth  🤯</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/5mbjp6uS-4s?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/5mbjp6uS-4s/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The second coming of Jesus will be the ultimate rescue mission. But will He take His followers in secret or will every eye able to see Him? This will be an in-depth study into the manner of the #SecondComing of Jesus straight from the #Bible.

With this world seemingly spiraling out of control toward certain doom, is there any hope? How will we survive? The Rescue will open our eyes to a plan to save all humanity.

This is the eighth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. #UBP20 #Ep08. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-rescue/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE RESCUE
Does it ever seem like the world is spiraling out of control? Do you ever get the feeling that the end of the world is almost here? The good news is that in the midst of all the chaos, you can be confident that God has a personal rescue plan for you. This plan is none other than the second coming of Jesus Christ!

Why should we learn about what Jesus’ second coming will look like? About 2,000 years ago, the people of Jerusalem were left stunned and unprepared because Jesus’ first coming didn’t match their expectations. Rather than coming as a glorious conqueror, Jesus came meekly as a little baby, born to a poor family. Unlike Jesus’ first coming, you won’t have to wait to hear the news of His second coming—it will be impossible to miss! Still, even though Jesus’ Second Coming will be visible to every eye and audible to every ear, it makes all the difference to know how He will return. 

The Bible declares that at Jesus’ second coming, “. . . every eye will see Him . . .” (Revelation 1:7). His second coming will not be a mysterious event in a desert or a secret rapture. Although some say that Jesus’ second coming will be a secret, the Bible actually warned us in advance against the thought. In Luke 17:23, Jesus tells us that someday people will falsely say “. . .‘Look here!’ or ‘Look there!’ . . .”, but we should not follow them. This is because any person who claims to be fulfilling Jesus’ second coming, but meets privately with a group or an individual, is only an impersonation. As lightning is visible from all angles in the sky, so will His coming be visible from all directions (Luke 17:24). And don’t expect to see Jesus walking down the streets of New York or Tokyo, either. When Jesus returns, the righteous will “. . . meet Him in the air.” (1 Thessalonians 4:17)!  Finally, Jesus reminds us that we must always be prepared because no one knows the exact time of His coming (Matthew 24:36).

Jesus’ second coming will be the climax of earth’s history. He will rescue His followers from death, pain, and disease. Those who have died following Jesus will come forth from the grave alive with new, indestructible bodies. The bodies of His faithful followers will be instantly transformed, as quickly as the “. . . the twinkling of an eye . . .” (1 Corinthians 15:51-52). Today is the day to choose to follow Him, because “. . . now is the day of salvation.” (2 Corinthians 6:2). Your eternal destiny is hanging on the choices you make. 

In John 14:2, 3 Jesus promised, “. . . I go to prepare a place for you. And if I go and prepare a place for you, I will come again and receive you to Myself, that where I am, there you may be also.” Jesus has prepared a beautiful home for us in heaven, so beautiful that no one can fully grasp just how glorious it will be (1 Corinthians 2:9). The best way to find out is to be ready to meet Him when He comes!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="15" average="4.73" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="207"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vZstmceDtQo</id>
  <yt:videoId>vZstmceDtQo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 11 | Ang Biblia at ang Propesiya</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vZstmceDtQo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-07T11:49:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-09T15:49:18+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 11 | Ang Biblia at ang Propesiya</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vZstmceDtQo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vZstmceDtQo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Tagalog Adult Sabbath School
Weekly Bible Lesson Review
Lesson 11, 2nd Quarter, 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="74" average="4.95" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1559"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:m1xKGJ40y6c</id>
  <yt:videoId>m1xKGJ40y6c</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>After the Final Breath What Happens After You Die 🔎😴</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m1xKGJ40y6c"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-06T13:00:15+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-06T13:52:05+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>After the Final Breath What Happens After You Die 🔎😴</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/m1xKGJ40y6c?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/m1xKGJ40y6c/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>What happens 2 minutes after you die?  Is there life after #death? Is there reincarnation? What about karma? Answers can be found in the #Bible and they speak loudly from this episode: The Grave.

This episode will focus on the nature of man and what happens when you die. Great emphasis will be placed upon the reality that death is simply creation in reverse. The state of being during death is a simply unconscious rest awaiting the return of Jesus.

This is the seventh episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. #UBP20 #Ep07. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-grave/

CAMI OETMAN

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE GRAVE

 
Have you experienced the loss of a family member or a loved one? Have you ever found yourself questioning, what happens when you die? We often hear stories of people who have had death experiences; they recall seeing bright lights, visions of Heaven, and even having out-of-body experiences. There is much controversy surrounding the topic of life after death. There are a number of different beliefs that are held by Christians and non-Christians alike. Some believe that, after you die, your soul goes to Heaven or Hell. Others believe in reincarnation or that death is simply the end. The most reliable source we have, the Bible, provides us with a clear answer on what really happens after death.
 
Many of the beliefs that people have about death today originate from ancient Greek philosophy, which teaches that the soul is immortal– it can live separately from the body and have a life of its own. This means that even after we have died, we are able to think, feel, and communicate with those on Earth and in Heaven. In contrast, the Bible views death as creation, only in reverse. Ecclesiastes 12:7: “Then the dust will return to the earth as it was, and the spirit will return to God who gave it.” God does not allow the soul to keep living after the body has died, instead, He preserves their identity in His mind alone. Their spirit is returned to God in the form of His power.
 
The Bible consistently refers to death as a sleep, even Jesus himself acknowledges this in the account of Lazarus found in John 11:11-25. God promises that there will be no more pain and suffering in Heaven. If we were able to witness the problems our loved ones are facing on Earth while we are looking down on them, wouldn’t this bring more pain rather than joy? God in His mercy would rather let us sleep than allow us to watch helplessly as our loved ones continue their lives on Earth.
 
Satan uses these false ideas about death to deceive us. Fallen angels appear to us as messengers, impersonating dead friends and relatives in order to communicate with those who are seeking guidance from them. Many people find comfort in knowing that their loved ones are enjoying Heaven; and, without realizing it, they listen to evil spirits and devils. The Bible predicts that evil angels will give warnings and foretell the future– appearing to be reliable– so their false teachings are accepted. These angels will influence the nations of the world and lead them to end-time events. We should seek our information from the Bible only. Satan can only deceive those who give in to his temptations. Those who rely on God’s word and endeavor to follow the truth will be rescued. Jesus is available to you always; all you have to do is ask Him.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="42" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="542"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:FhisogWV5aI</id>
  <yt:videoId>FhisogWV5aI</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>LIVE Sabbath Worship | June 6, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FhisogWV5aI"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-06T04:44:59+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-06T09:13:45+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>LIVE Sabbath Worship | June 6, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/FhisogWV5aI?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/FhisogWV5aI/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Live Sabbath Worship by South Central Luzon Conference</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="99" average="4.96" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3777"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:PK20ORMC70Q</id>
  <yt:videoId>PK20ORMC70Q</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>When is The Sabbath Day according to the Bible 📖😱</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PK20ORMC70Q"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-05T13:00:14+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-05T13:49:14+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>When is The Sabbath Day according to the Bible 📖😱</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/PK20ORMC70Q?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PK20ORMC70Q/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Sabbath Day has always been Saturday according to the Bible. That's the seventh-day of the week. The Jews have always believed the Sabbath was Saturday. But Christians believe it is Sunday - who changed this and why does it matter so much?

The Bible predicts that a 'power' would change the 'times and the law'. This study will cover the gradual change of the Sabbath over the centuries. It will look at how it happened, why it happened, and who is behind this great deception. By the way, this 'power' is still operating today.

Have you ever been scammed? Did you know that one of the greatest scams in history has been bought by almost everyone on the planet? What is it? How can you and I avoid it? Don’t miss the answer in The Counterfeit.

This is the sith episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. #UBP20 #Ep06. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

https://bible.awr.org/the-counterfeit/

CAMI OETMAN
Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE COUNTERFEIT
In Exodus 20:8-11, the Bible clearly states that “the seventh day is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God.” So, why do so many rest and worship on a different day of the week? When is the Sabbath? Saturday or Sunday? Could it be that the Christian Church has allowed man’s tradition to overshadow God’s way? Finally, why does it matter which day is the true day of worship and which is the counterfeit sabbath?

The “first day,” or Sunday, is only mentioned eight times in the New Testament. Some of these verses describe how women returned to Jesus’ tomb on Sunday to finish preparing the body of Christ (Mark 16:1-2, Mark 16:9, Matthew 28:1, Luke 24:1, John 20:1). Jesus was crucified on Friday, called the “preparation day,” because they were to prepare for God’s holy Sabbath day, Saturday. Jesus then rested in the tomb on Sabbath, the “seventh day” of the week, and rose on Sunday, the “first day” of the week. 

If we look at other verses mentioning the “first day” in the New Testament, we see no hint of change.

Many Christians read in Luke 4:16 that Jesus, “as His custom was,” went to church on the Sabbath. Christ said in Matthew 24:20 that His disciples would be keeping the seventh-day Sabbath 40 years after the cross. So, Jesus didn’t change the Sabbath! The Bible promises in Hebrews 13:8, “Jesus Christ is the same yesterday, today, and forever.” 

God did not change the Sabbath, Jesus would not change the Sabbath, and the disciples could not change the Sabbath! (Acts 5:29) 

We can look to Bible prophecy to see how God’s Sabbath could have been changed to a counterfeit. In Daniel 7:2-3, Daniel saw four great beasts come up from the sea. Daniel describes the beasts as a lion, a bear, a leopard, and a beast with ten horns. Verse 17 states that the beasts represent four kings, or kingdoms.

Most Bible scholars agree that the fourth beast represents the Roman Empire. Daniel 7:8 says “I was considering the horns, and there was another horn, a little one, coming up among them . . . ” This little horn comes up among the first ten horns, after the fall of Rome.

Daniel 7:25 predicts, “He [the little horn] shall speak pompous words against the Most High, shall persecute the saints of the Most High, and shall intend to change times and laws . . .”

The Bible tells us that Sunday’s sacredness comes from the tradition of men, changed from the law of God. It is Jesus Himself in Matthew 15:3-9 who says “in vain they worship Me, teaching as doctrines the commandments of men.”

God says the Sabbath is a great sign. (Ezekiel 20:12; Exodus 31:16) It’s a sign of our loyalty to Christ. It is a sign that we can rest in the completed work of salvation through Christ. The Bible Sabbath matters so much to God that He wrote it in stone!

Are you willing to follow wherever Jesus leads? The road may be narrow, but the way of Jesus leads to the tree of life in the city of God.

Have questions? Need prayer? Visit us at awr.org/bible</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="34" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="552"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:z6O6fJ43Okg</id>
  <yt:videoId>z6O6fJ43Okg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>LIVE Vesper Service | June 5, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z6O6fJ43Okg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-05T12:56:21+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-05T14:22:47+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>LIVE Vesper Service | June 5, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/z6O6fJ43Okg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/z6O6fJ43Okg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>LIVE Vesper Service</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="44" average="4.91" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="999"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:0fwUTVN67dM</id>
  <yt:videoId>0fwUTVN67dM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Does God Still Expect The Sabbath Day to be Remembered 🤔</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0fwUTVN67dM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-04T13:00:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-04T13:45:25+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Does God Still Expect The Sabbath Day to be Remembered 🤔</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/0fwUTVN67dM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0fwUTVN67dM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This masterclass will cover The Sabbath Day as found in the fourth commandment. It will trace it’s history all the way from creation and then through the history of Israel into New Testament times. It will also look at the benefits for Christians today.

The world has increasingly forgotten about God and His ways. How is that possible? The answer is found in a day, which is The Authentic Seal. #theSabbathDay

This is the fifth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at:

http://awr.org/bible

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.

It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE AUTHENTIC SEAL
Have you ever wondered why people would put a seal on a letter or document? What does it stand for?

A seal bears the name, title and territory of its owner and conveys authority and ownership to the receiver of the message. In ancient times, wax seals were often used on contracts or treaties as an identifying mark of authority and authenticity. Did you know God uses a ‘seal’ to identify his followers and mark them for redemption? Surely, humans won’t receive a wax seal on their foreheads—so what is this seal?

The Sabbath is a seal of commitment and relationship. By observing the Sabbath, God’s followers show they belong to Him. So, how do you observe the Sabbath and when is it?

Humans are the only created beings that can discern right from wrong and the part of our brain that makes those choices is our prefrontal cortex which sits behind our foreheads. When we choose to “remember the Sabbath day” as it states in the fourth of ten commandments, we are choosing to be ‘sealed’ by God. The Sabbath exists to remind us who God is. He is Creator of Heaven and Earth.  

God said through the prophet Ezekiel “I gave them my Sabbaths as a sign between us, so they would know that I the Lord made them holy” (Ezekiel 20:12). God wants us to remember that He is our Creator and Redeemer. 

God created humans on the sixth day of creation–Friday. The very next day–Sabbath; He rested, blessed it and made it holy. God wants to spend valuable time with the creation He made in His image. This means He wants to spend time with you.

Did you know the Sabbath has existed since the very first week of creation and it was not intended for only a select group of people? God created the Sabbath with the intention of spending time with all people. The Sabbath existed long before God gave the commandments to Moses on Mount Sinai; Paul and the Christian Gentiles were still keeping the Sabbath holy long after Jesus died on the cross.

When God created the days of the week, each 24-hour period was marked by the rotation of the earth. The night portion preceded the day portion, which means that sunset is the first part of a new day. Each day of the week begins with the evening portion at sunset. So it makes sense that the Sabbath would begin Friday evening at sunset and continue until Saturday evening at sunset.

What more can God do to emphasize the permanence and importance of His holy Sabbath day? He spoke it with His voice, wrote it with His finger, and sent His own beloved Son Jesus as our example to live by. The disciples taught it and God’s believers will keep it on the New Earth throughout all of eternity.

When the Creator of the universe asks you to do something, it makes sense to follow His direction. Don’t you think? Especially when His motive for spending time with us is love.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="28" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="339"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Ga2HJvaMVng</id>
  <yt:videoId>Ga2HJvaMVng</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Ten Commandments A Guide to Show God's Love to Others 🤲🏽❤️</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ga2HJvaMVng"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-03T13:00:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-03T13:30:46+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Ten Commandments A Guide to Show God's Love to Others 🤲🏽❤️</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Ga2HJvaMVng?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/Ga2HJvaMVng/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Would applying the Ten Commandments given to Moses change society? What has happened to the values of yesteryear? How has our society become so self-centered, disrespectful, and entitled? Is there a better way?  Is it possible that we’ve forgotten our most foundational values? 

There is a different path, The Way reveals that journey. This masterclass will explore the Ten Commandments and what they mean, how they apply and do they have any significance in the life of a Christian.
  
This is the fourth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

http://awr.org/bible

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.

It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE WAY

While in today’s world, everyone seems to have a different definition of what is right and wrong, God has outlined a clear standard for morality. In Exodus chapter 20 God has given us the Ten Commandments to show us the way to love and freedom. The first four commandments show us how to have a relationship with God, while the last six commandments deal with our relationship with each other.

In the first four commandments, we find that God desires us to acknowledge Him as our Creator and to give Him first place in our lives (Commandment #1). He desires us to worship Him “in spirit and in truth” (John 4:24) rather than through man-made idols (Commandment #2). God asks us to respect His name as a sign of our loyalty to Him (Commandment #3). Furthermore, God asks us to keep His Sabbath day holy and spend a 24-hour period in worship and thanksgiving with Him (Commandment #4).

The last six commandments admonish us to honor our parents (Commandment #5); leave off acts of harm such as hate, anger, revenge and murder (Commandment #6); stay true to our marriage vows (Commandment #7); not take anything that is not rightfully ours (Commandment #8); not involve ourselves in lying or gossiping (Commandment #9); and calls us to be content with what we have trusting that God will provide everything that we need (Commandment #10).

God’s law is like a wall of protection, prohibiting us from falling into one of the many landmines of sin. It is God’s desire for man and woman to be happy and live in peace. Obeying God’s rules will save us from learning things the hard way, but by themselves they won’t give us a personal experience with God. In fact, a list of rules without having an actual experience with God can be a miserable experience. 
The reason we obey is not because we are trying to earn God’s favor. It’s the response of our love for Him. Will you choose to follow His way today?

Have questions? Need prayer? Visit us at awr.org/bible</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="36" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="448"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:BqztLmxD3uY</id>
  <yt:videoId>BqztLmxD3uY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Clear Messages - &quot;Communication&quot; - June 3, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BqztLmxD3uY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-03T11:07:24+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-03T11:19:40+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Clear Messages - &quot;Communication&quot; - June 3, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/BqztLmxD3uY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/BqztLmxD3uY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Clear Messages - June 3, 2020
Topic: Communication
with Pr. Edgar Bryan Tolentino and Shallom Princesa</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="17" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="246"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vVjxGh2Olg0</id>
  <yt:videoId>vVjxGh2Olg0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Does the Book of Revelation Bring Good News for Judgement Day  ⚖️ 🤔</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vVjxGh2Olg0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-02T13:00:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-02T13:40:37+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Does the Book of Revelation Bring Good News for Judgement Day  ⚖️ 🤔</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vVjxGh2Olg0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vVjxGh2Olg0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This will be a masterclass on Revelation 14. We have seen polarizing politics, increased hate crimes, hunger for power, and the oppression of the poor. Is there a lasting solution to all of these problems? The Warning provides a framework for understanding that there is a day of reckoning and how you can be safe.

The book of Revelation presents the Gospel message being the good news of Jesus' saving grace. That good news also comes in the form of a somber warning that there is an end coming where the world will be judged. God calls for each of us to be ready.

This is the third episode in the AWR masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

http://awr.org/bible

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE WARNING

Do you seek relief from the things that you’ve done wrong?  Are you searching for peace in place of anxiety and fear?  You’re not alone.  In this look at what God says about the end of time, you’ll leave your fears behind and find new hope in God’s love for you!

God has often sent warnings before disasters strike.  Inspired by God, Noah warned of a worldwide flood that destroyed the earth just as Joseph forewarned Pharaoh of a devastating famine.  And God has sent another warning to you and me to prepare for the end of time.  

In Revelation 14:6-9, we find this final message of warning.  The good news is that it is wrapped in God’s love for us.  It is known as the “everlasting gospel.”  A message reminding us that God willingly let His only son be put to death to pay for our sins.  

How encouraging!  Though we must face God’s judgement, He has provided a way to ensure our forgiveness through Jesus!  And this forgiveness also opens the door for eternal life with Him in heaven!

The first angel gives the warning to “fear God” and to “give glory to Him.”  These instructions show our need to obey God’s law and to follow His teachings for how to live our lives.  (See Ecclesiastes 12:13 and 1 Corinthians 10:31)  

Next, the angel turns to the issue of worship.  You see, we live in an age where millions reject God as our Creator.  In this message of warning, God is calling the world to worship him as our Creator God.  

Why is this message so important?  The angel says that “the hour of His judgement is come.”  This indicates that God is doing the judging now.  A time of investigation is taking place before Jesus comes so that He will know who gets the reward of eternal life.  (See Revelation 22:12)

Could it be that we are living in this time of judgement?  Is our future being decided by the choices we make today?  This can be scary to think about, right?  

The good news is that God has warned us ahead of time.  We don’t need to be afraid.  He wants us to be ready and has opened the way for us to have everlasting life!

The second and third angels focus on truth and error.  Many people are being misled by following the false teachings of men rather than listening to God’s Word.  The warnings of these two angels are some of the most serious in all of the Bible.  

Don’t worry.  In upcoming videos, we will look into the meaning of Babylon and the Mark of the Beast.  Just remember that God’s Word is our source of safety and of truth!  (See John 17:17)

The key takeaway from this final warning is that you can be prepared to stand before God in this judgement.  Through the messages of the three angels, God has provided a way for the world to be ready when He returns to earth.  

God is preparing a group of people who will worship Him as Creator.  They will obey Him because they love Him.  And this group of individuals will stand up for Jesus no matter what happens.  

Have you come to a place where you want to give your life to God?  Do you want forgiveness, peace, and the assurance of God’s love?  Take this moment and give Him your heart!

Have questions?  Need prayer?  Visit us at awr.org/bible</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="41" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="546"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
