<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
 <title>Hope Channel Philippines</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg"/>
 <author>
  <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
  <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2006-06-28T12:51:18+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:0fwUTVN67dM</id>
  <yt:videoId>0fwUTVN67dM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Does God Still Expect The Sabbath Day to be Remembered 🤔</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0fwUTVN67dM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-04T13:00:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-04T13:45:25+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Does God Still Expect The Sabbath Day to be Remembered 🤔</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/0fwUTVN67dM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0fwUTVN67dM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This masterclass will cover The Sabbath Day as found in the fourth commandment. It will trace it’s history all the way from creation and then through the history of Israel into New Testament times. It will also look at the benefits for Christians today.

The world has increasingly forgotten about God and His ways. How is that possible? The answer is found in a day, which is The Authentic Seal. #theSabbathDay

This is the fifth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at:

http://awr.org/bible

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.

It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE AUTHENTIC SEAL
Have you ever wondered why people would put a seal on a letter or document? What does it stand for?

A seal bears the name, title and territory of its owner and conveys authority and ownership to the receiver of the message. In ancient times, wax seals were often used on contracts or treaties as an identifying mark of authority and authenticity. Did you know God uses a ‘seal’ to identify his followers and mark them for redemption? Surely, humans won’t receive a wax seal on their foreheads—so what is this seal?

The Sabbath is a seal of commitment and relationship. By observing the Sabbath, God’s followers show they belong to Him. So, how do you observe the Sabbath and when is it?

Humans are the only created beings that can discern right from wrong and the part of our brain that makes those choices is our prefrontal cortex which sits behind our foreheads. When we choose to “remember the Sabbath day” as it states in the fourth of ten commandments, we are choosing to be ‘sealed’ by God. The Sabbath exists to remind us who God is. He is Creator of Heaven and Earth.  

God said through the prophet Ezekiel “I gave them my Sabbaths as a sign between us, so they would know that I the Lord made them holy” (Ezekiel 20:12). God wants us to remember that He is our Creator and Redeemer. 

God created humans on the sixth day of creation–Friday. The very next day–Sabbath; He rested, blessed it and made it holy. God wants to spend valuable time with the creation He made in His image. This means He wants to spend time with you.

Did you know the Sabbath has existed since the very first week of creation and it was not intended for only a select group of people? God created the Sabbath with the intention of spending time with all people. The Sabbath existed long before God gave the commandments to Moses on Mount Sinai; Paul and the Christian Gentiles were still keeping the Sabbath holy long after Jesus died on the cross.

When God created the days of the week, each 24-hour period was marked by the rotation of the earth. The night portion preceded the day portion, which means that sunset is the first part of a new day. Each day of the week begins with the evening portion at sunset. So it makes sense that the Sabbath would begin Friday evening at sunset and continue until Saturday evening at sunset.

What more can God do to emphasize the permanence and importance of His holy Sabbath day? He spoke it with His voice, wrote it with His finger, and sent His own beloved Son Jesus as our example to live by. The disciples taught it and God’s believers will keep it on the New Earth throughout all of eternity.

When the Creator of the universe asks you to do something, it makes sense to follow His direction. Don’t you think? Especially when His motive for spending time with us is love.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="14" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="111"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Ga2HJvaMVng</id>
  <yt:videoId>Ga2HJvaMVng</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Ten Commandments A Guide to Show God's Love to Others 🤲🏽❤️</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ga2HJvaMVng"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-03T13:00:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-03T13:30:46+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Ten Commandments A Guide to Show God's Love to Others 🤲🏽❤️</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Ga2HJvaMVng?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/Ga2HJvaMVng/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Would applying the Ten Commandments given to Moses change society? What has happened to the values of yesteryear? How has our society become so self-centered, disrespectful, and entitled? Is there a better way?  Is it possible that we’ve forgotten our most foundational values? 

There is a different path, The Way reveals that journey. This masterclass will explore the Ten Commandments and what they mean, how they apply and do they have any significance in the life of a Christian.
  
This is the fourth episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

http://awr.org/bible

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.

It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE WAY

While in today’s world, everyone seems to have a different definition of what is right and wrong, God has outlined a clear standard for morality. In Exodus chapter 20 God has given us the Ten Commandments to show us the way to love and freedom. The first four commandments show us how to have a relationship with God, while the last six commandments deal with our relationship with each other.

In the first four commandments, we find that God desires us to acknowledge Him as our Creator and to give Him first place in our lives (Commandment #1). He desires us to worship Him “in spirit and in truth” (John 4:24) rather than through man-made idols (Commandment #2). God asks us to respect His name as a sign of our loyalty to Him (Commandment #3). Furthermore, God asks us to keep His Sabbath day holy and spend a 24-hour period in worship and thanksgiving with Him (Commandment #4).

The last six commandments admonish us to honor our parents (Commandment #5); leave off acts of harm such as hate, anger, revenge and murder (Commandment #6); stay true to our marriage vows (Commandment #7); not take anything that is not rightfully ours (Commandment #8); not involve ourselves in lying or gossiping (Commandment #9); and calls us to be content with what we have trusting that God will provide everything that we need (Commandment #10).

God’s law is like a wall of protection, prohibiting us from falling into one of the many landmines of sin. It is God’s desire for man and woman to be happy and live in peace. Obeying God’s rules will save us from learning things the hard way, but by themselves they won’t give us a personal experience with God. In fact, a list of rules without having an actual experience with God can be a miserable experience. 
The reason we obey is not because we are trying to earn God’s favor. It’s the response of our love for Him. Will you choose to follow His way today?

Have questions? Need prayer? Visit us at awr.org/bible</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="33" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="298"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:BqztLmxD3uY</id>
  <yt:videoId>BqztLmxD3uY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Clear Messages - &quot;Communication&quot; - June 3, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BqztLmxD3uY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-03T11:07:24+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-03T11:19:40+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Clear Messages - &quot;Communication&quot; - June 3, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/BqztLmxD3uY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/BqztLmxD3uY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Clear Messages - June 3, 2020
Topic: Communication
with Pr. Edgar Bryan Tolentino and Shallom Princesa</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="16" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="197"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:vVjxGh2Olg0</id>
  <yt:videoId>vVjxGh2Olg0</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Does the Book of Revelation Bring Good News for Judgement Day  ⚖️ 🤔</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vVjxGh2Olg0"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-02T13:00:11+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-02T13:40:37+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Does the Book of Revelation Bring Good News for Judgement Day  ⚖️ 🤔</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/vVjxGh2Olg0?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vVjxGh2Olg0/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This will be a masterclass on Revelation 14. We have seen polarizing politics, increased hate crimes, hunger for power, and the oppression of the poor. Is there a lasting solution to all of these problems? The Warning provides a framework for understanding that there is a day of reckoning and how you can be safe.

The book of Revelation presents the Gospel message being the good news of Jesus' saving grace. That good news also comes in the form of a somber warning that there is an end coming where the world will be judged. God calls for each of us to be ready.

This is the third episode in the AWR masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: 

http://awr.org/bible

Ten years ago, Cami Oetman had a real encounter with God that would change her life forever. She was a successful entrepreneur at the time, and the transition wasn’t easy. However, the truth Cami will share in this series was so compelling that she knew every human being in the world should experience the love of Jesus as she had.

Within three years, she had preached 350 Bible presentations. Today, as a vice president for Adventist World Radio, Cami travels the world documenting the miracles that take place when people give their hearts to Jesus.
It may seem difficult to imagine yourself understanding Bible prophecy. 

Cami couldn’t either. She had spent two decades in the modeling world — in front of and behind the camera. She had also used her master’s degree in social work to care for hospice patients. She then started a successful retail business. But no one can predict how they will react when they have a real experience with God!

THE WARNING

Do you seek relief from the things that you’ve done wrong?  Are you searching for peace in place of anxiety and fear?  You’re not alone.  In this look at what God says about the end of time, you’ll leave your fears behind and find new hope in God’s love for you!

God has often sent warnings before disasters strike.  Inspired by God, Noah warned of a worldwide flood that destroyed the earth just as Joseph forewarned Pharaoh of a devastating famine.  And God has sent another warning to you and me to prepare for the end of time.  

In Revelation 14:6-9, we find this final message of warning.  The good news is that it is wrapped in God’s love for us.  It is known as the “everlasting gospel.”  A message reminding us that God willingly let His only son be put to death to pay for our sins.  

How encouraging!  Though we must face God’s judgement, He has provided a way to ensure our forgiveness through Jesus!  And this forgiveness also opens the door for eternal life with Him in heaven!

The first angel gives the warning to “fear God” and to “give glory to Him.”  These instructions show our need to obey God’s law and to follow His teachings for how to live our lives.  (See Ecclesiastes 12:13 and 1 Corinthians 10:31)  

Next, the angel turns to the issue of worship.  You see, we live in an age where millions reject God as our Creator.  In this message of warning, God is calling the world to worship him as our Creator God.  

Why is this message so important?  The angel says that “the hour of His judgement is come.”  This indicates that God is doing the judging now.  A time of investigation is taking place before Jesus comes so that He will know who gets the reward of eternal life.  (See Revelation 22:12)

Could it be that we are living in this time of judgement?  Is our future being decided by the choices we make today?  This can be scary to think about, right?  

The good news is that God has warned us ahead of time.  We don’t need to be afraid.  He wants us to be ready and has opened the way for us to have everlasting life!

The second and third angels focus on truth and error.  Many people are being misled by following the false teachings of men rather than listening to God’s Word.  The warnings of these two angels are some of the most serious in all of the Bible.  

Don’t worry.  In upcoming videos, we will look into the meaning of Babylon and the Mark of the Beast.  Just remember that God’s Word is our source of safety and of truth!  (See John 17:17)

The key takeaway from this final warning is that you can be prepared to stand before God in this judgement.  Through the messages of the three angels, God has provided a way for the world to be ready when He returns to earth.  

God is preparing a group of people who will worship Him as Creator.  They will obey Him because they love Him.  And this group of individuals will stand up for Jesus no matter what happens.  

Have you come to a place where you want to give your life to God?  Do you want forgiveness, peace, and the assurance of God’s love?  Take this moment and give Him your heart!

Have questions?  Need prayer?  Visit us at awr.org/bible</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="39" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="401"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:YHo7_Q1Q-aY</id>
  <yt:videoId>YHo7_Q1Q-aY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Katotohanan LIVE | June 2, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YHo7_Q1Q-aY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-02T11:39:46+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-02T11:54:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Katotohanan LIVE | June 2, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/YHo7_Q1Q-aY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/YHo7_Q1Q-aY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Katotohanan LIVE | June 2, 2020 | with Bro. Johnson Amican &amp; Ptr. Bjon Capiendo</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="9" average="4.56" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="192"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:WIhrwUiT0sU</id>
  <yt:videoId>WIhrwUiT0sU</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Second Coming of Jesus: The Bible Reveals COVID-19 is a Sign</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WIhrwUiT0sU"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-01T13:53:30+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-01T14:37:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Second Coming of Jesus: The Bible Reveals COVID-19 is a Sign</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/WIhrwUiT0sU?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/WIhrwUiT0sU/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Follow
Is Covid-19 one of the signs of the second coming of Jesus? Do you wonder if the rise of natural disasters is a warning that the end might be near?

This masterclass will give an in-depth look at answers that may surprise you. This study will explore Matthew chapter 24 which focuses on the signs of the end-times. In addition, it points to the hope of the second coming of Jesus Christ.

This is the second episode in the AWR Masterclass series called Unlocking Bible Prophecies. You can follow the series and interact LIVE at: https://awr.org/bible
#BibleProphecies #UBP20</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="32" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="315"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kiRbkCtEG_o</id>
  <yt:videoId>kiRbkCtEG_o</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>United Bible Study - Episode 10 - I Am The Way</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kiRbkCtEG_o"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-01T12:00:16+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-01T12:00:16+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>United Bible Study - Episode 10 - I Am The Way</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kiRbkCtEG_o?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kiRbkCtEG_o/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>United Bible Study 
Topic: I Am The Way
Season 1 | Episode 10

Hosted by: Pastor Bryan Tolentino
Panelist:
Glenn Amican
Mitch Derecho
Linette Tenorio
Dominic Carpentero</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="9" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="109"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:jaa7RFHgAZk</id>
  <yt:videoId>jaa7RFHgAZk</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Sharing The Vision - Season 3 - Episode 9 - Danger in Depending Upon Human Plans and Methods</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jaa7RFHgAZk"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-06-01T11:30:06+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-01T11:30:07+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Sharing The Vision - Season 3 - Episode 9 - Danger in Depending Upon Human Plans and Methods</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/jaa7RFHgAZk?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jaa7RFHgAZk/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Sharing The Vision
Topic: Danger in Depending Upon Human Plans and Methods
Season 3 | Episode 9

with Dr. Alexa Tajud and Pastor Edgar Bryan Tolentino</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="22" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="334"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Xbe0WuVhoK4</id>
  <yt:videoId>Xbe0WuVhoK4</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Prophecy Fulfilled: Cami Unlocks Bible Prophecies in 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xbe0WuVhoK4"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T14:35:32+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-31T15:15:18+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Prophecy Fulfilled: Cami Unlocks Bible Prophecies in 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Xbe0WuVhoK4?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Xbe0WuVhoK4/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>This masterclass will explore the prophecy of Daniel chapter 2 which gives a prediction of the rise and fall of major world empires. This prophecy demonstrates the reliability of the Bible and shows that God can be trusted.
#Bible_Prophecy #UBP20</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="16" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="270"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:PGPQ7lUsU8A</id>
  <yt:videoId>PGPQ7lUsU8A</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 10 | Ang Biblia Bilang Kasaysayan</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PGPQ7lUsU8A"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-31T12:52:18+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-04T06:33:13+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Oras ng Pag-aaral 2nd Quarter 2020 | Lesson 10 | Ang Biblia Bilang Kasaysayan</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/PGPQ7lUsU8A?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/PGPQ7lUsU8A/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Tagalog Adult Sabbath School
Weekly Bible Lesson Review
Lesson 10, 2nd Quarter, 2020</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="109" average="4.85" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2430"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:0DzU-yr6qZs</id>
  <yt:videoId>0DzU-yr6qZs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>LIVE Sabbath Worship | May 30, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0DzU-yr6qZs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-30T04:15:12+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-01T10:05:33+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>LIVE Sabbath Worship | May 30, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/0DzU-yr6qZs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0DzU-yr6qZs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description></media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="108" average="4.89" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4101"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:n-bm1TInLiM</id>
  <yt:videoId>n-bm1TInLiM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>LIVE Vesper Service | May 29, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n-bm1TInLiM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-29T12:16:58+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-04T13:30:08+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>LIVE Vesper Service | May 29, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/n-bm1TInLiM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/n-bm1TInLiM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description></media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="40" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="972"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:BIERhdxRjyY</id>
  <yt:videoId>BIERhdxRjyY</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>LIVE Vesper Service | May 29, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BIERhdxRjyY"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-29T11:00:20+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-06-02T00:59:50+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>LIVE Vesper Service | May 29, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/BIERhdxRjyY?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/BIERhdxRjyY/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description></media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="18" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="306"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:7MTjjIGqn2o</id>
  <yt:videoId>7MTjjIGqn2o</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</yt:channelId>
  <title>Clear Messages Live | &quot;Respect&quot; | May 27, 2020</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7MTjjIGqn2o"/>
  <author>
   <name>Hope Channel Philippines</name>
   <uri>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2TBTBs9-HYCWLtnpW45cg</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2020-05-27T11:10:00+00:00</published>
  <updated>2020-05-27T11:25:05+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Clear Messages Live | &quot;Respect&quot; | May 27, 2020</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/7MTjjIGqn2o?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7MTjjIGqn2o/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Clear Messages Live | &quot;Respect&quot; | May 27, 2020
with Pastor Edgar Bryan Tolentino and Shallom Princesa</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="17" average="5.00" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="274"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
