<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--  RSS generated by APN on Sat, 30 May 2020 01:16:31 +1200 --><rss version="2.0" xmlns:nzh-sem="https://www.nzherald.co.nz/schema/xml/rss-sem-metadata">
	<channel>
		<title>New Zealand Herald - Top Stories</title>
		<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/</link>
		<description>Latest Content for New Zealand Herald</description>
		<language>en-nz</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2009 APN HOLDINGS NZ</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 01:16:31 +1200</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>APN RSS Generator</generator>
		<managingEditor>webnews@nzherald.co.nz</managingEditor>
		<webMaster>webmaster@nzherald.co.nz</webMaster>
		<image>
			<title>New Zealand Herald - Top Stories</title>
			<url>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/images/rssLogo.png</url>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/headlines.cfm?c_id=1</link>
		</image>
		
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Washington DC, United States, Crime, Trump, Assault and Homicide, Spotlight, World</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>'F*** Trump': White House in lockdown amid escalating protests</title>
			<description> The White House in the US is currently in lockdown, as protests escalate over the death of George Floyd.

NBC News White House correspondent Peter Alexander said on Twitter that he was on lockdown inside ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=12336022&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 12:44:46 +1200</pubDate>
			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202022/GettyImages-1216203538_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=Jamela J. Pettiford sings during a protest with Former NBA player Stephen Jackson in response to the police killing of George Floyd. Photo / Getty Images"/>

			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Drug Abuse, Euthanasia, NZ Government, Health, Election 2020, Media  and  Publishing Industry, Marketing, Advertising, Business, Premium, Legislation</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>The man charged with informing Kiwis about cannabis and euthanasia</title>
			<description> Paul Wilson isn't the whiskey-swilling, chain-smoking advertising cliché we've come to expect from the characters in shows like Mad Men.      

The softly spoken Saatchi &amp; Saatchi boss is instead the ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12335892&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 12:43:31 +1200</pubDate>
			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202022/saatchiinterviw_70x70.png?media_subtype_id=16|caption=Saatchi &amp; Saatchi managing director Paul Wilson. Photo / Supplied"/>

			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202022/2D4PBX6F7JGD3IRHEHOAIBTMZE_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=The right of New Zealanders to choose when to end their lives has already sparked some fierce debate. Photo / Getty Images"/>

			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202022/GettyImages-1197357587_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=New Zealanders will be required to vote on the legality of recreational cannabis. Photo / Getty Images"/>

			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Rotorua Daily Post, Northern Advocate, Hawkes Bay Today, Wanganui Chronicle, Bay of Plenty Times, Coronavirus, National, Politics, NZ Government</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Live: There are no new Covid-19 cases, one active case</title>
			<description> STAY IN THE KNOW.  SIGN UP TO OUR DAILY NEWSLETTERS HERE.  

There are no new Covid-19 cases in New Zealand for the eighth day in a row and still one active case.

Our total number of confirmed and probable ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12336024&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 12:42:16 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Business, Premium, Opinion, Best of Business Analysis, Markets</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Capital moves raise questions for shareholders</title>
			<description> COMMENT: 

The economic impact of Covid-19 has resulted in a plethora of listed companies raising cash on the market. Kathmandu (raising $207 million) and Auckland Airport ($1.2 billion) were first to ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12335878&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 12:07:11 +1200</pubDate>
			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202022/A_170119NZHJOCANNABIS13_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=Medical Cannabis researchers Nic Foreman (left) and Mark Lucas of Cannasouth Plant Research. Photo / Jason Oxenham"/>

			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202022/NZX2-File_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=The NZX is chock-full of profitable companies which have a relatively high share price relative to what they earn (ie, Price/Earnings ratio). Photo / File"/>

			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Sexual Assault, National, Crime</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Man films Tinder rape on victim's phone</title>
			<description> Warning: Distressing content 

A man who raped his Tinder date and filmed the attack on her mobile phone has lost a Court of Appeal bid for freedom.

Joel Nathan Creighton was found guilty of raping the ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335983&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:32:07 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Premium, National, Politics, Coronavirus, NZ Government, Health</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Top expert dismisses calls to move to alert level 1 as 'ignorant'</title>
			<description> Top epidemiologist Sir David Skegg says anyone crying out for an immediate move to alert level 1 is either ignorant or trying to score political points.

The Otago University professor is warning that ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335817&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:27:59 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>United States, North America, New Zealand, Dunedin, Tourism  and  Leisure Industries, National, Immigration, Coronavirus</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>50,000 tourists still in New Zealand after lockdown</title>
			<description> There are more than 50,000 tourists hunkering down in New Zealand at the moment; only 3000 left the country after lockdown ended.

Figures released to the Herald by Immigration New Zealand show, as of ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335841&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:25:55 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Auckland Region, Auckland Central, Premium, Retail Trade, Retailing, Coronavirus, Business</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Watch: First look inside Commercial Bay - opening date revealed</title>
			<description> Precinct Properties' $1 billion development Commercial Bay will open its doors to the public for the first time on June 11 after four years under construction.

The three-level retail precinct in downtown ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12334886&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:24:53 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Dunedin, Sexual Assault, Crime, National</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>'I blame myself': Sex assault victim feels guilt for clothes she wore</title>
			<description> Warning: Distressing content 

A woman repeatedly groped by a student at a Dunedin street party says she feels guilty about her choice of clothing that day.

Patrick John Hessian (20) appeared in the ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335976&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:23:52 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Premium, Sport, Hockey, Black Sticks (women), Premium Sport</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Olympic mutiny: Star players threaten to quit 'divided' Black Sticks</title>
			<description> Drama continues to engulf the Black Sticks women's hockey programme, with a squad divided between those still loyal to former coach Mark Hager and those who believe the programme needs a cultural overhaul.

The ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/sport/news/article.cfm?c_id=4&amp;objectid=12335867&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:08:05 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>National, Hospitals, Coronavirus, Health</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>'There was nothing more they could do': Four mums die after treatment at country's largest hospital</title>
			<description> The country's largest hospital has launched a review after four women died during or soon after pregnancy this year.

 Only one maternal death was recorded at Auckland City Hospital in three years, but ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335747&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 10:52:18 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Whangarei, Wellington, Thames-Coromandel District, Tauranga, Queenstown, Northland, Napier, Hamilton, Gisborne, Christchurch, Auckland Region, Roads, Road Safety, North Island, South Island, Coronavirus, Tourism  and  Leisure Industries, National, Weather</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Busy roads, heavy rain and flood warnings: Warning for holidaymakers</title>
			<description> Auckland is awakening to blue skies this morning but motorists are urged to take care as showers are expected and residents are likely to take to the roads early for the long weekend break.

Authorities ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335972&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 10:36:55 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>United States, World</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Minneapolis cop charged with murder after kneeling on neck</title>
			<description> The Minneapolis police officer who was seen on video kneeling on the neck of George Floyd, a handcuffed black man who died in custody after pleading that he could not breathe, has been arrested and charged ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=12335971&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 10:12:05 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>United States, Personal Finance, Entertainment, Celebrity</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>'Web of lies': Kylie Jenner isn't a billionaire, Forbes reveals</title>
			<description> Kylie Jenner is not a billionaire, according to Forbes magazine. 

The magazine now says a closer look at her finances shows evidence the star has been "inflating the size and success of her business" ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/personal-finance/news/article.cfm?c_id=12&amp;objectid=12335977&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 09:14:31 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Rotorua, Crime, National, Rotorua Daily Post, Bay of Plenty Times</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Police investigation continues after gunshots in Mamaku, Bay of Plenty</title>
			<description> Police are still investigating after multiple gunshots were heard in Mamaku.
 
A police spokeswoman said officers were called about 4:35am yesterday after shots were heard on Umuroa St.

Additional shots ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335715&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 07:02:02 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Premium, Opinion, National, Audrey Young on politics, Maori, Politics</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Audrey Young: Nikki Kaye learning to let the leader lead</title>
			<description> COMMENT: 

There is no single type of good deputy leader for a political leader but there is one type of bad deputy as Nikki Kaye and Todd Muller found out this week.

The bad deputy makes problems worse ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335709&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 06:38:30 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Newmarket, Auckland Region, Premium, Building  and  Construction, Property Investment, Commercial Property, Property, Business around NZ, Mobile Business, Business, Insurance, Commercial Construction</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>270 Newmarket insurance staff moving to CBD next year</title>
			<description> A Newmarket insurance business will move 270 staff into Auckland's central business district, after leasing an under-construction office block from Mansons TCLM.

Simon Pennington, Fidelity Life's chief ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12335794&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 06:26:44 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Wellsford, Wellington Region, Wellington, Warkworth, Waikanae, Taranaki, South Auckland, Rodney, Queenstown, Otago, Northland, New Zealand, New Plymouth, Manawatu-Whanganui, Levin, Australia, Auckland Region, National, NZ Herald Focus, Flight Centre, Travel, Weather, South Island, Marketing, Coronavirus, North Island, Airports, Traffic, Roads, Immigration, Go NZ</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Travel boom as Kiwis escape for long weekend</title>
			<description> STAY IN THE KNOW.  SIGN UP TO OUR DAILY NEWSLETTERS HERE.  

Push off, pandemic - we're back.

Kiwis have shaken off weeks of restrictions, hardship and loss to embrace our first holiday weekend under ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335954&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 06:14:58 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Business, Premium, Employment, Unemployment, Economy, Immigration, NZ Government, Coronavirus, Population</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Liam Dann: NZ faces big choice on immigration - are we ready?</title>
			<description> For better or for worse, our high rates of immigration have been a magic ingredient in New Zealand's strong economic growth over the past decade.

Now Covid-19 border closures have stopped that in its ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12335587&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 05:42:52 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>West Auckland, New Zealand, Mt Roskill, Henderson, Balclutha, Disabilities, Mental Health, Addiction, Emergency Services, Coronavirus, Crime, Family Violence, National</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>After lockdown, three women were killed. The short lives and tragic deaths of Angela, Tania and Shirley</title>
			<description> Three women were killed in the fortnight following lockdown. Overseas, such deaths are called "Coronavirus murders". But here, that masks an ugly truth. By Kirsty Johnston.  

Angela Smith's body was ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12335695&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 05:36:26 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>