<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--  RSS generated by APN on Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:58:54 +1200 --><rss version="2.0" xmlns:nzh-sem="https://www.nzherald.co.nz/schema/xml/rss-sem-metadata">
	<channel>
		<title>New Zealand Herald - Top Stories</title>
		<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/</link>
		<description>Latest Content for New Zealand Herald</description>
		<language>en-nz</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2009 APN HOLDINGS NZ</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:58:54 +1200</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>APN RSS Generator</generator>
		<managingEditor>webnews@nzherald.co.nz</managingEditor>
		<webMaster>webmaster@nzherald.co.nz</webMaster>
		<image>
			<title>New Zealand Herald - Top Stories</title>
			<url>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/images/rssLogo.png</url>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/headlines.cfm?c_id=1</link>
		</image>
		
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Health, Coronavirus, Northern Advocate, Rotorua Daily Post, Bay of Plenty Times, National, Hawkes Bay Today</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Watch live: Will the community outbreak reach 1000 cases?</title>
			<description> The total number of Covid-19 cases in the Delta community outbreak could tip past 1000 today, as locations of interest crop up outside of Auckland. 

Deputy Prime Minister Grant Robertson and director ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472698&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:45:00 +1200</pubDate>
			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202138/A_03-dpt-covidupdate011_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=Deputy Prime Minister Grant Robertson and Director of Public Health Dr Caroline McElnay. Photo /  Robert Kitchin"/>

			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Northern Advocate, Bay of Plenty Times, Rotorua Daily Post, Kahu, Newstalk ZB, Coronavirus, Wanganui Chronicle, National, Hawkes Bay Today</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Live: 'Mission critical' - Herald launches The 90% Project, major campaign to get Kiwis vaccinated, save lives ... and enjoy freedom</title>
			<description> &amp;zwnj;  

New Zealand needs to get vaccinated now to beat Delta - and that's why the NZ Herald and NZME is launching The 90% Project today.

A very high vaccination rate is vital for us to make our population ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472222&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:36:55 +1200</pubDate>
			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202138/907_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=New Zealand needs to get vaccinated now to beat Delta - and that's why NZME is launching The 90% Project today."/>

			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Business, Premium, Big Read</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Billion dollar gift: Family gives inheritance to charity</title>
			<description> In an extraordinary move, the family of the late construction pioneer and philanthropist Hugh Green has gone to court to lock up his massive legacy for nearly five decades at which time a majority shareholding ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12468370&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:14:10 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Timaru, Auckland news, Crime, Christchurch news, National</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Watch live: Police update on deaths of three children at Timaru house</title>
			<description> Police will provide an update at 1pm on the tragedy that unfolded at a Timaru house that left three children under the age of 10 dead.

A woman led away from the property after the gruesome discovery ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472716&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:13:13 +1200</pubDate>
			

			<enclosure length="20000" type="image/jpeg" url="https://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/202138/A02I3577_70x70.jpg?media_subtype_id=16|caption=Police have launched a homicide investigation after finding three people dead at a residential address in Timaru overnight. Photo / George Heard"/>

			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Business, Companies, Markets, Personal Investment, Premium</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Stock Takes: F&amp;P's sinking share price, giant waste deal underway</title>
			<description> Fisher &amp; Paykel Healthcare's recent share price weakness is being blamed on a change in recommendations for Covid treatment out of the United Kingdom.

The UK's National Institute for Health and Care ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12472063&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:09:27 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Rotorua Daily Post, Bay of Plenty Times, Kahu, Northern Advocate, Wanganui Chronicle, Coronavirus, National, Hawkes Bay Today</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>The 90% Project: Should I get vaccinated? How do I do it? Your questions answered</title>
			<description> &amp;zwnj;  

 New Zealand needs to get vaccinated now to beat Delta - and that's why NZME is launching The 90% Project.
A very high vaccination rate is vital for us to make our population safe from serious ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472030&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 12:08:01 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Business, Premium, Opinion, Best of Business Analysis</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Matthew Hooton: National's problems go much deeper than Collins</title>
			<description> OPINION: 

Judith Collins' non-existent message discipline, predilection for personal attacks, lack of media nous and tendency to see herself as a victim can't be helping her party. But National MPs are ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12472573&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:55:30 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Bay of Plenty Times, Rotorua Daily Post, National, Science, Health, Coronavirus, Immunisations, Wanganui Chronicle, Kahu</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>The 90% Project: Why NZ's vax drive must shoot for the moon</title>
			<description> &amp;zwnj; 

"Vaccinate, vaccinate, vaccinate." 

Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern couldn't have been clearer as she set out New Zealand's big pandemic priority to reporters this week. 

 

The country's Delta ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472156&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:49:57 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Sport, Premium Sport, Premium, All Blacks, Rugby</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Gregor Paul: Why we shouldn't expect fireworks from this All Black team</title>
			<description> OPINION: 

There's every chance that this weekend will not be a great advert for flowing, high-skilled, high-tempo rugby.

The Pumas seem likely to start their second test against the All Blacks with ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/sport/news/article.cfm?c_id=4&amp;objectid=12472539&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:44:30 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Tauranga, South Auckland, Otara, Mt Maunganui, Manurewa, Mangere, Bay of Plenty, Auckland news, Bay of Plenty Times, Coronavirus, Diseases, National</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>'Test immediately' - businesses outside of Auckland linked to Covid case</title>
			<description> A bakery, two petrol stations and other businesses outside of Auckland have been linked to a person with Covid-19 - the first time businesses outside of the city have been linked to the current outbreak ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472656&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:39:03 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>South Island, Christchurch news, Justice System, National, Crime</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Gloriavale investigation: At least 60 people involved in 'harmful sexual behaviour'</title>
			<description> Warning: Graphic details. This article may be triggering to some people. 

A police investigation into sexual and physical abuse inside Christian community Gloriavale has identified at least 60 people ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472680&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:34:55 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Rotorua Daily Post, Bay of Plenty Times, Wanganui Chronicle, Kahu, Opinion, National, Hawkes Bay Today</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Debbie Ngawera-Packer: Why I got vaccinated against Covid</title>
			<description> &amp;zwnj;  

 New Zealand needs to get vaccinated now to beat Delta - and that's why NZME is launching The 90% Project.

Here, M&amp;#257;ori Party co-leader Debbie Ngarewa-Packer explains why she decided to ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472603&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:30:48 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Timaru, Christchurch news, Assault and Homicide, South Island, National, Crime</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Timaru tragedy: Three children dead, person in hospital - neighbour heard a bang, sobbing, moaning</title>
			<description> Three children under the age of ten are believed to be the victims found dead in a Timaru house and a woman in hospital is the suspected killer, the Otago Daily Times reports.

Before the three children ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472609&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:22:34 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>National, Politics, Auckland news, Education</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Shifting is 'not the solution': Hipkins on why Auckland's school holidays are unchanged</title>
			<description> There will be no changes to the timing of school holidays in Auckland from the beginning of October despite the region having been in lockdown for nearly five weeks. 

Education Minister Chris Hipkins ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472685&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:13:01 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>United States, Premium, Personal Debt, Business</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Global debt is soaring — and we need to talk about it</title>
			<description> This month the thorny topic of debt is creeping back, belatedly, onto the political radar in Washington. Last week Janet Yellen, Treasury secretary, warned that the US government will run out of money ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12472741&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>South Auckland, Manurewa, Assault and Homicide, Auckland news, National, Crime</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Man, 23, charged with teen girl's murder - her family 'relieved'</title>
			<description> The family of a teenager found dead in Manurewa are "relieved and happy" the homicide investigation has led to an arrest.

A man, 23, has been charged with murder after a 16-year-old girl's body was found ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472677&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:41:40 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Business, Premium, Coronavirus, Property Investment, Residential Property, Commercial Property, Business around NZ, Mobile Business, Commercial Construction, Building  and  Construction, Auckland news, Property</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>High-flyers: Crane numbers up 6% in Covid-defying expansion</title>
			<description> New Zealand has 144 high-rise long-term tower, fixed and crawler cranes in seven cities and towns, up 6 per cent on 136 cranes earlier this year in pandemic-defying resilience.

Quantity surveying firm ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12472258&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:36:39 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>New Zealand, Coronavirus, National, Politics, Opinion, Premium</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Opinion: How key players have rated heading into Delta outbreak's third quarter</title>
			<description> OPINION:  

How the key players have rated heading into the third quarter of the Delta outbreak.

 Jacinda Ardern – 6 

Ran the 1pm press conferences effectively. Directed the dialogue between herself ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472649&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:32:41 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>Entertainment, Coronavirus</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>'Are we there yet?': Hilary Barry's shock look captures lockdown lament</title>
			<description> "Are we there yet?"

It's the question on all Aucklanders' minds as the city reaches the end of another week in level 4 lockdown - and Seven Sharp host Hilary Barry has once again captured the mood of ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/entertainment/news/article.cfm?c_id=1501119&amp;objectid=12472641&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:28:43 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item> 
		<item>
            <nzh-sem:metakeywords>National, Crime</nzh-sem:metakeywords> 
			<title>Police seize almost 1000 guns, $5m in organised crime crackdown</title>
			<description> Police are extending a six-month operation aimed at cracking down on gangs and organised crime after seizing almost 1000 firearms, nearly $5 million in cash and arresting 800 people.

Operation Tauwhiro ...</description>
			<link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12472647&amp;amp;ref=rss</link>
			<author>newsfeeds@nzherald.co.nz</author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 10:19:35 +1200</pubDate>
			
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>